100 rated chess, but the number of reactions is how much distance you must travel this game.
17 plus 6 is 23. 33 41 50 56 63 71 78 84 90 95 100 103.
Which is a lot. We get a 204 from India.
And I didn't know that you can take a selfie inside a prison.
E4. The furthest I can possibly go in my first move, is 2 squares.
E5. The piece that can move the most freely is obviously my queen.
I'll open the way for the woman. Perfect. Queen takes D4.
Knight C6. Pulling her back is not a very good option. Queen sideway.
Queen F6. I really want to move my queen again to cover more squares,
but since there are not many safe squares left for her.
Knight F3. According to the Pythagoras theorem, my knight traveled a distance of square root of 2
squared plus 1 squared. Which is square root of 5, so I'll add 2.236 into my counter.
Bishop C5. Bishop G5. Before you jump down to the comment below and say that I'm a noob.
Please listen to me. You see, a few thousand years ago,
God made a mistake to let Adam meet his maiden. When they are both f***ed.
Man I also wish I can meet a new woman when we're both f***ed. Such an amazing scenario.
But anyway, my point is that even God can make mistakes, so the fact that I made a mistake of
blundering my rook is totally acceptable. Ha! A random guy once said. If your enemy
doesn't spot your mistake, then you didn't make any. But anyway. That blunders a woman,
but I don't want to spend a turn on a 1.4 length of movement. So I guess.
What the f***?
[Music]