100 rated chess, but you can't capture a piece. Not pawn. The turn after it moves.
Very challenging. We get a 138 from Mexico. With diamond membership.
E4, nothing wrong so far. Knight f6. E5,
let's see if the diamond membership taught him anything about moving the horses.
Well, that blunders a horsey, but since it's just moved, I cannot take it, due to the rules.
Therefore, d4, I mean if he can just leave it there for another turn, I can take it.
Well of course, except for this case. G4. Knight g7. Fun fact, that is still. A book move.
I'm really curious to see who wrote this book about the modern defense Norwegian defense 3 e5
knight h5 4 g4 dot dot dot. But anyway, bishop h6. d5. Aha, the French move is possible,
but sadly, I don't like it. c4. Once again, on passant, is not forced.
Knight e6. I'll take his bishop. King takes. Very aggressive. c takes d5. Somehow that looks like a
blunder to me, but I don't really know why. Knight takes d4. Aha, now that is really a blunder,
but since his knight has just moved, I cannot take it due to the rules. So I guess, knight c3.
c5 is coming, and sadly I have to say, I will once again not take on passant.
Nevermind. That blunders a horsie. And after missing the free knight for like 200 times,
stockfish says. Great move. F*** you stockfish. Bishop takes g4. e6. f takes e6. At least he
didn't blunder his king, but that still blunders a lot. King f7 is forced. d takes e6 check.
And he resigns. Mission accomplished.
*outro*