100 rated chess, but only pawns can capture.
This sounds absolutely impossible, but since it also gave me a very clear idea of what I have to do, you can count on me.
We get a 123 from Italy.
Talking about Italy, better book your plane tickets right now.
E4. The plan is very simple. I open up the position, he blunders his king, I checkmate without captures.
Therefore, d5. And then he doesn't capture.
The worst thing is even I cannot capture because queen takes ends the video.
Knight f6. Man I hate this game.
Now he takes. You know what? Change of plan.
The plan is very simple. I'll trap his queen in the middle of the board, then he'll get desperate and resign from the game,
and even though a random queen capture ends the video, there is no way a guy who doesn't even have the gut to capture with a pawn can make a capture with a queen.
Absolutely.
Knight bd7.
Bishop c4.
E5.
This is possible, but there is no way a 100 rated guy knows about the French move, especially when he's an Italian.
He played that move. In two f***ing seconds.
You know what? It's fine, that move shocked me a little, but it's not like it does any harm to the video.
F takes c6. As long as no random capture happens, everything is still under control.
What the f***?
[Music]