100 rated chess, but you are far-sighted, your pieces and pawns cannot take any pieces or pawns
within a three-tile distance of your piece. Too easy! We get a 120 from Germany.
e4. Since I cannot take anything within three tiles, pushing center pawns or developing a knight
is not very efficient, therefore, b6. Playing the bishop on the long diagonal is definitely
the best way to start this challenge. Qh5. Very aggressive. Be7. Bc4. g6. Alright, Bf7 is forcing
Kxf7, which makes me a fool for ending my own video, but since it's obviously blundering a bishop,
who plays like that anyway. Right? Of course. e6. Again, Qxf7 is forcing Kxf7, which makes me a fool
for ending my own video, but just like last time, it is obviously blundering a queen, who plays like
that anyway. Right? No doubt. F5. My bishop is 4 squares away from his queen, which is longer than
3, so why not try our luck at winning the woman? g4. Bg7. I can already see that this video is
going in a very wrong direction. Gxf5. Nc6, there's nothing I can do about this pawn.
Fxe6. Qf7 is checkmate in 1, therefore, Ne5. I mean if he really goes Qf7, I technically cannot
take his queen because the knight only travels a 2 square distance every move, but of course he's
not going to play it. Right? Of course. Ke7 is forced. Well, I mean at least now Qf7 is not
forcing me to end the video anymore. Qf4. That blunders a bishop, but my knight can never take
anything. So I guess, Nh6, as long as he doesn't take my knight right here, I guess I can still
bring this game back into my control. That blunders a queen, but it's only 2 squares away.
Kf8. Qf4 check. Ke7. A repetitional draw will be very convenient. Of course it doesn't happen.
Moving the king up is obviously way too dank. Kf8. I mean Qxd8 is forcing Rx which ends the video,
but since he is the attacking side, of course he's not gonna trade down his strongest piece
on the entire board. Right?
[Music]