100 rated chess, but you have to move your king if you can. I normally don't take on easy challenges.
But you know, we need to relax sometimes. Victim is a 151 guy from the US. I'm so sorry you have
to accompany me in this easy challenge. E4. The plan is simple. Give the king no square to move,
because as a grandmaster once said, if the king doesn't have anywhere to go, he can't go anywhere.
Therefore, B6. All of these pieces and pawns will not move for this entire game.
Bc4. Bb7. Nothing wrong so far. Qh5. Very aggressive. G6 is kinda forced. I mean if he
takes my F pawn now, Kx is forced, and then I may have to move my king for the entire game.
But who plays like that anyway? Right? Of course, I really want to play F6 to attack his queen,
because even though the F7 square will be empty, his light square bishop is still controlling that
square, which means I still don't have to move my king, but on second thought,
that move is obviously a bit too risky. So I guess, Nf6. Qg3. That blunders a pawn.
Qf3. Oh, wait. This guy tricked me. He tricked me to take his pawn, then he can go Qf3 threatening
to take on F7, and even though there is E6 best move right now, I cannot play that because it
gives my king a free square to move, which means it's Nd6 forced, and then there is Bxf7 check
Nxf7 Qxb7, and even though materials are equal, my knight won't be able to move anymore because
it has to stops the king from moving. It's fine, at least he won't take my pawn with his queen.
Nevermind. Wow. Now NxBxKx and then I'll have to move my king for the entire game.
Ha! Nevermind. Mission accomplished.
[Music]