100 rated chess, but it's American Independence Day, no pieces, or pawns, can die on such a happy
day. Let's go, we get a 2 2 9 that is not from America. Pushing center pawns is just asking them
to be taken. Therefore, knight f3, expecting e5 and I win a pawn. Very convenient. That blunders
a pawn, since my opponent is not from the US, his pieces and pawns don't have to live to celebrate
the day. Queen e7. Very aggressive. I'll go back, I mean queen takes e2 will immediately end the
video right now and everyone will cry for Edward's death instead of having fun in a holiday,
but who plays like that anyway? Right? No doubt. Knight c3. Okay I mean taking one of these horses
also ends the video, and actually, when you think about it, he played queen e7 to attack my knight,
I moved my knight to f3, and then he moved his queen to f6, maybe his purpose was to take my
knight at all cost. Of course not. D3. Okay I know pushing center pawns is very dangerous,
but since his e-pawn is already dead, his c-pawn is the only pawn that can harm my video,
and not many people are aggressive enough to push their c-pawn forward. Queen e6. In every other
videos, I would have gone knight b5 to try my luck at forking his queen, but in this game,
even if I can win the woman, a pawn can still take my knight and absolutely destroy the video.
Therefore, g3. No need to rush. Knight f5. Bishop h3. I mean now knight e3 will pretty much force
the video to end, but he should be able to see, that knight e3 is actually blundering to bishop
takes e6 knight takes d1 knight b5 brilliant move knight a6 bishop h3 and his knight is trapped.
Right? Always have faith in the 100 rated players. That blunders a horsey to e4 bishop f5,
but again, pushing center pawns is obviously way too dangerous, therefore, knight d4. In no world
do you take my horsey. On second thought, maybe I was a fool because that move was probably the
best move. But anyway, happy birthday America.
[Music]