100 rated chess, but you have Alzheimer. Every 5th move, you must move 1 piece, or pawn,
back to its original location,
because you don't remember moving it there. Let's go. We get a 177 from the US.
d4. e5. I mean the pawns can never go back to their original square,
but since we still have 4 moves to go until move 5, there's nothing to be worried about.
c3. Not very aggressive. d5. knight f3. e4. Okay, that is 3 moves in, which means my next move has
to be a piece move, and then I'll have to bring that exact piece back to the original square the
move after. knight e5. Bishop d6. In no world do you just go crazy and take this pawn just
because I'll have to move my bishop back. Of course. That blunders a horsey, but sadly,
bishop f8 is forced. Bishop f4. Aha! Now that really blunders a horsey. I mean if he can also
blunder his queen, that will be very convenient. Of course that doesn't happen. Bishop f5. Provoking
g4 weakening his king is definitely a great idea. Knight d2. Bishop d6 bishop d6 queen d6.
Alright, one of these moves coming up next. g4. It's the bishop then. f takes e4. Bishop takes g4.
I mean if he can play h3 right now to blunder queen g3 checkmate in one, that will be very
convenient. I solemnly swear, that this guy is not a paid actor. Queen g3. Checkmate. Mission
accomplished, but since the video is still so short, I'll answer some of your comments instead.
A lesson learned. Being a coward is much better than being an idiot. Ha! Coward. Since you
achieved a better position in the video but still lost, I would argue your argument to be invalid.
Well, I'm better than my viewers.
I'll see you next time.
[Music]