100 rated chess, but all checks must be captures and all captures must be checks.
I can't believe that people can react into the word hard,
when this is such an extremely easy challenge. We get a 174 from Brazil.
Very handsome. E4 knight c6 d4. Nothing to think about yet,
this challenge is way too easy for me to spend my precious time to actually build a plan.
Knight c6. E5. Knight e4. Aha! That blunders a horsey, but since I actually cannot take it
because that capture is not a check, bishop d3 instead. I'm trying to provoke f5 protecting the
knight, so that my pieces will have more chance at checking his king in the future.
Didn't happen. This capture is still undoable, and I have a feeling that this game is going
very wrong very quickly. Let's try to end it real fast. This officially saves his knight as now he
can play f5 and don't have to worry about f3 anymore. Nevermind. Blocking with knight or
bishop is just provoking a capture that I cannot fight back. C3 is kinda forced.
And in no world do you take this pawn. Or that pawn.
Wow! Now everything is hanging, but nothing is hanging.
Well, you know what they say. If your opponent hangs 3 pieces at once, you attack their king.
Queen h5. The plan is very simple. He takes my bishop. I move my king. Then I move my knight,
I move my knight, I move my queen checkmate. Exactly as planned. King e2. This is not a royal fork.
You know what? I'm not gonna play this game anymore. Have a great day.
(upbeat music)
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh