100 rated chess, but if your opponent's clock is an even number after his turn,
then you can only move to even ranks, the same thing also applies with odd number.
Too easy.
E3. 4 minute 54 seconds, which is an even number. Therefore, G6, unlike yesterday when I had to rely
on the RNG god, today's RNG is totally depending on my opponent.
Knight F3. Odd number. D5. G3. Even number. Bishop G4. Ha, now if he can just move the
knight away and stop the clock on an odd number time to allow bishop takes D1,
that will be extremely convenient.
Well, I guess sometimes convenient things do happen in our lives. Bishop takes D1.
King takes, odd move again, E5. One more odd move please.
Even move. It's fine. D4. E takes D4. Even move again, but again, it is still fine,
statistically speaking, next move should be an odd move.
Nevermind. Knight C6, I can see that the RNG stuff is starting to turn its ass against me.
Bishop G2. The 4th even move in a row, and you know what, I'll just go queen F6. I'm forking
2 things, 1 in an odd rank, 1 in an even rank, and as long as he doesn't see knight F3, I should be
able to take something next. After this check, king D8 is kinda forced. Knight takes F7 check.
Wow. That blunders a horsey, but since the clock is at an even number, king C8 is forced.
Now don't tell me that he's gonna go bishop H3 forces king B8 and then rook E8 check on an
odd number time which ends the video because I have no legal odd rank moves. Thank you.
King D7 is forced, but still, this guy is totally destroying me with his random.
Nevermind. King takes E8. Knight takes H8. Ah ha, after all those crazy moves,
I finally have a chance to attack. King E1 is forced, queen H1 looks very tempting,
but as everyone can see the very obvious checkmate in 3 in this position, it has to be D3.
Knight takes G6. Queen E2. Checkmate. Mission accomplished.
[Music]