If you lose a trade, you trade. Sounds absolutely terrifying, but still doable.
We get a 100 rated guy from Spain. E4. We can never lose a trade with pawns,
and even though A6 forces a bishop sac as it makes a losing trade for me.
I mean who plays like that anyway? Right?
No doubt. D4. Again, pawns can never make a losing trade.
E takes D4. Aha! I normally like to sac a pawn here, but that will force Q takes D7 a losing
trade. Bishop D3 instead. Blocking my own queen keeps the woman safe. F6. Not very aggressive.
F4. Knight H6. F5. I'll let the pawns open the way first, and then my pieces can attack his king.
G6. This capture is not forced, but since I can at least make an equal trade and not a losing one,
I'll take it. The challenge said losing trades are forced,
but didn't say that it bans equal trades or winning ones. Bishop takes. Equal trade.
But it's actually winning. G takes H7. I mean if he can also let this pawn change his gender,
that will be very convenient. Queen H5 wins a bishop, but if he goes rook block instead,
I'll have to make a losing trade. Therefore, I'll promote. King E7. Queen trade is really nice,
but losing trade is forced. Bishop takes. Knight D2 F5 E F5. Have to say that it is getting pretty
difficult as my development moves can also harm my material balance, but if he can make a bad move
like moving his king forward right now, I solemnly swear, that this guy is not a paid actor. Knight
check. King forward again. I really want queen F3, but it may lead to a forced losing trade in
the future. So I guess, queen H5 instead. I need to make sure that my queen attacks absolutely
nothing besides his king. King F4. Very aggressive. Knight H3 queen E2. Checkmate. Mission accomplished.
[music]