100 rated chess, but you have wild horses. Another piece, not porn, must always be touching your
horses. Well even though I personally don't recommend touching wild horses since you may
get kicked in the face. But anyway, let's start the game. We get a 125 from Brazil. E4. E5.
Still theory. The plan is simple, I just need to keep the knights in their starting position so
that they can always touch my rooks, which means I will not be moving any of these pieces in this
game. D4. Since all I have is a queen and 2 bishops, I need to maximize my bishop's power,
and after E D4 C3 D C3 Bishops C4 C B2 Bishop E2, I will have 2 very strong bishops eyeing
down his kingside. Nevermind. I'll take this pawn then, well I mean opening up the bishops is also
good enough. Queen takes, bishop D3. Queen F6. F4, the pawns are also very important in this game
since I'm lacking materials, so I'll make sure to use them to their full potential. Bishops E5.
Ah ha, he is obviously threatening to take my knight, which makes my knight die, which means
there is no piece that can touch it anymore, because no one can touch a ghost, which means
I'll have to end my video. Therefore, E5, I mean not E2 to let the king touch the knight was
obviously a safer move, but he should be able to see that bishop takes G1 is blundering a woman.
Right? Of course. G3. Again, even though he can end my video right now, he should be able to see
that taking my knight is still blundering his queen. Right? Absolutely. Okay even though I
should really be playing knight E2 right now. F5. Again, he can end my video, but he should be able
to see that it's once again just blundering his woman. Right? Okay so I think he did see the thing,
but I have no idea how did he come up with this move. That blunders a woman. Ha, and even better,
now he can't even end my video, no matter how hard he tries. Resignation. Mission accomplished.
[Music]