If a piece, or pawn, lands on c4, your king gets blown up.
Ha! Too easy! We get a 172 from South Africa. Well I mean he can just play c4 right now and
immediately end the video, but as you can see, there's nothing I can do about that.
Thank god! Now c4 and bishop c4 are both threats to end the video, therefore, d5, well I mean he
can still play c4 and gambit his e-pawn, but most people don't play like that. Right?
Of course, but that move is actually also very bad, because it means that he really wants to
go bishop c4. Therefore, I'll reinforce my d-pawn. This mission is being much more difficult than it
should be because I started with the black pieces, but if he can just push his e-pawn
instead of taking my pawn, that will be very convenient. Well, I guess we can all agree,
that sometimes very convenient things can also happen in our lives. b5. Ha! Now c4 is just
blundering a pawn, and bishop c4 is not even an option. Queen e2. Bishop f5, well I mean if he
can also blunder his c-pawn next, that will also be very convenient. d3. Oh no no no no no no no no!
We can clearly see that he's in a very prepared position to play c4, which ends the video,
and as far as I can see, there is only one way to prevent it from happening. Bishop takes d3.
Please take back with your c-pawn, and since I'm attacking your queen, in no world do you play c4
here. Queen takes. I guess that's fair enough. Knight d7, c4 is just blundering a pawn now,
and since I'm also attacking his e-pawn, there's no chance for that to happen right now.
c3. Ha! Not even close. I'll take this pawn, queen c4 is obviously not an option.
Queen f5. Queen d6. I'm down for bishop f4 f6 and we trade everything because this is getting way
more dangerous than it should have been, and since he's been consistently threatening to end my video,
I think we can all agree that he is not a paid actor. Wait!
Well, I'll take the free win then, and he's definitely not a paid actor.
[Music]