100 rated chess, but you are Batman. You can only capture pieces that have captured your pieces,
and you only play on dark squares. Each segment of this challenge can even make a challenge on
its own, but I think I can do it. We get a 182 from Italy. E4. I can only play on dark squares.
E5. It's actually pretty lucky when I get the black pieces because I can make use of my queen
and my dark bishop more easily. Qh5. D6 can defend this pawn, but it blocks my dark bishop.
Qf6 instead. Bc4. Bc5. Qxf7 is pretty concerning because I cannot take his queen on a light square.
But who plays like that anyway? Right? No doubt. That blunders a pawn and probably will also lead
to a lot of advantage for me. But since his f-pawn hasn't taken anything from me yet,
I cannot take it due to the rules. Nh6 instead. The plan is very simple. He takes my knight,
my queen recaptures, and as my queen leaves my f-pawn, queen takes f7 king d8,
then I'll have a chance to sneak my queen straight into his territory and destroy his king.
Didn't happen. Qb6. In no world do you take this pawn.
Well that is still acceptable because even though my knight cannot capture due to the rules,
I can move my king. Bp7 ends the video as I cannot take his bishop because that is not a revenge,
but I have faith that my opponents won't be making such an obvious blunder. Right?
My god that was close. And in this position, something unexpected happened. I got a power outage.
Therefore...
(upbeat music)
(victorious music)