100 rated chess, but all pieces and pawns must be adjacent all the time.
Disclaimer. This video is only for entertainment purpose,
please don't try to stay adjacent to other people in the real world with a pandemic going on.
Let's go. We get a 135 from Colombia. Well, now E4, D4, C4, or any other 4s,
is gonna end the video. But you know, there's nothing I can do about it.
No. I disagree. Let's just say, the first move doesn't count.
E5, my E pawn is next to his E pawn, so it doesn't end the video.
No. How about, the first 2 moves don't count.
And I'm not a coward, I'm just trying to be fair. D5, okay. Now the challenge really starts,
and I think we can all agree, that this, can also be considered, as adjacent.
E takes D5, queen H5 is a threat, therefore, knight F6, and in no world do you play D6 now.
Yes, D6 is a threat, therefore, bishop D6. Queen G3. Very aggressive. Castle. And since my king
is not in the center anymore, in no world do you play bishop B5 now. Knight F3. That blunders a
horsey. E4. Knight G5. Aha, that blunders a queen. But should I even take it though,
because after I take his queen, he can get to play D6, which ends the video.
You know what? I don't believe. Bishop takes G3. Okay, now just calm down, and take my bishop.
Perfect. There's a free pawn on D5, but of course, that will leave his knight very lonely on G5,
which makes me a fool, for ending my own video. Therefore, queen D6, he should be able to see,
that bishop B5 is blundering queen takes D5, forking his knight and bishop.
He saw it. Knight D7. Rook F5. Very aggressive. Knight E5. Rook takes E5, queen takes E5,
now D4 ends the video, but he should be able to see, that there is E takes D3 on passan check
king D2 queen E2 check king C3 queen takes C2 check king D4 queen takes C1 winning a bishop,
a rook, and his king is in the middle of the board.
What the f-
[Music]