100 rated chess, but you reveal the challenge after 5 moves. Too easy. We get a 1 31 from Thailand.
This has to be my first ever Thai opponent on this channel, so let's welcome him with a massacre.
E3. Not very aggressive. E5. I only have 5 free moves, so the best plan is obviously
to develop as many pieces and open up as many lines as possible. E3. Again, not very aggressive.
D5. Fully open up the pieces. Queen F3. Spending 1 more move just to attack the queen sounds like
a very bad idea, knight F6. C4. Bishop G5. I mean if I can't attack his queen with my pawn,
I can attack her with my bishop. Queen G3. 4 moves out of 5, and of course as usual for my last move
before opening up the challenge. I have to move my queen. Sometimes this decision ends up really
badly, but I don't want to regret not spending time with my woman. C takes D5. Alright. Here we
go. Any pieces, or pawns, that is currently on a white square is frozen and cannot be moved for
the rest of the game. Very funny. I'll take this pawn. It's fine, I still have these pieces and
pawns with me, and even though this knight is currently on a light square, it was on a dark
square at the moment the challenge begins, so this knight is not frozen. H3. No way for me to save
that bishop. Bishop D6. A useless bishop dies. E4. Please don't see anything. Ha! Thank you. But the
question is, do I even want to take his queen though? I mean I only have this many materials
to win this entire game, so losing a bishop for a queen is probably not that good of a trade.
Oh well who gives a sh*t. I'll eat that woman. I mean who knows,
maybe he'll decide to be an unpaid actor and resign the game right now.
Ha! Mission accomplished.
(upbeat music)