100 rated chess, but you are kamikaze. If a piece or pawn captures, it has to capture every move
until it dies. Ah ha, it's been a long time since I last get to pick such an easy challenge like
this one. We get a 240 from India. E4. So normally I would have prepared a good plan to tackle on the
chosen challenge, but since this challenge is obviously way too easy, there is absolutely no
need to prepare... anything. D5. Ah ha. I'll take that pawn. From now on, Edward can only move
with a capture. C6. And that is a capture. Ha, can't be any more convenient. B takes C6. D4.
G5. Ah ha. That blunders a pawn, but do I even take it though, because if I take it, my bishop
won't be able to move anymore, unless there is something for it to capture, which means a move
like H6 will be forcing me to make a desperado. Well as always, I'm not a coward. I mean at least
he cannot play F6 because of queen H5 check. Nevermind. I'll have to sacrifice my bishop,
but before that, queen H5 check. King D7 is forced. Ah ha. As you can see, this pawn is
actually controlling this very crucial center square, so if I take his pawn, he may decide to
replace it with another pawn, which still controls that important E5 square, so I guess, knight F3.
I want him to take my bishop, and then I can move my knight to E5. F takes G5. Knight E5 check.
King C7 is bringing his king to safety, but for some unknown reasons, I feel like this
giga chad is gonna advance his king forward. As expected. Bishop C4 check. I think king D6
blundering a triple fork or blocking with the queen should be the best move here, but since
those moves are not very human-like moves, he should be going king F5 blundering queen F3
checkmate in 1 or king F6 blundering queen F7 checkmate in 1. Right? I solemnly swear,
that this guy is not a paid actor. But anyway, queen F7 checkmate. Mission accomplished.
[Music]