100 rated chess, but you reveal the challenge after you lose your queen.
This is absolutely meaningless as there is no way my 100 rated opponent can take my queen when I
don't allow him to do so. But in contrast, it actually makes me even more curious what can be
under this mysterious black section. So let's uncover it ourselves. We get a 100 rated American.
E4. D5. The only way I can see the challenge is to lose my queen. Queen H5. D takes E4.
On second thought, maybe sacrificing my queen right now is too early. Bishop C4 instead. To be
clear, I'm not a coward, I'm just trying to approach this challenge in the most optimal way possible.
Knight F6. That blunders a pawn. With check. King D7 is forced. I think queen E5 is best aiming for
queen E6 checkmate in one, but I don't need a checkmate when my queen is still alive, queen F5,
and he still blunders checkmate regardless. Bishop check instead. King down, bishop takes C8.
I also need to avoid a resignation before I lose my queen, because even though that
counts as a mission accomplished, I want to see what the challenge is first.
Knight B D7. Bishop B7 rook B8 bishop C6. Rook B6. Very aggressive. It is now 10 moves into the
game, and I don't think I want to delay sacrificing my queen any further as it only provokes more
people calling me a coward. Queen takes D7. Queen takes will be very convenient.
Well I guess everyone knows backward knight moves are very difficult to see,
so this guy is obviously not a paid actor. We'll see the challenge first.
You maidenless fool your king is enraged every move you make from now on must be very aggressive
if you do not give a check every 2 moves the video will end very aggressively.
Check. King takes. I have to give another check within 2 moves.
Knight F3. The plan is very simple. He doesn't take my knight.
Check.
(upbeat music)