100 rated chess, but you need to make a position where you can checkmate your opponent in at least
3 different ways. If they resign, you lose. Very challenging. We get a 2 24 from Brazil.
D4. The best opening to get an early checkmate against D4, is of course, E5. England, gambit.
E3. Not very aggressive. E4 knight H3 D5 bishop E2. I'll take that horsey. Destroying his king
side can never be a bad choice. G takes H3. Bishop D6. Alright, please castle. Maybe later.
Queen H4. Bishop back. Well, not very aggressive. So in order to create 3 ways to checkmate him,
I need a lot of pieces into the attack straight at his king. Therefore, knight D7. Bishop E5. C6.
A4. Ah ha, that blunders a bishop, but if I take his bishop, my opponent may decide to resign,
as that is literally the only piece he's been moving from the beginning of the game.
So I guess, I'll take this pawn instead. Bishop D2. Queen G2. I mean I technically don't want to
take this rook to avoid a resignation, but putting the queen here should help a lot in order to
attack his king. Knight C3. Knight F6. Queen E2. Ah ha, he obviously wants to castle queen side,
which is definitely going to be really bad for this video because my queen is still on the king
side. Therefore, I have to take this rook. Queen F1 queen F3. Stopping his king from castling.
Queen back to E2. Oh no. He wants to block my queen's view and castle, so I need to go,
queen H1 again, queen F1 queen F3. I mean in case he really goes queen E2 next, I cannot go back to
H1 due to 3-fold repetition, but who knows, maybe he himself doesn't really want to draw.
Ha, of course he doesn't want to draw. I'll take this pawn. Queen H1. That blunders a queen.
You may say that taking his queen is a stupid idea because that is just provoking him to resign the
game, but no, since he didn't want to draw by repetition, he is obviously aiming for a win,
and someone aiming for a win obviously never resigns. Of course.
What the f-
[Music]