100 rated chess, but you can't move a piece, not pawn, until its brother is dead.
Very challenging.
We get a 2 47 from the US.
D4.
So I believe the only way to do this challenge, is to sacrifice pieces on one side, and then
try to use the pieces in the other side.
Therefore, C5. I'll get this pawn all the way down to my horsey right here.
And of course, since I only have 1 king and 1 queen, I cannot move them through the entire
game.
D takes C5.
B6.
C takes B6.
Ok, let's think about this carefully.
After B takes A7 and A takes B8, he'll make a queen, but I cannot take his new woman,
because both of my rooks are still alive.
Therefore, H5.
I want to go H4, then after his new queen takes my rook, I can safely develop my other
rook to H5.
B takes A7.
H4.
A pawn changed gender.
And since my B knight is dead, knight F6.
Man, this challenge actually reminds me of Spider-Man, because he only lives seriously,
after his uncle Ben is already dead.
Queen takes A8.
Exactly as planned.
Rook H5.
Ok.
Now the game truly begins.
I'm being down 19 points of material, and if we include my queen as well, it's actually
plus 28 for my opponent.
Very, challenging.
Wait what?
That blunders a queen.
But I cannot take that queen, due to the mission's rule.
And after queen takes D8, the mission's failed, since I can't move my king either.
What the f*** am I supposed to do then?
E5.
Now please get tunneled vision and focus in the center.
My god that is scary.
But anyway, that forces me to take a queen.
Knight takes D7.
Even though I've won a queen, the situation is actually not much better than before.
I hate this guy.
♪ ♪