100 rated chess, but you have to pre-move every 7th move. That sounds a bit too easy.
Let's change it to 2nd. We get a 2 59 from India. E4. E5. Now the most popular move here
has to be knight f3, but since this is a 100 rated game, queen h5 is more likely going
to happen. Therefore, I'll pre-move. Knight c6. Aha! So he decided to go bishop b5, and
then bishop back to c4. Very funny. And now I find it really difficult to give commentaries
in such a game like this. Knight f6 bishop c5. That's pretty risky though, since if he
plays crazy things like d4, my bishop is dead. Queen e2. F3. Knight d4. Maybe e6. Queen d3
and knight c3. I want to play bishop e6, but if I play it now, I won't be able to make
a good pre-move, since I don't know whether he will take it or not. Therefore, castle,
and then bishop e6. In this case, even if he take my bishop, I can still actively take
it back. Wait wait what? I'll be honest, I didn't even know what happened back there.
But anyway, let's start an attack. Bishop takes c4. I'm calculating that after queen
takes c4, knight takes e4, knight takes e4, d5, queen takes c5, d takes e4, f takes e4
blunders queen h4 check. Of course he can also not go f takes e4, but I still believe
this is a worthy risk. Therefore, I'll pre-move. Knight takes e4. King d1. That blunders a
queen. But I already pre-moved. And now 2 of my pieces are hanging. Are you serious?
And then he made the correct choice of taking my knight. f5, queen f6 pre-move. Queen g4.
That blunders the queen again. And I cannot take it again. Queen g3. Rook ke8. e4. b3.
Oh, I forgot that my bishop is still alive over there. Alright it's fine. e takes f3,
knight takes f4, oh wait he can still take with pawn. Let's go for f4. Oh he really took
back with pawn. Queen f2. That blunders a pawn. And let's pull my knight back. I mean
who cares about that rook in the corner anyway. My knight is much stronger here in the middle
of the board.
What the f-
*outro music*