If two consecutive moves of one player are of the same vector, the video ends.
So in term of comparing two vectors, there are two things, called magnitude, and direction.
But who cares, all you need to do, is just to watch the video, and I will show you all
of the moves that can end the video during the game.
We get a 2.56 from the US.
With premium membership.
E4.
Since the first move is E4, the video is going to end if my opponent plays D4, C4, B4, or
any of these moves, on his next move.
Therefore, D5.
Of course he can still play those moves, but most people usually just take the pawn, right?
Yes.
Queen takes D5.
Now bishop E2 ends the video, but let's be real, no one plays like that.
Right?
Of course.
Queen back to D8.
And there's no such thing like knight H3 or knight D5, right?
Perfect.
Now there are knight E5 and knight B5 ending the video, but sadly, the only move that can
stop both of them is queen D5, which blunders a queen, and I don't think losing a queen
like that is necessary right now.
Therefore, knight C6.
I mean who plays knight B5 anyway.
Right?
D4.
Pawn moves are very scary, since there are so many of them, and their moves are pretty
much always the same.
Therefore, bishop G4.
Now please go H3 to attack my bishop, or even D5 is also fine.
H3.
Yes.
If I pull my bishop back, he may decide to go D5, which ends the video.
Therefore, bishop takes F3.
In no world do you end my video right now.
Queen takes.
Now there are queen H5 and bishop E3 ending the video, and even though queen H5 looks
like a guy walking down the street without closing his zipper, bishop E3 actually looks
very natural.
Therefore, knight takes D5.
Go back to D1 please.
And the best thing is, after queen D3 or queen D1, there is actually no move that can end
the video.
What the f-
[music]