100 rated chess. But you have to take any pieces or pawns when it is possible for you to do so.
Well, this is obviously going to be a total disaster. But again, I can't argue with money.
Therefore, let's find an opponent.
We get a 268 from Australia.
E4.
E5.
So far so good, as long as he doesn't play such an absurd move like A3, forces bishop takes A3.
D3.
Very solid.
Nc6.
I can already see a lot of you guys are going to say, oh you should have played d6, since it stops the bishop from seeing A3.
Well, that's right, but I don't think he's going to play that move, so there's no need to do such thing.
G4.
Very aggressive.
He's obviously threatening to go G5, forcing queen takes G5, which blunders a woman.
Therefore, H6.
H4.
You know what?
I'm just going to end this video here. I don't want to play this game anymore, sayonara, see you tomorrow.
[Music]