100 rated chess, but all captures have to be within 1 square radius.
Diagonal counts.
Well, this is too hard, so I guess we also need to say, knights captures are fine.
Actually, even after exempting the knights, I still can't see there is any way for me
to accomplish this.
But anyway, we get a 2 34 from the US.
G4.
Very aggressive.
D5.
Bishop G2.
Ah ha!
The grob gambit.
Normally, I would have taken this pawn without thinking anything much.
But of course, that is too far away.
So I guess.
E5.
E4.
Again, very, aggressive.
D4.
Let's play a bit more aggressively.
H5.
Bishop F3.
I really want to take this pawn, but after bishop takes, his bishop will be on an open
diagonal, which is too easy for him to end my video.
Therefore, knight F6.
My best-case scenario would be G5, knight G4, bishop takes G4, H takes G4.
Knight H3.
Well, that blunders 2 pieces, which is even better than my best-case scenario.
H takes G4.
Bishop takes.
I really want to go bishop takes G4, which forks his knight and his queen.
But of course, that is against the rules.
Knight takes G4.
And in no world do you take my horde.
What the f-
[outro music]