If a piece, or pawn, gets captured, identical pieces, or pawns, can't move anymore.
Playing 3 minute splits on a 100 rated account.
Ah ha! This challenge reminds me of Halloween.
You see, when a bunch of kids comes to your home and ask for candy, you can just refuse one of them, and everyone walks away.
Empty handed.
And with that out of the way, let's find an opponent.
We get a 1 54 from Peru.
G3. Not very aggressive.
But actually, that should be good for me, since I don't really want any captures to happen too early.
D5.
Bishop H3.
Ah ha! Now my best move should be bishop takes H3.
But then according to the rules, my bishops won't be able to move, and if this bishop can't move, then my king won't be able to castle, and I have to develop my rook in a weirdo way.
Also, if I just leave the situation like this, he may be going to take my bishop, which also leads to the same situation.
Therefore, E6.
B3. Again, not very aggressive.
Knight F6.
E3. This guy has to be the nicest 100 rated I have ever met.
Knight C6.
Bishop A3. Once again, offering a bishop trade.
But I think, I can take it this time.
And of course, now my light square bishop cannot move anymore, and even if he doesn't take my dark square bishop back, I won't be able to move it either.
Knight takes A3.
I'll castle.
C3.
Queen D6.
Knight C2.
Let's play a bit more aggressively.
Knight E4.
Queen F3.
E5.
Since my bishop cannot move, it would be perfect if he can make a trade.
Thank you.
Rook A takes C8.
D4.
That blunders a pawn.
But should I even take it though?
Because after I take that pawn, all of my pawns cannot move.
No.
I think I should take
this pawn.
This move looks pretty bad in normal chess.
But I believe that it should be my best choice for this video.
He takes D4.
Rook C2 E8.
Queen E2.
That blunders a queen.
Knight takes C3.
Oh.
Wait.
Now if he takes my rook, I won't be able to take his queen, because of the rules.
Are you serious?
He is really taking his time here.
Oh.
He chose to move his king instead.
And now offering a draw.
You know what?
Even though I can win a full queen, my queen won't be able to move after that.
Therefore, let's accept it.
Mission kinda accomplished.
[Music]