100 rated chess, but you have to move the same piece.
Or pawn.
As your opponent did last move.
Alright, this is obviously not doable.
But still, there's no way I'm scared of it.
Let's find an opponent.
[Music]
We get a 235 from Uruguay.
E4.
Well, a pawn move.
D5.
D4.
I'll take it.
So far so good.
Queen takes.
Alright, a queen move.
I would love to play queen F6, queen takes F6, knight takes F6.
But of course, after queen takes F6, I will have to make a queen move, and since my queen is already dead,
the mission is failed.
Therefore, queen E7 is kinda forced.
King D1.
Ok dude.
King D8 is forced.
Things are going very wrong very quickly.
Knight F3.
Thank you.
Knight C6.
Queen C4.
Moving my queen up is too risky, since if she is attacked by another piece, she can't move.
So I guess, queen E8 is kinda forced.
And with that, I have castled my king with his queen.
Bishop G5 check.
Normally, F6 would be the best move, but of course, bishop E7 is forced.
Please just take my bishop and end this quickly, this is like a torture to me.
H4.
Oh he wants to play.
F6.
Bishop F4.
I want to go bishop B4, but it's very likely that he's going to play C3 after that, which wins my bishop, since I'll have to move a pawn.
Therefore, bishop F8 is kinda forced.
G4.
Very aggressive.
A6.
G5.
Again, very, aggressive.
B5.
Queen D5.
Queen E7 is kinda forced.
H5.
Man! This dude has been moving his pawns and his queen for like 80% of the game.
H6.
G takes H6.
I want to play G5, but there's a chance that he knows about the French move, which would be really bad.
Therefore, G takes is kinda forced.
C4.
Another pawn move.
I'll take it.
Queen takes.
Man! This guy is like, if I don't move my pawns, I'll move my queen.
But anyway, queen E8 is kinda forced.
I feel like I'm literally torturing myself for taking this mission.
Knight A3.
Yes!
Finally, he moved another piece.
Knight E7 then.
Bishop H3.
Bishop G7.
I don't have many choices anyway.
Rook G1.
Rook G8.
Everything is going as planned.
Knight B5.
Okay that's not in the plan.
That blunders a horsey.
But of course, I need to move my horsey.
He's obviously threatening bishop takes C7 checkmate.
And apparently, knight D5 is the only solution to this.
But you know, after knight D5, E takes D5, there are even more threats to the video, which is already really bad.
So I guess, let's take a big risk.
Knight F5.
And that took me a whole 40 seconds.
Backseat me all you want, I believe this is a worthy risk.
If my plan works, the video is going to be much longer.
If it doesn't, well, let's say it ends sooner than it should have.
Ha ha! My experience from playing at 100 ratings paid off.
A takes B5.
Queen takes.
Now it's time for me to strike back.
Or maybe, even claim a victory on time.
Queen E4.
I mean I don't think I can win any pieces over here.
But at least I think I can make him scared a little bit and then burn down his time.
What the f-
[outro music]