Chess, but you can only capture with pawns.
And wow!
That's a lot of money.
But anyway, let's find an opponent.
That was fast.
We get a 150 from the US.
Since all of the pieces are pretty much useless, let's play really.
I mean really.
Aggressively.
E4.
E6.
Not very aggressive.
But that's actually perfect for my mission.
D4.
D6.
F4.
Let's make a huge...
Pawnstorm.
Bishop E7.
C4.
Bishop D7.
Man!
This guy has to be the nicest opponent I have ever got.
But anyway, that doesn't stop me from playing very aggressively.
B4.
G5.
Aha!
Very aggressive.
H4.
B5.
Again, very aggressive.
But anyway, that blunders a pawn.
Oh, wait.
On second thought, maybe taking on the other side was better.
C5.
I'll take it this time then.
And I can already see some people getting mad in the comments section for declining
the French move.
F5.
Okay okay.
I'll take it this time.
Bishop takes.
Okay now bishop H4 looks kinda scary.
Therefore, queen H5 check.
I mean my pieces can't take.
But they can still check.
White.
King E7.
Very aggressive.
Bishop C4.
Bishop takes D4.
F5.
Please take.
Yes!
Queen F7.
Check.
Mate!
Mission accomplished.
[Music]