100 rated chess. But if a piece, or pawn, is attacked, it gets immobilized.
This is hard. But anyway, let's find an opponent.
We get a 2 51 from Australia. E4.
E5. So far so good.
Knight f3. F6.
That blunders a pawn, oh wait wait wait. If I take his pawn, he takes my knight.
Queen h5 check. G6 will attack and immobilize my queen, which
prevents me from going queen e5 forking his king and rook.
And even worse, he can win my queen on his next move.
So I guess, d4. c5.
That blunders a pawn. But sadly, since my d-pawn is being attacked
by his pawns, it cannot move. So I guess, c3.
He takes d4. I want to take that pawn back, but again,
my c-pawn is being attacked, so it cannot move.
This mission is getting very wrong very quickly.
Therefore, let's just gambit some more pawns, I mean who cares about the pawns anyway.
Bishop to c4. Knight c6.
Ah, just as I said no one cares about the pawns, he shows me that he not only cares
about his pawns, but also cares about my pawns.
He's such a pawn lover. But anyway, I still don't care.
Bishop f4. I'm trying to bait him into playing g5, which
should even give me a chance to checkmate him.
g5. Yes.
That blunders a lot. Knight takes g5.
Please take my knight and loose. And since he cares so much about the pawns,
I believe he will take my knight to avenge his dead g-pawn.
And he did. Wow.
I really can't believe that I have just finished such an impossible mission.
Queen h5 check. And I can pre-move.
Queen f7. Checkmate.
Mission accomplished.
[Music]