100 rated chess, but you must tell your opponent when he blunders and let him keep that peace.
If he blunders twice, the video ends. Well, I guess we can say, not pawn.
This is going to be short. We get a 435 from Myanmar. e4, e5, still theory. Knight f3,
d5, very aggressive. I'll take this pawn. Knight h6, d4, bishop d6. I'll take this knight.
g takes, queen h5, castle. It's funny how he's been attacking my knight for like 10 moves,
and still hasn't taken it yet. I'll take this pawn. c5. I'll take this pawn too. It's amazing
how he's down 3 pawns already, but no pieces have been blundered yet. Queen a5 check. Very aggressive.
c3. c takes d4. Bishop d3. Man, such a peaceful game for a video. I guess this is partly because
my opponent is pretty high rated this time. Bishop takes e5. Ha! Most of my opponents blunders that
piece is everywhere in my games, but then there comes this guy, who just straight up blunders his
king, as his first blunder. That blunders a king. f4. I'll make him sacrifice his bishop to save
his king. Oh wait. I should have made him sacrifice his queen instead. Oh well, who cares anyway.
Ah ha! So he did sacrifice his bishop, but failed to save his king.
And for those of you guys watching, feel free to pause the video to find the checkmate pattern
for white, while I don't give you any seconds to do so, since I have to end the video.
[Music]