100 rated chess, but you can only land your pieces and pawns on a different color square
from where your opponent landed theirs.
Alright then.
We get a 2 1 3 from India.
e4.
That pawn landed on a light square.
Therefore, e5.
Queen f3.
Light square again, knight f6.
I have to be really careful, because if he takes something, I won't be able to take back.
For example, if he takes my knight here, that is a dark square move, which means I cannot
take back, since I'll have to make a light square move.
But of course, there's no way he's going to make such an absurd move like that.
Right?
Bishop c4.
Another light square move.
Bishop c5. Oh wait, don't tell me you're gonna play d4 here.
Phew!
Thank god.
I was worrying that he was going to play d4, which blunders a pawn, but since it's a dark
square move, I won't be able to take it or move my bishop away, so instead of me winning
a pawn, it's him winning my bishop.
But anyway.
Knight c6.
I wanted to move my bishop away, but that's against the rules, so I decided to put more
pressure on d4 instead.
G4.
Very aggressive.
Knight d4.
Queen f5.
That blunders a queen.
But I can't take it due to the rules.
I also can't fork his king and rook, also due to the rules.
Alright.
It's fine.
D6.
If he blunders it once, he will blunder it again.
And it happened sooner than I expected.
But once again, I can't either take the queen, or take the fork, due to the rules.
Even worse, instead of me forcing his queen to move, now it's him forcing my queen to
move, or else I lose.
Are you serious?
And he resigned.
I solemnly swear that this guy is not a paid actor.
Or at least, I didn't pay him.
But anyway.
Mission, accomplished.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[Music]