Chess, but you only have
$690 and you pay your soldiers for every moves
Blah blah blah
Castling counts as moving. Oh, wait, wait, wait. That's a different comment. Oh
I see. He didn't mention about castling. So let's make it
$0
Let's go. We get a 215 from India
e4
e5
still theory
Since I have a very limited budget. Let's try to play really aggressively and get some chances at winning quickly
d4
F6 that blunders a pawn
F takes e5
Aha, now it gets really tricky in this position. I have Queen h5 check g6
Queen takes e5 check Queen blocks Queen takes h8 winning a rook
But then he can go Queen g7 which forces Queen takes g7 trading the Queens which is for Queens move in a row
which costs me
$360 more than half of my entire budget and also
Losing the Queen will make it harder for me to checkmate my opponent
Well, but on the other hand if I don't do that, it's actually even harder to find a good plan now
therefore
YOLO Queen h5
check
King e7 that's a lot of testosterone right there
Normally, I'll go Queen takes e5 check King f7 is forced Bishop c4 check d5
Bishop takes d5 check Queen takes d5 e takes d5
But that line requires me to move my Queen first which costs
$90 and even though it wins my opponent's Queen it opens up too much space for his King and other pieces to move
Which should make it harder for me to win quickly
Therefore Bishop c4 I'm threatening Queen takes e5 checkmate in one and you know
There's a chance that he cannot see it, right?
Wow, he actually saw it
Before the video continues in this position. There is a brilliant move according to stockfish
So feel free to pause the video to try and find that move while I give you a couple of seconds
*PAUSE*
Okay for those of you who were able to find it
Congratulations, and for those of you who just wants to enjoy the show
It's Bishop to f4 the idea is if he takes there is Queen d5 check King e7 is forced
Queen e5 checkmate if he just ignores it and play things like a6
There is a forced checkmate in 8 or even if he finds the best move of Queen f6
We can move our Bishop once again to g5 and he'll either have to sacrifice his Queen or go Queen g6 and blunder his
King to Queen all the way back to d1 check King c6 Queen d5 check King b6 and Queen b5 checkmate
But anyway, of course, I didn't see the brilliant move
Queen f7 I was planning that he might decide to go Queen e7 to offer a Queen trade which blunders Queen
d5 checkmate in one
but instead he went for
Knight h6
That also blunders checkmate in two anyway
Queen d5 check and I can pre move Queen takes e5
Checkmate
Fun fact I actually always analyze my games with Stockfish after it is done and this time I got to see
this
0.0% accuracy from my opponent
Man, that was the funniest thing I've ever seen in my entire life
Except for that day when my best friend was kicked in the balls by his girlfriend
but anyway
mission accomplished
[Music]