100 rated chess, but you are religious, you need to promote 3 or more pawns into bishops,
you cannot let any bishops die, and every piece, not pawn, has to visit your bishops before they
die. The last part just doesn't make any sense, so I'll say that we'll just gonna delete away
that entire section. And I'm not a coward. We get a 1 34 from Argentina. Ha, I'm very sorry
about your defeat against Saudi Arabia. E4. E5. Still theory. D4. Since the challenge doesn't
allow me to trade down my bishops, the best plan is obviously to quickly open up the board,
and then give my bishops a lot of activity without having to move them around for too many times.
D5. Bayer Gambit. I'll take this pawn, a resignation means the challenge is failed,
but since I've only taken a pawn, there is absolutely no reason to resign right now. Right?
No doubt. That blunders a woman, but of course, I don't dare to take it. Again, I'm not a coward,
this is just the most logical way to continue this video. Bishop E4. Blocking with a knight
is just provoking him to take, which is not good because I cannot recapture. Therefore, C3.
Bishop E7. That still blunders the queen, but I'll take the pawn instead.
Queen H4. That blunders the queen for the third time, but bishop D3 instead. It's fine,
as long as he doesn't take this pawn and force me to take his queen,
there is absolutely nothing that can go wrong. Are you serious? King takes F2 is forced.
Alright, I mean since he is the one forcing me to take his queen,
there's no reason to resign the game right now. Right?
Of course. I cannot take that bishop due to the rules, so king G1. I'm trapping my own rook to
somewhat make him feel better after losing his woman. And in no world do you play bishop F2 right
now. I'm worrying too much. C4. Alright, now we know that he's not the type of player who
just randomly resigned from the game, I'm down to say that this challenge is definitely a success.
What the f-
[Music]