100 rated chess. But I have to move my king, every time my opponent moves his queen.
Also, I cannot take his queen, because that will make it too easy.
I actually got this idea from someone else, who commented on one of my videos.
But sadly, I couldn't take a screenshot at that time. So now that comment is nowhere to be found.
Therefore, if you are the one who suggested this idea, please leave a comment below, with a link to your comment, or to the video that you commented in.
I'll go check it out, and then pin your comment to return the favor.
And with that out of the way, let's find an opponent.
We get a 100 rated from India.
Ah ha! This is a lot of pressure on me.
This mission actually resembles my name of simp.
So if I fail to complete it, it will be the biggest humiliation towards my channel.
And yet, after such a long time, I finally get to see, an Indian opponent.
And in case you don't know, I have never defeated an Indian before, and even worse, those videos ended,
very, quickly.
Therefore, let's put some real focus into this game.
E4.
Well, at least he cannot move his queen from move 1.
Right?
D5.
Ah ha! Very tricky.
Right at move number 1, we can already see the danger.
If I take his pawn, queen takes d5 will force me to go king e2, and then queen to e4, is actually, a checkmate.
Therefore, no no no no no.
Knight f3.
The Tennyson Gambit.
I think that this opening sucks, but who cares, since I'll most likely be going to push my king forward this game anyway.
D takes e4.
Knight g5.
Nothing too crazy so far.
And he went afk.
Mission, accomplished.
[Music]