100 rated chess, but on every second move, you must move the same piece, or pawn, you
moved on the previous move.
Ok then.
We get a 1 8 e 9 from Canada.
Let's be real, this is 100% not doable.
But of course, I'll still try my best.
And to be honest, I only hope that I won't be checkmated too early.
e 4.
e oh wait wait wait.
If I play e 5, I won't be able to move my e pawn again next turn, because his pawn is
already blocking the way.
And if you really think about it, this first move is actually harder than it looks.
Let's see.
e 6 also doesn't work, because if he just pushes e 5, my e pawn is once again.
Trapped.
Pushing the d pawn is just provoking bishop b 5 check, which also prevents me from moving
it again.
Developing a knight also doesn't work, because since I have to move my knight again, it's
most likely going to jump around for a while.
And if I push another pawn, for example, c 6, queen h 5, c 5 is forced, bishop c 4, g
6, queen f 3, g 5 is forced, and I get checkmated by a bishop.
So I guess.
g 6.
I mean this is the only way to prevent queen h 5, or at least just delay it for one move.
Knight f 3.
Ah ha.
He's obviously trying to prevent me from pushing g 5.
But guess what?
g 5 is forced.
Ha ha, you didn't stop anything, noob.
Well of course that's a free pawn.
This mission is getting out of control really quickly.
But anyway.
That knight is actually really annoying.
Therefore, e 6.
Well, technically, if he just plays knight back to f 3, e 5 is forced, and then I'll
lose another pawn.
What is wrong with this mission by the way?
Queen f 3.
That blunders a horsey.
But e 5 is forced.
But that's blundering a king.
Are you serious?
Well, at least I tried.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(upbeat music)
(audience cheering)