So a guy gave me a challenge that is actually not even his 100 rated chess, but it's a diplomatic
mission. You must negotiate and establish peace by offering a draw to your opponent before making
any captures or checks. I've never heard that chat GPT can also make grammar mistakes,
but who cares anyway. We get a 100 rated Filipino. And since chat GPT logo is green and white,
I decided to change my board color to match with the AI. D4. The challenge only includes my
captures, so my best choice is obviously to let him capture. He takes. Bishop c5. F4. D6. I'll use
the Eric Rosen special, and if the plan goes well, my first capture will be his queen. He takes d6.
Knight e7. Oh no my horsey. And for some unknown reasons he decided to take the other way instead.
But anyway. That blunders a woman. Brilliant move by the way. King takes f2 is forced. Alright.
Here comes the problem. I can take his queen for free, but before I do that, I have to offer a
draw, which very much may get him to agree as this capture is very easy to spot. I don't buy it.
Draw offer. Yes. I'll sit here and wait for his response before taking that woman.
Ah ha. Bad choice baby. Okay now please resign. Didn't happen. And the situation got really bad
again as now I only have one good move is to take his new woman, which requires a draw offer beforehand.
And he declined it again. I have no idea what he was thinking when he declined it,
but I'm not complaining. G4. I'm not taking anything else this game. Bishop d7. We'll head
straight to a quick checkmate. G5. Very aggressive. Bishop c6. F5. Rook d8. G6. Queen d4. King e1.
Queen h4. A beautiful checkmate with all of my pieces are very far away from his king.
Mission accomplished.