Today is the United States National Short Girl Day.
Therefore, for today's challenge, if a queen moves further than one square,
the video ends. And I'm not gonna explain the reason why.
And of course, I cannot capture my opponent's queen,
or let my queen die, because it's the girl's day.
Let's go. We get a 230 from the US.
E4. Aha! Right as our first move, there are queen f3, queen g4,
and queen h5, ending the video. Knight f6 can prevent 2 of the 3 threats,
but after e5, things get really bad for me.
Therefore, d5. With this move, I can at least stop queen g4, give my
opponent a target, and let's be real, who develops their
queen first anyway. Right?
Knight f3. Yes! Bishop g4. Since he blocked away his
queen's movement with his knight, pinning the knight down will help keep
this blocking stuff lasting a bit longer.
H3. Very aggressive. Bishop h5. Knight g1.
That blunders a woman, but I cannot take it, due to the rules.
Knight f6. Well, at least he still cannot get his queen out right now.
F3. Perfect. I'll take this pawn. Bishop c4. I'll take another pawn.
G takes. Man, it feels like this guy really wants to lock down his queen to
help my video. But anyway, now d4 allowing queen d3 is
the threat. Therefore, e5. Well,
unless he plays c3 and unleash a bunch of other threats.
Ha! He blocked his c-pawn instead. This video is going way much better than I
expected. Bishop c5. Let's try to checkmate him
fast, before anything weird happens. Knight e2. Wow!
His queen is stuck now. Man, at this point, people are so gonna say that this guy is
a paid actor. Bishop takes f3.
Rook f1. Okay, there has to be some sort of sketchy checkmate right now.
Knight e4. Fun fact, there wasn't any checkmate,
and that move was a blunder. My bad.
d3. That blunders a king. And f*** the rules, queen h4 check. And even
though I really want to show you guys the entire checkmate,
I have to end the video here.
[Music]