100 rated chess, but once you develop a piece, not pawn, you must use that piece until it
gets captured.
Very funny.
We get a 291 from the US.
I'm pretty sure there is no way to complete this mission, but still, let's try our best.
E4.
Let's be hyper aggressive with the pawns.
Knight C6.
Aha!
Perfect.
Bishop B5.
So I believe the best way to do this is to trade down the pieces as fast as possible,
so that we can reach the best endgame, of only kings and pawns.
Knight F6.
Bishop takes C6.
B takes.
Yes, now I can move the other pieces.
But of course, there is no need to move them right now.
E5.
Knight E4.
Very aggressive.
D3.
Knight C5.
B4.
That's a testosterone move right there.
Knight A4.
C4.
D6.
That blunders a horsey.
Should I even take it, though?
Because if I take his knight, I will have to move my queen, or pawns, until she is captured.
YOLO.
Queen takes A4.
I mean if I didn't take that knight, people would say that I'm a coward in the comment
section.
D takes E5.
Queen takes C6 check.
Please block with your queen, and I promise that I will just trade queens with you, instead
of going for the rook.
Bishop blocks.
Queen E4.
Rook B8.
C5.
A5.
I'll take it.
Rook B5.
I'll take this too.
F6.
Queen C3.
C6.
A4.
I'm literally making random moves right now.
Rook takes A5.
D4.
E5.
Opening up the E-file is definitely not the smartest choice here.
D5.
C takes D5.
C6.
Bishop C8.
That blunders a rook.
C7.
D4.
That blunders a queen.
C takes D8 equals queen.
Check.
King takes.
Queen takes A5, check.
King D7.
Wow.
I can't believe this actually happened.
Now the game is very easy.
All I have to do, is to promote my A-pawn, trade it with his rook, and use my queen to
clean things up, or I can just make a draw by repetition with my queen.
Alright then, here we go.
Queen D5.
King E7.
A5.
G5.
A6.
Bishop G7.
A7.
Rook D8.
Oh wait wait wait.
That was very sneaky right there.
Queen C5.
Check.
There is no point to trade down my queen when I can have two queens at once.
King E6.
A8 equals queen.
The rules only mentioned about the pieces that I developed, and didn't say anything
about the new pieces I can get from the pawns.
Therefore, I believe that it's totally fair that I can also move my new queen around,
along with my old queen.
Bishop B7.
Queen takes D8.
Once again, this is definitely not cheating.
And he resigned.
Mission, accomplished.
[Music]