Chess, but your queen acts like a second king
Well, that doesn't sound very impossible. Does it?
Let's see
100 rated chess, but you cannot capture your opponent's or or
horse yes or eyes
Okay, dude, let's just say horses
100 rated chess, but you cannot capture your opponent's horses nor you can let our horses get captured
This also doesn't sound impossible
Therefore
100 rated chess, but I don't harm the horses and my queen sucks
Yeah, that's much better let's find an opponent
*music*
We get a 103 from the US
with premium membership
Since the horses are pretty much useless. I believe I should try to stay
as solid as possible
g3
e5 bishop g2
Knight c6 b3
Knight b4. I don't know what that knight is trying to do. But anyway bishop b2
Knight d5
That blunders a horsey
But of course taking it is against the rules
There's also a free pawn on here, but somehow I have a bad feeling about taking it
so I guess
d3
f5 okay, I'll take the pawn
Knight c3
That blunders this horsey again and what the f*ck dude
Now that knight is threatening my queen and my knight
but I cannot take it and
Since my queen is a second king. This is basically a check so I have to move it
But if I move it now knight takes b1 destroys the mission
Is this some kind of torturing
Okay, fine queen d2 please don't take my knight
Yes
that move blunders the very knight again and
Again taking it is not an option
also, it's attacking my queen which equals to a check and
Moving it up is just too risky. So I guess queen back to d1
I mean, I'm fine with a repetition and I also know that so many people are going to backseat me about that move
But this game doesn't look like it's going well for me. So I need to take the risk, okay?
Bishop before check this is so frustrating
c3
Man, he's so gonna go knight c3 again
Bishop takes oh
I can take that
Knight takes and
Here we are once again
Queen c2
Since he didn't take my knight last time. There's no way he's taking it this time, right?
Why is he thinking for so long
Knight back to d5 blundering that very night for the fourth time
But anyway, I think the danger is over
Knight d2
It's time to strike back
Queen e7 that blunders that horsey for the fifth time and
You know, let's just block the bishops view so I won't have to see that again
B5 very aggressive our castle
Before again, very aggressive night d4
Queen takes c2 that blunders a queen
Mission accomplished
[Jazz music]