If a queen lands on the A file, you do a Q N A. For example, queen A6 means doing a Q N A with 6
questions. Plot twist, I cannot take my opponent's queen, because it will make the mission too easy.
Let's go. We get A 100 rated from the US. Well, it's actually pretty unlucky that we got the
black pieces, because I was planning to develop my pieces and go queen A1 right away as the white
pieces. But sadly, things doesn't work like that on the other side of the board.
E4. The most obvious threat now is C4 and queen A4. Therefore, A5. D4. A4. Ha,
now I don't have to worry about queen A4 anymore. A3. Oh, would you look at that. I was about to
mention that there is also queen F3 and queen A3 threat, but now, that's not a problem anymore.
E5. Since I'm so much behind in developing, gambiting a pawn should be fine. H4. I'll take
this pawn. Queen takes. Knight C6. Rook H3. That blunders a queen, but of course, I cannot take it,
due to the rules. B6. Queen D5. Very aggressive. Knight F6. And in no world do you play queen A5
here. Rook F3. That blunders this woman again, but again, I still cannot take it. Bishop B7.
Knight C3. You know what? I'll just leave a number right here, showing how many times that he
blunders his woman in this game. Bishop C5. Bishop E3. I'll take it. F takes. Castle. Bishop C4.
Very aggressive. Knight A5. I'm starting to feel uncomfortable for my F pawn,
so let's try to trade down some pieces. What the hell was that? Is this guy challenging me to take
his queen? King H8 is forced. Now don't tell me that he's gonna play queen G8 check, which forces
me to take, which makes me a fool, for ending my own video. Rook G3. Wow! This guy is literally
trying to checkmate me, while ignoring that his queen is still being attacked. G6. Somehow rook
G8 looks like a blunder to me, but I don't really know why. H5. D5. Oh wait! I have a knight here.
My bad. Rook takes G6. Ha! Jokes on you, I can take these guys.
My god, this guy is so insistent in checkmating me. Knight H5. Well, at least there's no way for
him to end my video now. What the f-
[Music]