100 rated chess, but you have to extend the game to over 100 turns.
Playing 5 minute splits on a 100 rated account.
And wow, that's a lot of money.
I actually haven't received any donations in the past few weeks,
which makes me really sad, thinking that people already got bored of my videos.
So dude, that $100 means more, than just money to me.
But anyway, back to the video.
I'll be honest, I have never played a game, that lasts over 100 moves.
So this time, I also don't think I can do it.
The result is going to be, either my opponent resigns, or his time runs out.
But of course, it's not like I'm scared of it or something.
Let's find an opponent.
We get a 1-0-3 from the US.
With premium membership.
And a cat profile picture.
E4.
E5.
Queen H5.
Don't panic guys, I have a plan.
Knight F6.
That blunders a pawn.
But no, I won't take that pawn.
So the thing that makes this mission so hard, is that my opponent can just resign,
at any time during the game.
Therefore, take this.
Queen takes F7.
Check.
King takes.
Now that he has 8 points of material advantage,
he should have no reason to resign from the game.
Bishop C4 check.
D5.
Very aggressive.
I'll take it.
I know it brings his advantage from +8 down to +7.
There's still no way that he's going to resign.
Right?
E4.
Again, very, aggressive.
Knight C3.
Bishop F5.
Knight E2.
C5.
That blunders a lot.
En passant.
Check.
Bishop block.
Wow!
That's a lot of testosterone right there.
Alright.
As you wish.
Bishop takes E6.
King takes.
C takes B7.
Ok.
Now I can only hope that my opponent won't get panic and resign from the game.
Just calm down,
move your knight,
and everything is fine.
Yes.
Now.
Here comes the big question.
Do I take his rook?
I mean after I take his rook,
he will no long have an advantage,
which may cause him to be sad,
and then quit the game.
Aha!
I know.
I'll take it,
but I'll make a horsey instead.
Because if you look at the material difference,
I'm only having a +2 advantage.
But if I had made a queen,
that +2 would have been a +8,
which may cause him to resign.
Queen takes A8.
Yes.
Now he's up +1 again.
Of course it's very risky playing at this small difference,
so I guess I'll try to sacrifice some more later on.
Castle.
Knight G4.
D4.
I'm threatening D5,
but let's see if he learned the French move.
Amazing!
C takes D3.
Bishop D6.
Knight G3.
Knight takes H2.
Dude!
That blunders a horsey!
But should I even take it though?
Because if I take his knight,
I will officially be up in material,
which may cause him to rage quit.
Okay.
I have to take it.
If I don't take it,
that horsey will jump around in my territory,
without any mercy.
Knight D4.
I'll go back.
Knight C2.
Very aggressive.
Rook B1.
Bishop B4.
Okay.
It's time to give him back some materials.
Knight D5.
Queen takes.
Bishop E3.
Let's give him some more.
Queen takes A2.
Rook Fc1.
Knight takes E3.
F takes E3.
H5.
Very aggressive.
Knight E4.
H4.
Again, very aggressive.
Rook A1.
Queen takes B2.
That blunders a bishop!
Rook Cb1.
Queen E2.
Rook takes B4.
G5.
Man!
This guy is really aggressive.
But anyway,
that blunders a pawn!
King F6.
Ah ha!
It looks like he wants to attack my knight.
I think now I have...
Rook K6 check.
King takes B5.
Rook B5 check.
King G4 is forced,
and then rook G6.
Checkmate!
But sadly,
that is only about 30 moves into the game,
which is still very far away from a hundred.
Therefore,
let's just go back.
King F5.
Let's make a trap.
G3.
I know that it's a bad move,
but it looks cool.
Ha ha!
He fell for it.
Now I have knight takes G3,
which comes with a royal fork.
But once again,
should I even do it though?
I mean right now,
he's having A+1 lead.
But if I do that,
it will become A+9 lead for me.
Oh wait.
What am I thinking?
If I don't do the royal fork,
the people in the comment section
are going to backseat me so much
about blundering that G pawn,
without getting anything in return.
Also,
his time is very low already,
so if he has fewer materials on the board,
he is less likely going to waste his time.
Knight takes G3 check.
King F6.
Knight takes E2.
Rook G8 check.
Ah ha!
Perfect time to give back some materials.
Rook G4.
Why is he thinking for so long?
Finally!
King F2.
Alright,
let's speed up the video.
Rook takes E3.
That blunders a rook.
Okay.
Now is the video's fate.
If he resigns,
the mission is failed.
If he doesn't,
the mission is a success.
Thank you.
Rook F7.
Here's my plan.
I'll use my rook to cut his king off,
and then I'll walk my king from top to bottom,
push my pawn,
and then bottom to top,
and then top to bottom,
push my pawn,
and so on.
And since he only has a king,
there is no way his time is running out.
Let's go.
Oh wait wait wait.
Ha ha!
Can't catch me babe.
*knock knock*
What the f-
*outro music*