Chess, but you play against bot.
Great idea, but of course, I have to add something to make it a challenge.
Let's say, I have to win, without losing any material.
Let's go.
I chose Harry Mack as my opponent, and for anyone who don't know, Harry Mack is an artist,
and is a participant of PogChamp 4.
E4.
Since I can't afford to let any pieces die, pushing center pawns seems a bit too risky.
Therefore, knight C6.
Knight F3.
B6.
Bishop C4.
Bishop B7.
Nothing wrong so far.
Knight G5.
Oh, here it comes.
E6.
Queen H5.
Knight E5.
Oh, wait.
I blundered.
Now he has knight takes E6, D takes E6, queen takes E5, winning a pawn, and end the video.
My bad.
Haha, of course a 600 rated engine cannot see it.
G6.
G4.
That blunders a queen.
But if I take his queen, it will turn out that I have a double attack on his knight
and bishop, which may cause him to make a desperado.
So I guess, I'll take the bishop.
A3.
That blunders the queen again.
Chess.com, I believe you guys should try to fix this engine, since I don't think Mack
is going to abandon his woman, twice.
But again, should I even take it though, since there is also G takes H5, and even though
that blunders the horsey, I mean he blundered his queen twice, so the horsey is nothing
much.
Yeah, I think that is still too risky.
Knight F6.
Alright, now there are 2 pieces attacking his queen, of course he'll move it.
Right?
What the f-
(Outro music)