100 rated chess, but the password is egghead.
You must move your queen to land on those files in correct order to unlock the ability to checkmate.
I actually preferred egghead more than egghead.
But let's go anyway.
We get a 1 0 8 from Brazil.
And by the way, very bad selfie skills.
E4.
First letter is an E, I have to open up the way.
Bishop C4.
Queen E7 makes the first step, but if I do that, my queen will be blocking my bishop's way.
I'll move my bishop first.
Queen H5.
Alright, now the challenge officially begins.
Queen E7.
It's pretty concerning that his queen is preventing my queen from going to the G file for the next letter,
so if he can move his queen somewhere else, that will be very convenient, but not that one.
That blunders a woman, but bishop recaptures ends the video, not to mention that there is no F in the egghead word.
This may be the shortest video on this channel.
Ha! Nevermind, not only does he blunder his woman again, but he also helps my woman gets the next correct letter.
What a nice guy.
That gets me another G.
Rook G1 and I'll also get my H.
That is even better.
Queen takes H1.
My god this guy is the biggest unpaid actor I've ever met.
King E2.
That allows another check, which comes with another letter.
And I've just realized that it may be impossible for me to get an A this game.
King D1.
It's alright. I have a plan.
He takes D4.
The plan is very simple.
He makes a random move, I push E3, he wouldn't want to take with pawn because he'll get 2 isolated doubled pawns,
so bishop takes, then I can go queen A5, and then my queen on A5 will be pinning his C pawn,
which disallows him from pushing C3, and then I can safely go queen D4 finishing the challenge.
Oopsie! My internet is broken, I got disconnected, the video ends here.
Have a great day.
[outro music]