100 rated chess, but you move to dark squares on odd moves, or move to light squares on even moves.
To be honest I don't think this is a very challenging challenge, but the lack of ideas
is giving me no other choices. First move has to be a dark square move. D4. E5. I really want to
take that pawn, but sadly, it's time for a light square move. E4. Ha, now it's a normal danish
gambit. Knight F6. I'll take this pawn. Knight takes E4. Bishop C4. I'm expecting, knight C6,
queen D5, F5, and I win his king. Of course it doesn't happen. Very aggressive. C3. Bishop C5.
That blunders a pawn to bishop F7. King F7. Queen D5. King back to E8 and queen takes E4,
but sadly, even though I can go bishop takes F7 now, my next move has to be a dark square move,
which means I cannot go queen D5. Therefore, why not queen D5 immediately? I mean bishop F2 check
will force me to end my own video, but he should be able to see, that after king F1, both of his
pieces and his king will be under attack and there is no way to save all of them. Right?
Ha! You see? Always have faith in the Indians. That blunders a horsey, but again, it's time for
a dark square move, so bishop E3 is kinda forced. It's fine, he takes my bishop, I take his knight,
everyone is happy, and in no world do you play knight takes F2 now.
Perfect. Queen takes E4. Bishop C5. It's pretty funny that he could have played bishop all the
way to C1 to be an imposter in my territory. But anyway, a dark move now. H4. I mean what else can
I play anyway? D6. Not very aggressive. Bishop D3. And please have no idea of what I'm trying to do
here. Bishop E6. That blunders a ko wait wait wait. I almost forgot, that it is an odd-numbered move,
which means I cannot move my woman to a light square. So I guess, B4. Well, at least I can win
a bishop. Ha! Noob. Queen takes H7. Checkmate. As I've predicted, the main thing is that I'm
gonna win. The mission is quite easy.
*Outro Music*