100 rated chess, but it's take your child to work day.
Every fourth move you let your child make a move.
I don't have a child, so I actually invited my cousin over during the recording of this video.
And he's 9. We get a 123 from the Philippines.
E4. Not only my cousin is 9, he also knows how to play chess, but not that good.
So I actually don't know if that's a good thing or not.
But anyway. First move is my move. E5.
Bishop C4. I don't want to play too aggressively,
because I don't know what will happen when it's my cousin's turn.
Therefore, I'll make a defensive move. Fun fact, I actually taught this cousin how to play chess,
so I hope that he and I will make a great team.
Knight C3. This is my last move before disaster strikes,
so in order to prevent a crazy king E7, I'll block away my king.
Ha! Now I don't have to worry about anything. Anymore.
Except for that. My cousin's move, and I mean since I taught
him how to play chess, he should be able to see, that this is a very obvious checkmate in one threat.
*Badly edited*
Comment section time. Don't give up on this challenge,
it seems like a fun one that keeps chess fresh. I actually prefer frozen stuff.
I'm bad at chess, where was the first mate in 6?
0 replies, and I mean everyone at average can see any checkmate patterns shorter than 27 moves,
so if you want to get better, I would suggest you try solving that short and easy checkmate in 6 by
yourself. I would have loved to see you play it out to the end, you weren't that much at a
disadvantage, I would have been excited to see who wins. No.
MMMMM. Great comment.
*Outro*