100 rated chess, but you do not let your opponent enters your half of the board.
And I think we can all agree, that he meant pieces and pawns.
Very aggressive. We get a 139 from Argentina. First of all, I just want to say that I think
this challenge is very difficult. Therefore, let's get serious right from move 1. E4 will provoke him
to play E5, which will open up the way for bishop B4 and queen H4 ending the video, and of course I
cannot prevent both of them, because even if I play A3 instead of E4, E5 will still be very likely
to happen, and then there are still E4 and queen H4 at the same time, which is also unstoppable.
Therefore, D4, D4 will provoke D5 to happen, and that move only allows bishop G4 to end the video,
which is very easy to prevent. There we go. Bishop G4 is the threat, therefore, F3, I mean H3 looks
more natural, but F3 will further prevent knight F6 and knight E4 in the future. Knight C6. Knight
B4 is the threat, so of course, C3. Ha! Believe it or not, I actually prepared all of this before
the game begins. Okay, that move was not in my preparations, therefore, it gets serious now.
DxE4 is kinda forced. Of course I cannot let that pawn end my video, and even though there is queen
H4 is available, I mean who develops their queen first anyway. Right? Of course. 2 threats now,
so I have to choose one. I mean who plays a weird move like knight C4 anyway.
Perfect. B3. Ha! The video is safe. G5. Very aggressive. G4 is obviously the threat,
but sadly, that pawn dies now. H5. Again, very, aggressive. Queen D4. I mean H4 is a threat,
but since I'm attacking his knight, he can't just move a pawn like that. Right?
Bishop E6. That blunders a horsey. Yeah, now I'm really threatening to take another horsey
with a family fork, so in no world do you end my video now. To be honest, I think I deserve that.
[Music]