100 rated chess, but white pieces cannot be taken on white squares, and black pieces cannot be taken
on black squares. Not pawns. This is going to be annoying. We get a 290 from Saudi Arabia.
If my pieces cannot die on the light squares, I'll put the pawns there. E5. D4. Still theory.
No more theory. D takes E5. Knight takes E4. Aha! So the best continuation should be bishop C4,
he makes a random move, and then there is bishop takes F7, king takes F7, queen D5, check king E8,
queen takes E4 and I win a pawn, but sadly, king takes F7 actually kills my bishop on a light
square, which is against the rules. Therefore, bishop D3. D5. Aha! Taking his knight and trading
queens to make him unable to castle should be my best choice, but sadly, D takes E4 also ends the
video, not to mention that I also cannot capture his queen on a dark square. So I guess. On passant.
Knight takes. Knight F3. An absolutely normal development move. That move is definitely not
normal. Knight C3. Knight F5. Taking that knight is just provoking him to end my video. Therefore,
knight D5. I'm attacking his queen and threatening a fork right now, but before the video continues,
I just want to say that YouTube has finally given me the power of the join button.
If you like my videos and want to support me with your real money, that button will do the job,
and you'll also get some very special privileges back. But anyway. Queen D6. He's obviously
threatening to take my knight and also ends the video. Therefore, A4. He should be able to see
that queen takes D5 is blundering bishop B5 check with a discovered attack on the queen. Right?
[Bloopers]
By the way, for those people who are thinking that there is C6 blocking the check and also
defend the queen, jokes on you, queen takes D5 still happens and the C6 pawn is pinned so it
cannot recapture the queen. But anyway. What the f-
[Outro]