if any piece or pawn is attacked from its back, the video ends. Too easy! We get a 300 rated from
Canada. e4, knight f6, e5, knight g4 attacking the pawn from behind will end the video,
but since it's blundering a knight, he's not going to play it. Right? Of course. d3. In no world do
you play knight f2 to end my video here. Please! Thank god! That blunders a horsey. Ha! Now he
cannot end my video, no matter how hard he tries. Bishop c5. Ah ha! Now queen g4 is obviously the
best move, but that will allow bishop d4 attacking my pawn from behind, which ends the video. So I
guess, knight f3. Now there are 2 pieces guarding the d4 square, so in no world do you move your
bishop there. Queen h4. That blunders a queen, but should I even take it though? I have a strong
feeling, that after I take his queen, he will become extremely crazy and go bishop takes f2,
which attacks my knight on h4 from behind. You know what? I don't believe. Knight takes h4.
Alright, now just calm down, and don't take anything crazy.
Well, I kinda saw that was coming, so there's no what the f*** today.
[Music]