If a pawn is stopped, the video is stopped. Playing 3 minute splits on a 100 rated account.
I normally don't take challenges that depend on luck. But you know, I'm pretty much out of ideas.
Therefore, let's go. We get a 1 45 from Ireland. Pushing center pawns is obviously not a great
idea. Therefore, G3. Now knight C6 or knight F6 ends the video, because they stop the movement
of these pawns. But you know, there's nothing I can do about that. A5. Well, I guess that's lucky,
since the video can last a bit longer. Now A4 is the threat, because it can come with A3,
which stops my A pawn, which ends the video. Therefore, B3. H5. Very aggressive. Bishop G2.
I mean I already have a pawn on G3, so no need to worry about H4. And H4 happens anyway. Now H3
ends the video, since it stops my H2 pawn. Therefore, G takes H4 is kinda forced. And in
no world do you play rook H5 here. Thank you. Now knight F3 attacking the rook should be really good.
But of course, that makes me a fool, for ending my own video. Therefore, bishop B2.
A4. Man this guy is really aggressive. B takes A4. Alright, just take it please,
with any rooks you want. Perfect. D3. And in no world do you play rook D4 here.
Rook KB4. Attacking the rook with one of these moves looks really fun. But once again,
I can't just end my own video. Queen C1. Rook HG4. Yeah, I saw that was coming. King F1.
Rook B5. Knight D2. Rook BG5. Very aggressive. Now knight E4 is obviously the best move,
but it will just provoke rook G6, which stops the G pawn, which ends the video. So I guess.
Bishop E4. I mean things may get real bad if he plays F5 here. But what else can I do anyway.
And he found it. Well, I guess we have no other choice. H3. Of course rook H4 ends the video,
but let's just hope that he sees knight F3 forking the rooks, and then plays rook F4 instead.
Aha, perfect. And by the way, that rook didn't stop his F pawn. Knight C4. F takes E4.
Queen takes F4, and in no world do you play E3 here. E5. Knight takes E5. Now just don't see
anything and blunder your king. E takes D3. Wow. I can't believe I've actually won that challenge.
Queen F7. Checkmate. Mission accomplished.
[music]