100 rated chess, but you're running low on fuel, you can only move 4 times, but you gain
1 additional move for every point of material you capture.
Giving me 2 additional moves was way too many to use, and quite frankly, turning 2 to 1
is still very easy.
We get a very angry guy from Iceland.
E4.
E5.
Qh5.
Nc6.
Nothing wrong so far, except the fact that I only have 2 moves until the video ends.
Bc4.
Alright, g6 is the most popular move right now, but that will make this video absolutely
impossible as I cannot capture anything to raise the move limit.
Therefore, Qf6 instead.
Qxf7 will be very convenient.
Sadly he's not a paid actor.
I have to raise the move limit right now, and the only option is, Qxf3.
+3 baby.
Gxf3.
G6.
It's fine, a real man doesn't need a woman in his life.
And my opponent agrees.
That is very convenient.
Now since I have a lot of moves, I think we can already see an easy victory in this game.
F4.
3 more moves.
These challenges get really convenient sometimes.
D3 knight back knight a3 bishop takes pawn takes d5 e d5 knight e5 rook g1 knight f6
f5 that blunders a pawn bishop h6.
He'll have to castle the other way, knight g4.
Attacking the bishop and also preparing the knight for a free f-pawn.
Bishop g7.
Very aggressive.
Rook g8.
Bishop b2.
Strong castle.
If I castle, he'll castle.
Absolutely.
That blunders a pawn.
Rook d2.
Knight h3.
I feel like I'm wasting too many moves on this useless horsey.
Rook g3.
Rook e8.
Only 6 moves left, guess I'll have to find a way to trade down a rook.
Nevermind.
+5 baby.
How about blundering the other rook too.
I solemnly swear, that this guy is not a paid actor.
Rook takes e2.
c4.
Knight e3.
Checkmate incoming.
Or not.
Mission accomplished.
Thanks for watching.