100 rated chess, but you have pawn structure superiority.
Your opponent needs to have 2 sets of triple dissolated pawns.
Before you checkmate.
You know what? It actually doesn't sound so hard.
We get a 181 from Bangladesh.
F4. The pan is very simple.
He goes E5, E takes F4, and then we have a doubled pawn.
D5. C4. Same plan as the other side.
But then he doesn't take.
I can already see, that this guy will make a very annoying opponent.
D4. I need my pawns alive so I can reposition his pawns.
Nevermind.
That blunders a woman.
I don't want to win by resignation because it ruins the purpose of the challenge,
but if he wants to resign, nothing I can do about it.
Knight.
Thank you.
Knight C3.
Ah ha! After all those moves, he has finally capture the pawn.
G3.
Knight D7.
Bishop G2.
Knight GF6.
Here we go.
Bishop C6.
The plan is very simple.
He takes, and we have 1 set of tripled pawns.
For some reason, this guy managed to blunder his queen on move 3,
then he missed my free bishop, but he knows how to queen side castle,
which is a very advanced technique.
E4.
E6.
Ah ha! He doesn't want to take my bishop.
I'll take his bishop then.
Any of these captures are good for the video.
Bishop G5.
Alright. The plan is very simple.
He takes my bishop, he takes my pawn, I take his knight, he takes my bishop.
The challenge is a success.
And since my bishop is pinning his knight, this capture is totally inevitable.
You know what? I'm not playing this game anymore.
This opponent is a very good player.
I'm not playing this game anymore.
This opponent is way over my level.
Continuing this will harm my mental health.
Have a great day.
[Music]