100 rated chess, but you can only capture pieces which worth more or equal points with the piece
you captured before it. I think I've done something similar to this before, but since I don't remember
it, I guess it's fine to take it on again. We get a 144 from his rail. E4. The plan is very simple.
We take all the pawns first, and then all the minor pieces, and then all the rooks, and then
the woman, and it ends right there because taking the king is not an option. And he decided to give
me a pawn capture to start the game. He takes D5. Knight C6. Ah ha. That blunders a horsey, but if I
take that horsey now, I won't be able to take any pawns from that point onward. So I guess, I'm not
gonna do that. It's fine, it's not like he's not gonna blunder anything from now on anyway. G5.
Very aggressive. D3. E6. Ah ha. I can take this pawn. A lot of people may protest against this
move as it loses a horsey, but I don't give a sh*t. Rook B8. A very useful move. I'll take this pawn
too. You know what, maybe this game is gonna become the easiest win in this entire channel.
King takes F7. Queen H5 check. King E7. Bishop takes another pawn. King E6. Okay. Here comes the
question. Do I take this queen? I mean if I take his queen, I will be banned from capturing anything
from that point onward, which will give him the chance to go absolutely crazy and destroy my
entire territory. But the good thing is, he may resign immediately after becoming maidenless.
Well, as always, I'm not a coward. Who knows, maybe he'll decide not to capture my bishop
and blunder queen D5 checkmate in one in the middle of the board. Man, I should have hired
a paid actor for this recording so that he could have done better. But anyway. Queen D5. Checkmate.
Mission accomplished.
[Music]