100 rated chess, but you cut the break wires, rooks, bishops and queen can only stop by bumping
into a piece, or pawn, or the edge of the board. I think I've done something similar to this before,
but since I don't remember when that was or how that turned out, it's totally fine to start
another attempt. e4. e5. The pawns are not affected by the challenge, but of course it is totally
fine to just move the pawns the furthest they can travel. d4. I'll take it. Opening up the board may
not be the greatest idea because those pieces will have too many squares to move, but of course,
I'm not a coward. Qxxe6. I mean if he can just blunder his queen and then immediately resign
after that, it will be very convenient. Qc3. Ah ha, that actually also blunders the queen to bishop
b4 skewering the royal couple, but sadly, according to the rules, my bishop can only go to a3 touching
the wall, and cannot be stopped at b4, so I guess. d5. f3. That blunders the queen again, but again,
I can only take this pawn. fxe4. That once again blunders the same queen, and you know what,
I'm down to say that he's just gonna blunder his woman for the rest of the game. Qh4 check.
Touching the wall. g3. I'll take this pawn. Alright, as I said before, he's gonna blunder
his queen for the rest of this game, so let's see if he is able to find queen e3 blocking the check
and also pin my queen to my king so my queen cannot take his rook in the corner. He couldn't.
I'll take the rook. Bumping into a piece and the edge of the board at the same time.
Bishop f3. Aha, that bishop forks my queen and my knight which threatens bishop c6 bc6 queen c6
forking my king and rook, but sadly, I can bump into this horsey. Man, maybe this challenge is
actually easier than I expected. Resignation. Mission accomplished.
[Music]