100 rated chess, but if you can blunder a pawn, you have to. No love for those soldiers today,
we get a 185 from Thailand. E4. Ah ha, F5 is just gambiting a pawn, which is not really a blunder,
and D5 is just suggesting a pawn trade. Therefore, B5 is kinda forced. I mean blundering a pawn on
the very first move of a chess game doesn't sound very positive, but as long as he doesn't get his
queen out to absolutely destroy all of my pawns, there is absolutely nothing to be worried about.
Knight F3. Ah ha, now I can choose whether to end Edward's life or the G-pawn's life,
and even though that was a tough choice, the guy with no name needs to go. I'm sorry the guy that
doesn't have a name, but I'll try to write something on your gravestone. He's dead. And
I've just realized, that now F5 is forced, which allows queen H5 checkmate in 1.
This game sucks. Oh my god thank you very much. Knight F6. Ha, now queen H5 is not checkmating
anymore, but I mean if he still decides to play it to give me a free queen, that will definitely
be very convenient. Of course it doesn't happen. E5. Castle. Rook G8, I mean it will be very bad
if he doesn't move his knight back, but I'm positive that he will do so. Nevermind. That
forces me to blunder my H-pawn, therefore, knight takes E4. Man, now queen H5 rook G6 knight H7 will
be very dangerous, but since he didn't see the checkmate in 1 last time, there is no way he's
seeing that tactic here. Right? Ha, F takes E4 is kinda forced, because that also blunders the F-pawn.
G3. No pawn to blunder anymore. I'll take this pawn. Knight D5. Ah ha, that threatens to take
my C-pawn, and according to the rules, I have to let that happen. Knight takes E7. King D8. Knight
takes A8. E3 is kinda forced. D3. That blunders a king, queen H1. Checkmate. Man, I can't believe
I actually won that.
[Music]