100 rated chess, but your hands are coated in butter, every third move must be a mouse slip.
Wet and slippery. We get a 189 from the Philippines.
E4. First move is not a slippery move, and I mean what can be wet when we've just started by the way.
D5. I'll take that pawn.
Queen takes. Ah ha. Now things get wet. The most popular next move is knight c3 attacking the
queen, but sadly, oopsie. As a wise man once said, knight on the rim is mouse slipped.
Queen e5 check. Bishop e2. I have no idea how to make a mouse slip if I have to do it when
he gives a check to be honest. Queen back to d5 again. Knight f3. Expecting knight back to e5
which blunders a woman. Didn't happen. I want to play b3 trying to fianchetto my bishop, but sadly,
mouse slipped. E4. Very aggressive. C4. Danger levels, and since his e-pawn has left the e5
square, I do believe he'll move his queen back to that square. I have too much experience against
these 100 rated guys. That blunders a woman. He'll resign soon, I think we can already prepare
ourselves for a mission accomplished. F6. Ah ha. I want to go bishop h5 g6 knight g6 hg6 going for
a quick attack at his king. But sadly, mouse slipped. And that was 100% a mouse slip. I'm
definitely not baiting him to take my knight which blunders a rook to queen h5 queen e5 queen h8.
Trust. F takes e5. He gives me no other choices. G6. Queen takes e5 check. And I've just realized
that the next move has to be a mouse slip, so I actually cannot take his rook. Ha. Nevermind.
Mission accomplished.
[Music]