100 rated chess. But checks are forced. This is going to be short. We get a 165 from Brazil.
In case you are wondering why there are some weird shapes around the Brazilian flag right here,
it's because I'm recording today's video using Microsoft Edge, not Google Chrome like usual,
because there seems to be something wrong with my Google Chrome today.
E3. Pushing E5 is very natural, but if he plays D4 next, it will make Bishop B4 check forced,
and after C3, I will have to sacrifice my Bishop, because that is also a check. Therefore,
Knight F6. I mean D5 obviously allows Bishop B5 check, and there is always a chance that he won't
play it. Queen E2. Very aggressive. Knight C6. Queen D3. Aha, now there is Queen takes D7 check,
and since he's obviously not going to play that, D6. The plan is very simple. Not allowing any
checks, and if there is no possible check, the video cannot end. And it's going to be really
hard if he keeps moving his queen around threatening my video like this. E5. My dark
bishop is already blocked, so there's no reason not to take some center space. Queen F3. Aha,
now there is Queen takes C6 check, and once again, he's definitely not going to do that.
Therefore, Bishop D7. Knight C3. Bishop E7. Once I can castle, we can finally play the game
normally. Queen G3. Wow. Now if I castle, there is Queen takes G7 check, but since it blunders a
queen, he's not going to play that, which means the video ends. So I guess, Knight H5. Well,
at least there is no possible check right now, so he can't end my video, no matter how hard he tries.
Queen back to F3. Queen takes F7 is a check, therefore, Knight back to F6.
Ha! Very aggressive. Knight back to H5. This challenge is really hard,
so I'll take a draw anytime I can. Yes. Knight back to F6. Draw by repetition.
Mission kinda accomplished.
[Music]