100 rated chess, but it's fair, all captures must be part of fair trades. The only fair trade I've
ever had in my life is when I decided to lose my virginity instead of studying math and then get a
B-. But today will be different. We get a 162 from Israel. E4. E5. Gambits are not allowed in this
challenge. Nf3. Bb4. Very aggressive. That gambits a pawn, but a gambit is definitely not a part of
a fair trade. C3. I literally have never seen this opening since I started playing chess,
so let's just hope that I won't get destroyed by his preparation. Ba5. Again, cannot take that pawn,
Bc4. Nf6. Aha, now taking this pawn is a part of a fair trade, but this trade actually blunders
another pawn, so it turns out to be not a fair trade. D3 instead. Ng4. Bg5. F6. I'll go back
this way. G5. Aha, now I really want to go Ng5 brilliant move Fg5 Qg4 Gh4 and I'll have a very
easy to see checkmate in 12, but since that continuation breaks the rules, Bg3. Nc6. Nfd2.
D5. That blunders a pawn in 2 different ways. But again, that's not a fair trade. Bd7. H3.
And I've just realized that I actually cannot take that knight even if he blunders it.
Fair trade, Nxe4. I mean it's fine, as long as he doesn't play a move like Bxe3 check which forces
me to either take the bishop or not take the bishop which all end up as an unequal trade.
The video is fine.
What the f-
[Music]