100 rated chess, but it's father's day, your pieces. And pawns can only capture enemy pieces,
and pawns, 3 squares near your king, like a child trying to impress his father. Alright,
it's father king today. E4. E5, just normal opening move so far. Nevermind. Knight c6.
F3. Alright, since I can only capture the things that are close to father king,
which as you can see, is not very far away, I think it's time to make the most decisive move
in this entire game. King e7. Hashtag, father's fun, matters. Bishop c4. G6. I mean pushing father
forward can also provoke him to keep his queen closer, which means that there will be more
chances for me to win the woman. Queen g5 check, of course pulling father back is obviously not
an option, so I guess, f6. Queen g4, that blunders a bishop. D5. E takes d5, that blunders a woman,
and let's see, 1, 2, 3, bishop takes g4, and then the bishop asked, are you proud of me papa?
Ultra amazing elegant, Carlos. D takes c6. I'll pull Carlos back. D4, that blunders a pawn,
and let's see, 1, 2, 3, I'll take the queen, well technically I don't have to count the squares if
I take the queen because the queen is obviously not one of the king's children, but let's just
say that the wife also wants to impress her husband. C3. That blunders this bishop, and 1,
2, dead. This challenge is going way smoother than what I imagined, but the hard part is actually
when I have to push father even further ahead. Nevermind. Happy father's day.