100 rated chess, but I'll pay you $5 for every piece or pawn of either side that ends the game
on a dark square. -5 for each that ends on a light square. That sounds pretty racist. Free money for
me. We get a 177 from the US, E4 putting a pawn on a light square sounds absolutely stupid. D4.
I mean D5 will be pretty problematic because it puts his pawn on a light square, but who knows,
maybe he'll play D6 instead and help me get another 10 bucks instead.
Well, thank you. Bishop F4. London system baby. C5. Very aggressive. Eliminating materials on
dark squares doesn't sound like a very good idea. E3. But then he takes me. Oh well, I guess I have
no other choices. I mean it's fine if now he puts another piece on the dark square. Amazing. Bishop
C4. Since I need a lot of things on dark squares, my light square bishop is definitely the most
valuable piece in this game, because if I have a strong light square bishop, my opponent won't
dare to put his materials on the light squares. F#@k. Knight F3. Don't worry, I'll maneuver this
horsey back to a dark square later. B5. I don't want to take that pawn because it may still advance
to B4. Bishop D5. This will force him to move his rook to B8. Or not. I'll give a check.
You know what? Somehow I actually saw that was coming. H4. Queen E8. So instead of moving his
rook, he gives me a fork instead. I'll pull it back. Because I feel like if I kept my bishop there,
he'd play bishop D7 next forcing a trade. Bishop E7. Ha, that blunders a bishop. Knight E6. I'll
pull this back. A6. Not gonna lie, these pawns are very annoying. D5. Moving a pawn from a dark
square to a light square doesn't sound like a very good idea, but this will help me attack his
queen which will move his queen to a dark square and it also attacks his knight which also forces
his knight to move to a dark square. Or not. C3. Knight F5. Bishop C6. Dude. Now everything is
hanging. And he said that it is okay to hang one more thing. I'll take it. I mean as long as my
light bishop is still alive, he will definitely see its threats at some point. Nevermind. Oh well,
I cannot let that queen live. Rook G8. That move has no f***ing usage other than reducing $10 from
my payment. Knight D2. Knight C7. A3. Knight D5. Queen F3. A5. Queen D5. E6. Queen B5. A4. C7.
Resignation. 13 dark squares, 9 light squares, 20 bucks. That is a very small payment,
so even though I won this game, mission is failed.
[outro music]