100 rated chess, but you have to do en passant every 10 moves. That sounds pretty impossible.
But let's go anyway. We get a 1 51 from Pakistan. Checkmating him in the first 10 moves doesn't
sound very practical, so I guess I will have to do some en passant to extend the length of the game.
Therefore, E4. Well, of course I need to push pawns if I want to do the French move.
E5. D4. I know letting my pawn die in a pawn challenge sounds very stupid,
but bear with me, I have an idea. E takes D4. Yes. E5. Ha! You see, this guy is totally playing
in the palm of my hand. En passant. C takes. Okay. Change of plan. Now I have to checkmate
him in the next 10 moves, because there is no way I can get the second en passant on the board.
Therefore, queen. Takes D4. Queen A5 check. Bishop D2. Queen back to D8. Very funny.
Bishop C4. I'm calculating, knight C6, queen D5, knight F6, queen takes F7, checkmate.
Nevermind. Knight F3. I'm not gonna lie, it's already 4 moves out of 10,
but the checkmating plan is still nowhere near its target. Knight C6. Bishop B5.
Rook C8. You know what? Change of plan. The plan will go from checkmating him,
to forcing him to resign. Therefore, queen takes A7. Rook C7. That blunders a rook. Bishop A5.
King E7. Very aggressive. Bishop takes C6. 1 move left. B takes. Okay. It's 8 moves already,
and since there will definitely no en passant possible to happen, this will be my last move.
Bishop takes C7. Okay. Please resign. No. I know I have to end the video right now,
but please just bear with me. Just 1 more move, and I promise that he will resign.
That blunders a queen. Yeah. This is obviously impossible.
[Music]