100 rated chess, but circus is in town, for every point of material blundered.
You laugh for 10 seconds.
Playing a game with a longer time control will make this challenger walk in the Mondstadt.
Therefore I'll keep my normal time control.
We get a 100 rated guy from Vietnam.
And to those of you who are saying that I'm a coward for not playing bullet this game.
F*ck you.
E4.
D6.
Not very aggressive.
D4.
The plan is very simple.
The more I laugh, the more time it takes on my clock, so my only choice is to win this
game real fast before he manages to blunder my entire clock.
C5.
Bishop C4.
C takes D4.
Queen F3.
And just to be clear, I'm not blundering this pawn, it is called, a gambit, and now if he
can just go E5 to blunder his king, that will be very convenient.
Still pretty convenient, but not very convenient.
That blunders a pawn, and since a pawn is worth 1 point of material.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
10 seconds passed, queen takes F7.
King D7.
That drops an entire bishop, which is 3 points of material, but I definitely don't want to
sit here and laugh for entire half a minute.
Therefore.
Ha ha.
Time skip.
Queen E6 check.
If I had taken that bishop, I would have had to laugh for at least another 10 seconds,
so I decided to give a check, and in case he goes back, I will also go back and I won't
have to spend 30 seconds again because I've already spent it.
He went up instead.
Ha ha.
Queen D5 check.
And since he's already gone up, may as well just go this way.
Very convenient.
That blunders a king, and since there is no official value given to a king, I'm not
laughing here, queen B5.
Checkmate.
Mission accomplished, and to those people who are saying that king is worth 50 points
and I should have laughed for 500 seconds which means my time should have run out and
I lost by time.
F*** you.
[Music]