100 rated chess, but if an opponent's pawn... not piece, attacks one of your pieces... not pawns...
the video ends. Ha! This is obviously one of the easiest challenges ever. We get a 170 from Germany.
Man. No offense, but this guy has to be the lowest rated German out there. E4. E5. D4.
Since the pawns are the only things that can end my video, the best plan is obviously to trade all
of them down. Or not. I'll take it this way. E takes. Ah ha! Now queen takes is obviously the
best move, but then there is a big chance that he'll play c5 to end my video. Therefore, knight f3.
Queen e7. Wow! If I block with this bishop, I'm ending my own video. If I block with queen or
this bishop, d3 also ends the video. So I guess, we have no other choices. Come at me baby!
Ha! Coward. Now I'll take this pawn. I mean c5 does end the video,
but since he is obviously a coward, I bet he will never play that move in this entire game.
Of course. C3. Bishop a5. B4. Queen g5 check. That blunders a bishop. King c2. Well I mean if he
moves his bishop now and blunders his queen, I may not dare to take it because of f6 or h6 ending
the video, but who plays like that anyway? Right? No doubt. B takes a5. Ha! And now I'll take this
bishop. And even better, now he should be able to see, that c5 is just asking for knight b5
threatening a triple fork so he'll have to move his queen again. Right? Of course he sees it.
C4. Queen takes c4 check. That blunders a woman. Alright, now he should once again be able to see,
that c5 is just blundering a very obvious checkmate in 9 after a key 1 check. Right?
He sees everything. Rook e1 anyway. Ha! And just like that, there is no good way for him to end my
video anymore.
What the f-
[outro music]