If your king is in check and can't move out of check?
Wait. Not only I have to be
in check, I also have to
can't move out of check?
Ha! What kind of easy challenge is this?
There is no way I'm gonna lose, and since there's no way I'm gonna lose,
there is also no need to read this part of the challenge.
Let's go. We get a 173 from the US.
E3. Not very aggressive. I got a challenge that depends on king's
activity, and he made such a passive opening move.
E5. This is such an obvious victory for me.
Queen h5. Ah ha! Now we're talking. I was about to go king e7,
saying that I should give him some chances to end my video.
But of course, king e7 now is just blundering checkmate in 1.
So I guess, knight c6. Let's just delay king e7 for one move.
Well unless he blunders his queen to end my video.
Bishop c4. Well, I guess we'll have to delay the move for another move.
g6. It's fine guys, for most of the time,
people will just gonna play queen f3, which means I'll have to delay it for
one more move, and then I'll play it.
Did I just lose to that challenge? Oh well. I mean the video is still so
short. I'll answer some comments instead.
Your mom is in the thumbnail. No you. You did argue with my money though
last year. Well, to be honest I did argue with a lot
of donations ideas, due to them being things like exposing
my face, exposing my main account, or build a
freaking chess engine. So maybe yeah, your money might be in one
of those times.
Quack.
UHHH what is he drawing?
I think I tried to draw a bishop in that video,
and I think it looks fine.
[Music]