100 rated chess, but it's Halloween, if you scare an opponent's piece.
Not porn, but they don't run away, the video ends scarily.
This is going to be short. We get a 121 from the United Kingdom.
With diamond membership.
D4. E5.
Since the challenge is not applied to the pawns, it is definitely a great idea to just kill all
the pawns and open up the position for a quick attack at his king before he can end my video.
C3. Not very aggressive.
D5. Knight F3.
Ah ha. Here we go.
E4. Alright, now I'm scaring this knight, so if he doesn't move it, the video ends,
but since this attack is just as obvious as the fact that my viewers are absolutely maidenless,
there's no way he's not seeing it. Right?
Of course. That blunders a horsey to F6, but if I play F6 right now, maybe he'll realize that his
knight is actually trapped and then refuse to move it away, which breaks the rules and ends the video.
So I guess, bishop D6. This move is not scaring the knight because it is defended by a pawn,
so even if he doesn't move it away, the video will still continue.
But then somehow he still decided to move it.
King takes, that was unbelievably convenient.
Knight D2. Ah ha.
E3. The challenge said that if I scare a piece, that piece needs to move, now I'm scaring this
knight, so if he takes my pawn instead of moving the knight, the video ends, but he should be able
to see, that F takes E3 is obviously blundering, queen H4, check G3, bishop takes G3, check H takes
G3, queen takes G3, a very textbook checkmate in 3, so of course he'll have to move his knight right
now. Right?
What the f-
[outro music]