100 rated chess, but you're a conqueror, your pieces, and pawns, must only die on your opponent's
half of the board. Ha! Easiest challenge ever, we get a 130 from Lebanon, and I'll say that this guy
is pretty handsome, E4 may have to face E5 and then my E pawn will stuck on my side of the board,
which is not good because if he takes it, the video ends. Therefore, let's develop a knight
first, I mean if he can go E5 and blunder his E pawn now, that will be very convenient.
Of course it doesn't happen. E4. Queen E7. Very aggressive. E5, now Edward is officially in his
half of the board, so I absolutely don't care if he dies or not. C6. D4. Nothing wrong so far.
D5. Aha, now the French move is possible, but after queen takes, his queen will be open to
target many things in my half of the board, which is a bit dangerous for the video. So I guess,
A3, this move is to prevent knight C3 bishop B4 bishop takes C3 ending the video in the future.
Knight D7. Bishop G5, I mean there's F6 but I can't resist that feeling of trapping a woman
in her own house. F6. EF6 GF6 bishop H4. Trust me, I will win his queen. Bishop H6. Knight E5.
F takes E5. Aha, that blunders a woman. In no world do you take my pawn here instead of my bishop.
No doubt. Queen H5 check. King D8. Okay, now the question is, do I take his bishop?
I mean if I take his bishop, there is a big chance that he'll go E takes David, which ends the video.
Nah, I'm not gonna take that risk. D takes E5. Call me coward all you want, I'm just trying to
save my video, and who knows, maybe he'll decide to keep blundering his bishop. Ha, that is very
convenient. Queen takes H6. I'm sorry David, but at least you'll get to meet Edward in heaven.
Farewell David. Knight D2. And look at that, he can't even end my video, no matter how much he
wants to do so. D3. Aha, taking with bishop is obviously dumb, therefore, I'll take with pawn.
In no world do you take this pawn now.
What the f-
[Music]