100 rated chess, but you are frisk, every move must be filled with determination.
Every piece or pawn you capture must be a desperado or a lower value trade.
For those of you guys who don't know this is an undertale reference,
and if you don't know what undertale is, me neither.
E4. E5. I don't think my opponent can force me to make a desperado,
so we only need to care about the lower value trades.
Knight H3. D5. Queen F3. Aha! Now D takes E4 should be the best move,
but that only results in an equal trade, which is not allowed by the rules, bishop C5 instead.
Knight G5. Very aggressive. That blunders a horsey, but a blunder is not a lower value trade,
therefore, knight F6. I mean if he takes my knight right now, I actually also cannot take his queen
back because that is also not a lower value trade, but who plays like that anyway. Right?
No doubt. I cannot take that pawn back because that is an equal trade. C6.
Bishop C4. Castle. D takes C6. Aha! Knight takes C6. That was 2 pawns for 1,
so I believe that trade obeys the rules, but if you disagree with me and want to end the video
here. F*** you. Knight takes F7. I have to take that. Bishop takes. If I take his bishop now,
it's going to be an equal trade of a rook and pawn for 2 pieces, which is against the rules,
therefore, I have to move my king. Somehow I feel that this challenge is going very wrong very
quickly. Yeah. That's why. That blunders a queen, but once again, that is against the rules,
queen B6 instead. And this is not checkmate. F***! That blunders a queen,
but I don't even want to talk about it.
Let's hope that he thinks my bishop is magically defended by something.
Nevermind. Knight G8 is forced. Ha! My knight is defended by my king.
[Music]