100 rated chess, but you can only capture one piece, or pawn, every 10 moves.
Ha, in case you don't know, I have managed to defeat a lot of people without capturing any
pieces at all while also trying to do another challenge in the meantime, so this one should
be a walk in the park. We get a 187 from Australia. E4. I guess some people may say that I should have
played E4 instead of E4 to go for a more positional opening and avoid too many tactics and captures,
but sadly, I'm not a coward. E5. Knight F3. Knight F6. Normally I would have taken this pawn
without thinking, but classical Petrov defense requires a lot of captures and tactics, which is
definitely not good for this video, so I guess, Knight C3. Again, I'm not a coward, I'm just trying
my best to extend the video's length. Knight C6. Four knights game. Bishop C4. Man I hate this
boring opening. Bishop C5. Still theory by the way. And you know what? I'll stop the theory here.
Threatening an attack at his F-hawn, and even though he's been playing like he wants to castle
kingside, I doubt that a 170 rated player knows anything about that room. Exactly. That blunders
a horsey. With that knight's death, now I can not capture anything until move number 16, so in no
world do you take this knight here. Rook G8. Ha! I bet you he tried to castle. So of course. Castle.
Showing him how the professionals do it. Knight B4. Bishop B3. Queen F6. My god that looks like
a mouse lip. D3. No need to rush, I cannot capture anything until move 16, so we should just slowly
make progress here. Nevermind. That blunders a bishop, but king H1 is forced. I can already see,
that this video is not going to last for much longer. Bishop D4. Aha! That blunders a queen,
but in fact, it is him who's trying to backrank checkmate me, so I guess. Bishop D2. In no world
do you...
...do that.