If a piece or pawn captures a piece or pawn... oh wait...
My bad. If a piece or pawn captures a piece of higher value, the video ends.
Too easy. We get a 173 from Brazil. Before the game begins, let's make this clear. King is 3.5,
which means, if a king takes a rook or a queen, the video ends. E4. D5. I'll take it.
Queen takes. Knight c3. Of course my knight cannot take his queen due to the rules, but you know,
he doesn't know about that, and there is also a chance that he's gonna play queen h5,
allowing me to take his queen with my queen. Right? Queen d4. Well of course such a convenient
thing cannot happen that easily. Knight f3. Queen f4. Very aggressive. D4. Bishop f5. That blunders
a woman, but of course, I cannot take it, due to the rules. So I guess, bishop d3. Bishop takes d3.
That blunders the woman again, and you know, I think I'm just gonna put a number right here,
to see how many times that he is going to blunder his queen this game. Queen takes d3. Of course c
takes will end the video, so queen takes was pretty much my only choice. Knight c6. Castle.
Of course queen takes h2 will force me to end my video. But of course, no one plays like that
anyway. Right? Knight takes d4. Ha, that is of course still blundering the queen, but sadly,
I can only take the knight. Well I mean if he can just blunder his queen this way instead,
I can finally take it. Of course it doesn't happen. Knight db5. Okay, the game is almost done.
Right at the moment that he sees my bishop is attacking his queen, he will move his queen away,
which blunders the king instead. Knight g4. Ha, he's been blundering his woman for 7 times,
and now he wants to use that same woman to checkmate me. G, 6. Okay, now in no world do
you not see that your queen is under attack. I was wrong. King takes h2. 3.5 is bigger than 3.
Aha! Finally! That saves the queen from danger. But sadly, he has to give back the king.
Mission accomplished.
[Music]