I'm better than my viewers, you are black and white moves first.
Well, it's not like people gonna let me play with white anyway.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to another episode of I'm better than my viewers, the series
that I made so that people can humiliate me in a chess game, but apparently no one has
been able to do that yet, and the challenger this time is a guy called Texan Ranger.
He took a horsey.
I take a queen.
Man, it's actually pretty sad that even though this king has 10 wives, he has to spend his
life alone in a very distance corner of the board.
Queen takes queen queen takes queen queen takes queen queen takes queen.
We can call that the women fight.
Queen takes queen.
Bishop takes queen.
I bet he doesn't have the gut to take this bishop.
Ha!
Coward.
G4.
Okay so as you can see, Stockfish didn't like that move very much, but even after I've spent
an entire night thinking about this position, I still couldn't find any problems with it,
so if you have any explanations about this position, please feel free to leave a comment
below to brag about your IQ.
Queen takes F2.
Ah ha, I haven't taken this pawn yet because the queen might come down to C6 and absolutely
destroy my position, but since she has moved away from the diagonal.
Bishop takes E6.
D takes E6.
D5, opening up this very strong diagonal.
Queen takes G2.
This pawn is about to change his gender, therefore, bishop E5, preparing a skewer.
Queen takes E5.
That blunders a queen, bishop C7 discovered check.
King H7.
Rook takes E5.
Queen G6.
Very aggressive.
Knight G5 queen G5 F G5 king G6 rook G8 I don't see any checkmates king G5 rook G7 king
H4 ah ha.
Now queen H8 is a very obvious side-ranked checkmate in 1, but you know what they say,
if you see a mate in 1, look for better.
Knight F5 king H5 queen H8.
Checkmate in 2.
I'm better than my viewers.
[Outro]