100 rated chess, but queens are always protected. And furthermore, I cannot take my opponent's queen,
or lose my queen, because that will make the challenge too easy. Let's go, we get a 1 18 from
the US. E4. D5. Oh no no no no no no no. Taking his pawn is obviously provoking him to end my video.
Therefore, E5. The plan is simple. Close down every single way that his queen can go out.
F5. Ah ha, the French move always looks very tempting, but everyone knows, that it only
helps him develop his horsey. So I guess, D4. After all, en passant, is not forced.
Queen D6. I can easily tell, that the video is going to end, very soon. That blunders a queen,
but of course, I cannot take it due to the rules, and queen B4 is a threat, so I guess, C3. Please,
see that your queen is under attack and retreat her to the original square, because this is a bit
too dangerous for my video. Oh no please stop doing this to me. Queen H4 ends the video,
therefore, knight F3. Alright. It's still fine.
What the f-
[Outro]