100 rated chess, but you can only take their most extended piece, or pawn.
So in other words, I can only take what is closest to my territory.
Very challenging. We get a 1 24 American.
H3. Ah ha, long time no see, the Clemens opening.
E5. I actually don't know anything about the Clemens opening, so it's actually pretty scary.
G3. Not very aggressive.
D5. I mean if I don't have to capture anything,
I'm not breaking the rules, and the video can last longer.
F3. Very aggressive, I guess he wants to prevent E4, but sadly.
E4. F takes E4.
Bishop D6. I mean I actually cannot checkmate him because his E pawn is the most extended
material right now, but he should be able to see, that taking my pawn is obviously blundering a
checkmate in 1. Right? There we go. You see, always have faith in the 100 rated guys.
I'll take this pawn. D3. Man I have a feeling that this guy is just randomly pushing his pawns here.
Bishop takes G3 check. King E2.
Bishop F5. King D2.
Wow, it is very impressive to see a 100 rated guy seeing that he can move his king to unlock
the way for his bishop to defend a pawn. But anyway, knight C6.
Queen H5. Very aggressive.
Bishop G6, this is actually pretty problematic because now his queen is his most extended piece,
so unless he blunders his queen, I cannot continue to attack his king.
Well. That was very convenient.
Okay so I believe there are a lot of people already typing "paid actor" in the comment,
but please trust me, he's not a paid actor at all, because a paid actor would immediately
resign after blundering his queen instead of offering a draw like this.
Man, that was just a coincidence, and since the video is still so short,
I'll answer some of your comments instead.
You could've put this video "I am sometimes not better than my viewers".
No, I disagree, I'm better than my viewers, and even if sometimes I lose,
I'm still better than my viewers.
Plot twist it actually wasn't a viewer.
Oh, that's right, that actually makes sense because he actually beats me in that game,
and since I'm better than my viewers, it should've been me winning that game instead.
So now I absolutely agree with you that he was actually just pretending to be my viewer.
*quack*
Just fork me please, simp 2022.
Well, actually, this video was produced and published on December 29th, 2021.
*outro music*