I'm better than my viewers, Vietnam War. In Vietnam we call it the American War,
but what's the difference anyway? Men and women and people in the middle,
it is another I'm better than my viewers video, and today's viewer is a guy called Cullen1994,
with an ELO of whopping 2400 rating points. And it's funny that I've just banned two of
his accounts just a few minutes prior to this game. I'll take this pawn first.
Bishop takes d4. Ah ha, it seems like Stockfish didn't really like that move,
so it is my chance to take over the advantage. And that was also not the correct move.
D takes e6. He makes a mistake again, and rook g5 cannot be a wrong move. I mean it wasn't the
best move, but it's still a fine move. And in this position, my opponent took a very long time off
the clock thinking what to do next, so I gave him an offer. Queen f5 is very natural. I mean,
I'm thinking of something else but I don't know. Alright, it's risky but I'm losing anyway.
Queen takes c3. So instead of trying to defend his king, he decided to counterattack me on the
other side. In this position, there is a textbook and very easy to see checkmate in 10, so if you
want an easy morning warmup for an energetic day, please feel free to pause the video right now to
find the checkmate pattern, while I don't give you any seconds to do so. Knight e7 king h7 knight f5
discover check king h8 bishop d4. And even though the best move right now is obviously king takes
d4, knight takes d4. I mean I obviously saw what the best move was, but I decided to give him a
chance at continuing the game. Rook g8. Queen f7. Knight f2 check. King e3. It's always good to play
with your food. Knight g4 check. King d2. Queen g2 check. King c3. Knight f6. Queen f6 rook g7,
and even though queen g7 is checkmate in 1, rook takes g2. As a grandmaster once said,
if you see a mate in 1, look for better. Rook g8 queen check rook blocks queen takes h7.
Checkmate. I'm better than my viewers.
So,