It's April Fool's Day, so why not go for...
100 rated chess.
But I lie to my opponent.
And who the hell is Elis?
But anyway, we get a 100 rated simp from Kuwait.
The plan is simple.
I try my best to trick him to resign, and if he can survive my lies until move 10, the mission is failed.
E4.
I will start telling my lies from move 2.
E5.
Yeah.
Here we go.
Hi, I'm a girl.
Can you let me win please?
Ha!
Now just resign you simp.
D4.
No.
Ah ha.
So he is playing hard to get now isn't he?
E takes D4.
To make things look real, I will tell a lie every two moves,
so that he won't think that I'm just trying to get free rating points.
C3.
D3.
He's trying to give back his pawn, but before that...
I'm single, and I can give you my phone number.
Bishop takes D3.
I don't want.
Wow.
A very tough guy ha.
Bishop C5.
Knight F3.
No worries.
I'm very confident that he will immediately resign after my next lie.
Queen F6.
All right.
Let's see if he can resist to this.
We can go on a date.
Question mark.
E5.
Oh wow.
He doesn't reply anymore, so I guess he's really thinking about it.
But anyway.
That blunders a queen.
I mean since he's already blundered a queen, maybe he'll also decide to resign right now.
Nevermind.
All right.
It's time for me to pull out my strongest weapon.
Oh please.
I just want to have a boyfriend to teach me how to play chess.
Bonus.
A crying emotes.
Ha.
Let's see how he can resist that.
King takes F2.
The mission only lasts until before move 10, so the next move is pretty much all I have.
Knight H6.
Wow.
He still doesn't reply.
I'll take that knight.
This is the last move, so please just res-
Mission.
Failed.
[Music]