100 rated chess, but you are *******, you can only take enemy pieces, or pawns, from behind.
And this challenge was posted on Valentine's Day.
Very aggressive. We get a 191 from the US.
E4. E5. My pawns are actually useless because they can never do it from behind,
but I of course need to push them forward to create space for the other pieces to move.
Bishop C4. Knight F6. G4. Aha! That blunders 2 pawns at the same time, but funny enough,
I can not take any of them due to the rules. So I guess. H6. At least it will stop G5 from happening.
Not anymore. D5. Since my pawns are useless anyway,
it's better to just sacrifice this one to open up the way for my bishop to go out.
E takes D5, bishop G5 is best, but again, I cannot take that pawn from the front. Bishop C5.
G5. Knight G4. The plan is very simple. Since he's been very aggressively pushing his pawns to
attack my knight, I think we can expect F3 coming next attacking my knight which let me plunge my
knight really deep into his territory. Or he can take my knight which blunders his woman and I
cannot eat her because my bishop cannot do anything in front of a woman. C6. I don't know,
just want to sack more pawns to create more room for the pieces to move. Queen H5. Bishop F5.
King D1. Not very aggressive. And you know what? I think we should take a risk. Queen C8. Wait for
it. Knight F3. Alright. Here we go. Bishop G4. His queen. Is trapped. But still, now there are
3 things that can happen. Situation 1, he resigns after seeing his queen is trapped. Situation 2,
he continues to play, but decides to not move his queen anywhere, which allows my bishop to
thrust his knife into her from behind. Situation 3, he makes a desperado. And I'm f***ed. And before
I show you what happened, I just want to say thank you to one of my viewer that donated me a massive
amount of 1000 US dollar. I really appreciate it. Back to the game, and his decision was.
Resignation. Mission accomplished.
[Music]