100 rated chess, but your pieces, and pawns, have anger issues, a piece, or pawn, cannot
capture unless when it is attacked, and from then on, it is only allowed to do moves with
captures. Sounds absolutely impossible, but of course, I'm not a coward. We get a 1 24
from Brazil. E4. It's fine, all we have to do is to win, while trying our best to avoid
as many captures as possible. E5. D4. The plan is simple, E takes D4, C3, D takes E3,
bishop C4, C takes B2 will be attacking my bishop so I can go bishop takes B2. A perfect
Danish gambit. Nevermind. I'm attacking this pawn, but he's also attacking my pawn, therefore,
D takes E5. Knight takes E5. F4. I mean even if he decides to leave his knight here, I
actually cannot take it because this pawn is not being attacked by anything, but who
plays like that anyway? Right? Of course. F5 is just blundering queen H4 queen E4 queen
H1. Therefore, knight F3. In no world do you take this pawn and then laugh into my face
because I cannot take your knight due to the rules. Are you serious? Knight C3. Bishop
E7. Bishop C4. I mean he should be able to see, that knight takes G2 check is just blundering
a horsey after king F2 knight H4 queen D5 knight H6 bishop takes H6 and then he'll have
to castle instead of taking my bishop back. Right? Of course he sees it. G3. Well actually
if he retreats his bishop right now, I still won't be able to take his knight due to the
rules, but most people will just make a desperado here. Right? Knight G2 check. That traps a
horsey. Bishop takes G3. I'm attacking his bishop, and he's also attacking my pawn, therefore,
H takes G3. Knight F6. And again, I still cannot take this knight, due to the rules.
This horsey is f***ing invincible. Knight G5. Let's try to checkmate him real fast before
his other horsey can cause the same amount of destruction. Knight takes E4 check. That
knight is also attacking my knight, therefore, that blunders a horsey. F6. I'll take this
pawn. Queen E7. Queen H5 check. Queen F7. Ah ha! My woman is attacking his woman, and since
his woman is also attacking my woman, there can only be one woman wins. King D8 is forced.
Ah ha! That blunders a king to knight G5 rook E8 knight E6 rook E6 rook H8 rook E8 rook
E8 checkmate in 4, but since the rules said after capturing, a piece can only make moves
with captures. So I guess, knight takes F6. He should be able to see, that rook takes
H1 is just blundering queen to E8 checkmate in 1. Right? That is very convenient. Queen
takes F8. Checkmate. Mission, accomplished.
[Music]