100 rated chess, but the amount of reactions in this message is the amount of pre-moves you have
to make. 9? Is not that many. First move is obviously the best time to make a pre-move. E5.
Pre-move successfully. D4. I'll take that pawn. It's pretty obvious that his queen will recapture.
Knight C6 pre-move. And even if he doesn't recapture, knight C6 is still a very good
developing move. Exactly as planned. Queen E4 check. Bishop blocks. Knight F6 pre-move,
and in no world do you take my bishop here with a check and ruin my pre-move.
Of course. Queen F3. Knight D4. Knight takes F6 check is a threat, but of course he doesn't
want me to put my bishop on a more active square, so of course he won't be doing that,
and I expect he'll be going queen E3 blundering his queen, knight takes E2 pre-move. Very risky,
but I'm down to sacrifice a horsey for the greater good. Well? I mean the pre-move worked,
but didn't as I expected. Ha! Nevermind, it worked as I expected. Knight E4 knight G3.
Free woman. Castle. It's pretty concerning that he may decide to resign too early as I have
already taken his queen halfway into the challenge. Doesn't count, 9 is too many,
and there is no way a 100 rated guy can last 20 moves against me, so mission accomplished,
and I'll answer some comments. I expected the rushy song to be played. There is a thing called
copy strike. This video is too short, answer some comments instead. No? You are wrong.
This video is too short, so I'm answering some comments instead. Assuming pawns are female is
different from assuming females are pawns, besides in the rushy isles, the monarch is called king
even if they are female, so who knows, maybe queens are male. I actually have a video about
queen David, but I don't remember which one, so yeah, queens can be male.
[Music]