100 rated chess, but you are sexist, your king must get more captures than your queen,
open parenthesis, your queen must get at least one capture, close parenthesis.
Disclaimer, I'm not sexist.
E3. The royal couple are the protagonist and deuteragonist of this video,
therefore, I'll open the way for them.
E4. That's our first chance. D5. C takes queen takes and we're done with the woman.
But I guess we're stuck with the woman.
Bishop C5. I'm trying to get his eyes to tunnel vision into this specific area of the board.
Work like a charm.
Queen takes D5. Alright, one capture for the wife, two more captures for the husband.
E4. Queen D4. Believe it or not, my queen is actually pretty safe on D4.
Queen E2. Here we go. King E7. Push him baby.
G4. Very aggressive. But since I'm not a coward, I have to be. Even more aggressive.
Knight H3. H5. This knight is very suspicious.
Knight G5 check. King F6.
H4. HG4. Bishop G2. That blunders a pawn. Of course it's a brilliant move,
and he should obviously see, that rook takes H4 is risking his own king's life.
Nevermind. Queen G1 is best, but if queen blocks I'll have to trade queens which leads to my queen
capturing unnecessary too many pieces and will create more problems for my king. Therefore,
I'll keep things simple. Rook H1. Coward. King F4. Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
Knight A3. This guy really likes to put his horses on the edge of the board.
G takes F3. This is actually a massive blunder, and in fact, any moves could have been a blunder
in that scenario, so there is no problem if he doesn't see D3. As expected. This is a good
chance to complete the challenge. Bishop G4. Bishop takes queen. F2. Queen takes bishop. Takes
king. Takes king. Takes. My king has officially captured more materials than my queen, which means
the rest of the game is now just a normal game, therefore I'll have to end the video here to
avoid being called a smurf. Have a great day.
[Music]