100 rated chess, but you can only move your king. And I did it successfully.
Smiley face. And it came with a picture. Draw by stalemate, 32 blunders,
and one guy's name is chessimp69. With a weird avatar face.
But anyway, we get a 300 rated from Philippines.
Knight f3. Well, since the challenge only allows me to move my king, and it's stuck now.
So I guess. No wait. I was kidding. Let's just assume that we can move a pawn for our first move.
E5. Since I'm not using any pieces or pawns this game, the best use for those trash is obviously,
gambits. And he didn't even take it. King e7 is forced. What the f*** was that?
Alright then. King e6. It would be nice if he blunders his knight now.
I solemnly swear, that this guy is not a paid actor.
King d5. King c3. Ha, he obviously wants to move his king forward to have more fun with my king.
Therefore. King c5. No chance for you sir. King back to d3. Oh wait.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking guys? King back to d5. King c3. Hell yeah. King c5.
Okay dude. Just one more time, and we both are happy. King d3. Ha. Easiest mission of my entire
channel. King d5. Draw by repetition. Mission accomplished, but since the video is so short,
I'll answer some of your comments instead. The king is not a piece. So if you open up google
search and then type. The king is a piece. You can see here is a result of. The king is a piece
in chess. But when you type the king is not a piece, you can receive a weird suggestion that
is not even grammatically correct. How did you get a 435 opponent as a 100? You can blame chess.com
for that man. They even paired me with a 1900 sometimes. Well. Beaver's claw by Maximum Arief.
I have no idea.
(upbeat music)