If a piece or pawn lets their king down, which means they are captured with check.
And this will give me a copyright strike, so let's just change it to the video ends.
So let's sum it up. If a capture comes with a check, the video ends. Let's go.
I normally don't take on challenges that are too easy, but you know, I can't argue with money.
We get a 149 from the US. E4. And the best thing is, he cannot check me in this position,
no matter how hard he tries. E5. Since this challenge is quite easy,
let's go for a risky opening line. D4. Queen E7. Very aggressive. I'll take this pawn.
Queen takes. Ah ha, now queen takes E4 comes with a check. Therefore, knight C3. Well of course
queen takes C3 also ends the video, but who plays like that anyway? Right? Well no one plays like
that either. And even though I should have ended the video right now, I'll answer some of your
comments to make the video longer instead. You're actually miserable, sad. Step outside.
I disagree, there is covid out there, and if there's no reason to go out, not only me,
but no one should go outside. Zero missed win when you show us that you can win in one move
several time, good stockfish. Fun fact, all of those missed checkmate in one in the video were
considered as blunders instead of missed win, and just like you, I also don't understand why.
It is fascinating how a king can easily get a harem, it's very cool to even have 4 wives at a
time, very cool. Well, until you realize that your new wives are actually pawns,
who were technically men, that changed their gender.
[carnival music]