100 rated chess, but the light squares have minds, if you land on a light square, that
piece, or pawn, becomes disabled.
Definitely not racist at all.
We get a 1 22 from India.
An impossible challenge, against an impossible opponent.
C4.
Half of my board is disabled.
E5.
Queen A4.
Very aggressive.
My dark square bishop is very important in this game, so developing him this way is very
dangerous.
G5.
D3.
Bishop G7.
G4.
C5.
I don't know, just randomly pushing the pawns that I can push, and hope that something great
will happen.
E4.
Knight C6.
And since this knight is now on a light square.
It's dead.
Knight F3.
Queen D6.
Right after developing a knight, people normally develop their bishop.
Exactly as planned.
I'll take this pawn.
I mean it's actually very risky as my queen cannot change color.
But I really need to take risks if I want the slightest chance to win this challenge.
Queen back to D1.
Very weird.
I'll take this rook.
Queen C2.
That last pawn that can be pushed.
A5.
Knight D2.
Ah ha.
He's planning to trap my queen, and even though it normally wouldn't work as I can counter
attack his queen, my knight is actually dead according to the rules.
So I guess.
I'll run.
Man.
It's actually pretty problematic as I don't really have many dark square moves left.
Nevermind.
Wow.
And since the video is still so short, I'll answer some of your comments instead.
Why not just restart the challenge with a new game and post that instead?
You must be new to the channel, we don't do that here.
Is that python colon o o o o?
No it's a snake.
That doesn't count in my eyes.
So disconnecting is a new way of saying I failed the challenge but won't show it.
You've known too much.
[Outro Music]