100 rated chess, but your every third move has to be a blunder? According to Stockfish.
Man, I don't know why so many people reacted to this idea, but it's kinda obvious,
that this video is not going to last long. We get a 281 from Netherlands.
H3. Aha, long time no see, the Clemens opening. E5.
G3. Not very aggressive. D5. F3. Alright, as much as I hate it,
the third move has come, and as the rule requested, this has to be a blunder. Therefore,
Bishop takes H3, but not yet, I still have to check if Stockfish thinks that it's a blunder.
Thank you. E3. Wow, don't tell me that he's also doing some stupid challenge like I am.
Bishop back to E6, well at least that helps me save a piece. D3. Knight C6. C3. Three moves went
by real fast. And again, Bishop back to H3. Stockfish? Of course. B3. Bishop back to E6 again.
A3. Knight F6. Ha, now all pawns are forward, I wonder what he's going to do now. Another pawn
push. I solemnly swear, that this guy is not a paid actor. But anyway. A blunder is forced.
Stockfish? Yes. And I mean since he didn't take my Bishop the last 2 times, he won't take it this
time, right? Wow. That's weird. D4. Congratulations to myself, the video has officially got past move
10. Well unless he resigns right now. C takes D4. E takes D4. E takes D4. I really want to take this
pawn, but sadly, a blunder is forced. Stockfish? Thank you. Castle. D5. Very aggressive. I'll take
it. Queen takes B7. Again, very aggressive. That move blunders a piece to Qe8. Check King F2. Rook
B8. Qe6. Rook takes B1. But sadly, a blunder is forced. I'm blundering my knight on C6, but since
he's already up 4 points in materials, I have a feeling that Stockfish is not going to think that
it is a blunder. Yeah. I saw that was coming.
[Music]