100 rated chess, but if your opponent moves a piece, you move a pawn, and vice versa.
Sounds fun. We get a 137 from Brazil.
E4. That's a pawn move, so I have to move a piece.
Queen h5 check. Very aggressive. Queen is also a piece, therefore, g6.
Queen c5. E5 is obviously the best move. But I'm afraid, that there is a chance that he's
gonna blunder queen takes e5, thinking that it forks my king and rook, and since it's a piece
move, I'll have to move a pawn, and since there is no legal pawn move, I'll have to end my video.
So I guess. E6. You know what people say. Better be safe than sorry.
Knight c3. That blunders a queen, but since it's a piece move, I guess I finally have to play.
E5. You know, moving the other pawns may get him to notice that his queen is being attacked.
Aha! Now that really blunders a queen. Knight d5. Oh no. I have a feeling,
that bad stuff is going to happen, very soon. Now there are knight f6 and knight c7 check ending the
video, because there is no legal pawn move in a knight check. But sadly, I have to move a pawn.
All I can do, is just to pray, that he doesn't end my video right now.
Yes. Another pawn move. Let's just hope that I can move my bishop and take his knight quickly
for the video's safety. Bishop e2. Another pawn move. Castle. Another pawn move. Man. At this
point, I'm afraid that I'll have to move the pawns for the entire game. Knight d2. Pawn again. I mean
as long as he doesn't end my video, I'm fine with keeping moving pawns forward. C3. Aha! Finally.
Bishop e6. Okay. Come on. Just one more pawn move, and I can finally get rid of this dangerous horsey.
What the f-
[Music]