I'm better than my viewers? Arrow. To me it looks more like a d***head. But anyway.
Girls and boys and others, welcome to another I'm better than my viewers video, and today's
viewer is a guy called Manos Sef. These knights are way too close to my king. I'll eliminate them
first. B takes e6. d7 check. Knight B takes d7. E takes d7 check. King e7 blundering king f3
discovered check knight e4 or takes e4 checkmate in two will be very convenient.
Didn't happen. I don't know why Stockfish hates his move so much, but I'll take this knight
regardless. Knight takes f6. Aha, that removes a defender of the king, Stockfish even goes as far
as saying this is a forced mate in 9, and even though I cannot see this very difficult checkmate
in 9 yet. Let's start with a check. Queen blocks. I'll take. Queen 7 takes e7 is blundering queen
takes d8 a very cool checkmate in one with his king being checkmated while being right next to
his wife. He didn't fall for it. I'll trade. And then he said. I'll do it for the content,
put my next message in the video. I offer a draw. Good content. Knight takes d7. Rook takes d7.
H takes g4. Aha, now king g2 will bring my king to absolute safety, but you know what? I'm not
a coward. G5 check. King takes g5. I will never retreat. Nevermind. Bishop sacrifice. Knight
takes rook check. King over rook sac king takes. And at this point, everything is hopeless.
I'm better than my viewers.
[Music]