I'm better than my viewers. You are white. No I'm actually Asian. But it's fine.
Girls and boys and people in the middle, welcome to another episode of I'm better than my viewers,
and today's viewer is an 800 rated guy called... Nando.
D5. A wise man once said, "If you have a past pawn, push him until he's passed."
Knight D7. Pawn push. Bishop takes pawn takes rook takes. Rook D3 putting his rook behind my
pawn will be very dangerous. Rook D4. There is no need to defend this pawn, as it takes too much
effort to actually make that pawn valuable to my position. He took it. Rook H2 will also be very
dangerous. Rook D2. This rook alone will act as my defender, now I only need a chance to use the
other one to make some counterplays. Rook HH1. He wants a skewer. I'll protect my rook. A trade
should be bad for me, but managing to have two pawns very far forward may get him to tremble a
little bit. F4. I want rook A7, but there is a skewer, so king B3 first. I'll move my king around
this pawn to avoid future checks, but in this position, my opponent made a monstrous positional
decision. Rook H3 king B2 rook H1. He spent two moves just to bring my king back to B2, so that
if he checks me next, I cannot move my king in front of my pawn to avoid the checks, which seriously
reduce my king's safety, and even though I can move him back to B3 aiming for a repetitional
draw, he knows I definitely won't do that as I'm obviously not a coward. Rook K7 then. That was a
really bad move as it puts my king in a lot of danger, but since he's playing like a grandmaster
right now, I'd rather take a risk. Check check king D3. Rook B3 then I guess I'll resign.
Nevermind. That blunders a horsey. Finally, the unpaid actor part is kicking in.
Now he checks. King up. G5. And with that, this game is now a draw.
Actually it's a win. I'm better than my viewers.
[Music]