100 rated chess, but on each turn you randomly choose between, horizontal, vertical, diagonal,
and you have to move that way for this turn. Let's add a number 4. Horsey. Very simple.
First of all, we need to create the directions. Next, we create the exception. Our move is going
to be randomly chosen among all of the directions and exceptions. But since my computer is a noob,
I have to teach him what random is, and then we just need print out the result. Very. Simple.
We get a 2 0 0 from Australia. D4. Alright I mean if I roll horizontal or diagonal here,
the video ends, but that's life. Ha. Nevermind. Knight F6. F4. No diagonals allowed yet.
Vertical. D5. Alright, now the game truly begins. E3. Diagonal, bishop G4. I mean there will be a
small problem if he takes my bishop right now and I cannot roll a knight next move.
But who plays like that anyway? Right? Of course. That blunders a queen, so now I need. Diagonal.
It's fine. Queen C8. Knight F3. Another knight move, knight C6. Bishop E2. Quite frankly,
anything besides horizontal is good now. Of course. Queen D8. Queen A4. Another knight move,
another knight move, and since this knight is pinned, knight E4 I guess. I can already see,
that this game is going very wrong very quickly. Knight E5. Ah ha, that knight is forking my knight
and my bishop. So please, god of RNG. I need. A diagonal. Thank you my lord. Bishop D7. G3.
That blunders a horsey, but to be honest, as long as I don't roll a diagonal again,
I'm fine with whatever the result is. Alright, bishop H3. Please get tunnel vision.
Ha, so he didn't get tunnel vision, but also didn't see the knight hanging.
Another knight move, knight F6. My god why do I keep rolling horses. C takes D5. Okay. RNG god.
I desperately need. Another knight move. Vertical. Ha. Still fine. I mean I'll be losing my woman if
he goes knight C3 right here and I roll a knight next. But what are the odds. Right?
It's fine, it's not like I get another horsey here.
I'm buying another computer. Knight H5. Oh no my horsey.
Ha. Not even close. Diagonal, queen E6 is kinda forced. I mean it's still very bad after D5,
but there is a chance that. Nevermind. Another knight. What kind of 25% is this?
Knight takes G3. Oh no my horsey again.
You know what, I'm not gonna play this game anymore, this is absolutely impossible. Have a great day.
[Music]