On March 17th, 2022, a Discord member sent me this.
He wants me to play the White Pieces, but what the f*** is that king doing over there?
Well, I think this can still be a legit idea. Therefore, I decided to make a new series.
I'm better than my viewers. And of course, we'll start the first episode,
with this very position right here. My first challenger is a Discord member called W!
First move, King B5 will put my king closer to the center. So I guess, King A5. Knight C6 check.
Very aggressive. King A4. The plan is simple. Pull my king back. And that's all.
A6. Ah ha, big chance right here. B4, King B3 coming up. There we go. King B3. Ha, your chance
is over W! Now is my time to counterstrike. D5. D4. Knight F6. C3. Solidify the center.
Queen D6. Oh no. Every time I see a woman, I see trouble coming my way. Knight F3. A5. Bishop D2.
Surprisingly, I don't think my position is bad at all. Bishop G4. E? No. H3. Bishop takes F3.
E takes F3. A takes B4. I really want to take this pawn now, but I guess I should pay attention
to my king first. C takes B4. Fun fact, Stockfish actually suggested me to take the pawn instead.
But to be honest, I think that is way too aggressive. G6. Bishop takes B5. Rook B8.
I'll take this knight. That knight has been causing too much trouble for my king until now.
Queen takes. Knight C3. Oh wait I blundered a big check. Ha. Nevermind. A3. Well at least he can
win back his pawn. That's totally fair with me. Bishop E3. I mean the check is still possible,
but with my B pawn protected by the A pawn, I don't think it's that good anymore.
E6. Well, I guess the check was still better than that move. That blunders a woman. I solemnly swear
that this guy is not a paid actor. E6. Wow. I'm surprised that he can remain absolutely calm and
play a best move after blundering a queen like that. Rook E1. I guess the game is still on with
this amount of self-control that he has. Nevermind. That blunders a rook. Knight D7. Alright,
we had fun, now let's end this game real fast. Queen D4 E5 Queen takes D5 F6 Rook E D1 Knight B6
Rook A8 check Oh no my rook knight takes A1 Queen D7 checkmate. To all of those people who have been
back seating my videos. I'm better than my viewers.
you
(upbeat music)
Oh