If your opponent plays a move that has never been played before,
the video ends.
Playing 3 minute splits on a 100 rated account.
This is going to be short.
In fact, I will be surprised if this video can last over move 5.
But anyway, in order to do this challenge, I need an opening database.
And this time, I'll use the Leech S database.
I actually wanted to use the chess.com one, but sadly, it requires premium membership.
And I'm poor.
Disclaimer.
Using an opening database is not much different from using a chess engine, which is considered cheating.
Therefore, in this video, I only used the database, after the game is already done.
Which means I didn't cheat during the game.
And with that out of the way, let's find an opponent.
That was fast.
We get a 192 from Australia.
So in order to extend this video, I believe that I need to play, as theoretical, as possible.
Therefore,
E4.
The most played move in the book, with over 1 million games on Leech S.
But even though I have played the most famous move, there are still some chances, that the video is going to end, right now.
E5.
Thank god.
Let's continue.
Knight F3.
Knight C6.
Yes.
Now as you can see, bishop B5 is the most popular move here.
But sadly, I didn't know that during the game.
So I played, bishop C4.
Which is also a very famous move, so there's nothing bad about it.
Right?
Knight F6.
Ah ha!
He's provoking me to play knight G5, the fried liver.
Now as you can see, D3 is the most popular move in this position, but once again, I didn't know that during the game.
So I played, knight G5.
There are a ton of theories in the fried liver, so I think that this will at least get the video a bit longer.
[Fried liver]
That blunders a horsey.
But anyway.
What the f-
[Outro]