If a player makes a move that undoes their previous move, the video ends.
Playing 3 minute splits on a 100 rated account.
Ha ha.
This is obviously a big successful challenge.
I mean who even does that in the first place?
We get a 189 from Ukraine.
E4.
Ha ha.
A pawn move cannot be undone.
Still, if he moves the other pieces, there is always a very small chance that he's going
to undo those moves.
Therefore, I think I should keep him busy.
D5.
F3.
Very aggressive.
D takes E4.
Knight C3.
Ah, now knight back to B1 ends the video.
But once again, who the heck does that anyway?
He takes F3.
G takes.
So instead of taking back with his knight, he decided to take back with the G pawn, which
also cannot be undone.
I mean, yesterday was a devastating loss.
But today, it's definitely the easiest challenge to be accomplished.
E5.
Queen E2.
Knight C6.
I bet my entire fortune that queen D1 is not going to happen.
D3.
Knight F6.
Man, I can't express how happy I am every time I see him moving his pawns.
Knight H3.
I'll take it.
Bishop takes.
Even though I don't think it will happen, bishop F1 is still a threat.
Therefore, bishop B4.
I want to lure his attention towards this side of the board, instead of the other side.
Bishop D2.
Bishop takes C3.
I want to trade down the pieces, since the fewer pieces on the board, the more space
for the other pieces to move, and the lesser chance that he's going to make weird moves.
Bishop takes.
Castle.
Oh no my pawn.
Bishop takes E5.
That blunders a bishop.
Queen takes E5.
That blunders a queen.
Rook E8.
And in no world do you move your queen back here.
Why is he thinking for so long?
What the f-
Oh no.
(upbeat music)
[Music]