If a piece or pawn lands on B4, the video goes back in time.
Ah ha! B4 and B4. Good joke there.
But anyway, we get A208 from Chile.
For those of you who are looking for the B4 square, it is right here.
If anything lands on this square, the video ends.
First move. The most obvious threat right now is E5, followed by bishop to B4.
Therefore, knight F3.
Well, technically, if he plays E5 right now, I will have to play things like A3 to prevent bishop B4,
and then he can push E4 to attack my knight, which should be really good for him.
But let's be real. No one plays like that. Right?
D6. Wow! Not only he didn't open up his bishop, he also put another pawn in front of it,
and further disallow bishop B4.
This video is definitely going to be very long.
D4. Bishop D7. Not very aggressive.
E4. C5. Ah ha!
Now it looks kinda like a Sicilian, just with a weird bishop on D7.
But anyway. Bishop C4. Such a peaceful game for the 100-rated ELO.
Okay no more peaceful game now.
Bishop D2. The bishop blocks the check, counterattacks on the queen, and also controls the B4 square.
He totally deserves a pay rise.
Queen A4. Very aggressive.
Bishop B3. Please remember that your queen is still unable to go to B4.
(The end)
(Subscribe)
(More videos)
(Please subscribe)