If an equal trade of pieces, not pawns, happens, the video ends.
Playing 3 minute splits on a 100 rated account.
Well, I think that I have already done something like this in the past.
But of course, I can't argue with money.
Therefore, let's find an opponent.
[Music]
That took quite some time.
We get a 400 rated from Brazil.
E4.
E5. Nothing special.
Knight F3.
Ah ha! Now if I play knight C6, he will get a big chance to play bishop B5,
which will force me to move my knight again, since he may decide to take it next turn.
Knight F6 also doesn't look good, because after knight takes E5, D6, knight F3,
knight takes E4, queen E2, queen E7, D3, knight back to F6, queen takes E7 forces me to take the queen back,
which is a trade, and therefore ends this video.
So I guess, my only choice that makes sense is,
D6.
Bishop C4.
Knight F6.
I'm trying to get him to play knight G5, which looks like fried liver.
But then I have D5, E takes D5, and since the white pawn on D5 doesn't have a knight to attack,
I can play bishop D6, which makes his bishop gets blocked by his own pawn.
Knight C3.
He saw it.
Bishop G4.
Developing my light square bishop first, which allows me to play knight D7,
since knight C6 is just ending my own video.
Knight takes E5.
Very aggressive.
Right at the moment that I pinned down his knight, he moved his knight to prove that
I didn't pin anything.
But anyway,
that blunders a queen.
Bishop takes F7 check.
I thought he was planning something like knight takes F7, but this is actually even better for me.
Alright then.
King E7 is forced.
Knight D5 check.
Wait.
I think I understand now.
He thought that after bishop takes F7, king E7, knight D5 is checkmate,
and totally missing my knight on F6.
But the worst thing is, now he's forcing me to play knight takes D5,
and then he can take my knight back, which makes me a fool, for ending my own video.
Are you serious?
Okay.
Alright.
It's fine.
There are still chances, that he won't take back the knight, or take the bishop,
because taking the bishop is also counted as a trade.
Knight takes D5 is forced.
Please don't take back
my knight.
I hate this guy.
[Music]