If a piece or a pawn is captured on an uneven numbered rank, the video ends.
Playing 3 minute splits on a 100 rated account.
This shouldn't be too hard. Let's find an opponent.
[Music]
We get a 2 22 from the US.
Black pieces.
Man, I think it would be easier if I got the white pieces.
But anyway, this is life.
For those of you who are wondering how to count the rank numbers, don't worry.
They are all written right, here.
If something dies on the odd numbered ranks, the video ends.
D4.
Knight F6.
Just want to put my horsey on an even rank.
Queen D3.
Very aggressive.
D6.
F3.
G6.
You know, I'm just trying to play on the even ranks here.
E4.
Again, very, aggressive.
Bishop G7.
C3.
This guy is very aggressive and very solid at the same time.
This guy is such a legend.
I'll castle.
Bishop F4.
Knight.
C6.
I mean the D7 square is on an uneven rank, right?
Knight D2.
Okay now how do I make progress?
I mean normally people would play E5, D takes E5, knight takes E5, bishop takes E5, D takes E5, and it's a winning position for black.
But of course, a capture on E5, ends the video.
So I guess, A5.
Let's just B.
A pawn pushing simpleton.
Long castle.
Very risky.
B6.
Queen B5.
Man! This guy is really aggressive.
Bishop D7.
Queen C4.
Queen B8.
Knight E2.
B5.
There is no way this is a move.
Why is he thinking for so long?
Queen back to D3.
B4.
Please take! It's on an even rank.
Yes!
Knight takes.
Even rank baby!
Queen C4.
That blunders a queen.
Now I have, bishop E6, D5, knight F takes D5, E takes E5,
E takes D5, bishop takes D5, trapping the queen.
Of course things may proceed differently, but I believe that losing only a queen is the best continuation for him.
But no! Because you know, that sequence ends the video.
Therefore, bishop to B5.
Queen B3.
Bishop D3.
I'm just slowly getting in there.
Queen A4.
Let's see.
I think I need more pieces into the attack.
Knight back to D7.
Oh no my video!
No!
Because he should be able to see, that if he goes queen takes D7,
knight takes A2, is a checkmate in one.
*click*
I can already see, that some people are going to say,
"You did that on purpose."
But anyway,
what the f-
*outro music*