If a piece, not a pawn, lands on the H-file,
simp names a good adult anime,
playing 3 minute splits on a 100 rated account,
of course, the starting position, doesn't, count.
Man, this video is so going to get demonetized.
But anyway, let's still find an opponent.
We get a 1 67 from Singapore.
Yes. In case you don't know, Singapore is considered to be the smartest country in the world,
with an average IQ of 108.
Therefore, there's no way he's going to play such an absurd move like knight to H3.
Right?
E3.
Aha! The threat is obviously Qh5.
Therefore, G6.
Well, since he's from Singapore, I don't think he's going to develop his queen first.
But you know, better be safe than sorry.
Qf3.
Thank god I was playing safe.
Now since the queen has occupied the f3 square, the move knight H3 is more likely going to happen.
But sadly, there's no way I can prevent it.
So I guess, knight f6.
Bd3.
D6.
It's starting to look like a king's Indian position.
Knight c3.
Bg4.
I'm giving him my b7 pawn, just to get the f3 square free for his knight.
And he didn't even take it.
Well at least now knight f3 is available.
But in the other hand, now queen h4 is also a threat.
I mean g5 looks like it prevents it, but after f3,
I move my bishop away.
Qxg5 will be very dangerous, and also open up the queen h4 threat once again.
So I guess, let's just play normally.
Bg7.
There's no way he's going to play a weird move such as queen h4, right?
Okay guys. Talking about such topic may get my video demonetized.
So I guess, let's just end the video instead.
Thank you for watching.
[Music]