If someone moves a bishop, simp draws an elephant.
Okay so for anyone who doesn't know, the bishops are actually called elephants in Chinese chess.
And those pieces suck.
But anyway. We get a 2-94 from Uruguay.
Pushing a center pawn doesn't seem to be a great idea,
since it mostly provokes my opponent to do the same, which opens up his bishop's way.
Therefore, c4. I'm pretty sure he's just gonna play c5 and leave his bishops closed.
E6.
Alright. It's fine. Now the threats are bishop c5 and bishop b4,
because the other 2 moves look pretty stupid.
Therefore, a3. That will at least stop bishop b4.
And he should be able to see, that bishop c5 will immediately get kicked back by b4.
And not to mention that a lot of people just push their e-pawn to develop their queen.
Ha! I called it.
b4. Now bishop c5 is no longer a threat anymore, and since the other 2 moves are bad,
this entire bishop is basically no longer a threat.
f5. Wow! That is even better for me, since this bishop is basically crying from his home.
Nf3. It would be great if he can take this pawn instead of just retreating,
but horizontal moves tend to be a little bit hard to see.
Qg4. Ah ha! I guess we are a bit closer to our goal now.
h3.
Finally!
d3. The more you move your queen, the longer the video gets.
Ha! That is interesting.
Should I sacrifice my rook to keep him moving his queen,
or should I just take his queen and risk the chance of him moving his bishop?
I'll take his queen. I mean that rook is innocent, and just look at this bishop.
No way out, and this bishop just doesn't have any moves that make sense,
so it's also kinda no way out.
Yeah I should have sacrificed my rook.
And you know what the worst part is?
Bishop e7 is excellent.
Yeah I think that's good enough.
[Music]