If a pawn only moves one square in its first move, the video ends.
Okay then. Let's find an opponent.
We get a 163 from Germany.
E4. It's pretty obvious that there are 8 different ways that he can end my video right now.
But of course, there's nothing I can do about it.
E5. Thank God.
So in order to prevent my opponent from moving pawns one square, I need to keep him busy in every move.
The most popular move here is knight f3.
But sadly, he may decide to play d6, the Philidor defense, which ends the video.
D4 is also very risky because of d6, and f4 looks like it's really good, since everyone accepts the king's gambit.
But sadly, f4 allows queen h4 check, and since g6 ends the video, I will have to play king e2, which I don't like at all.
Therefore, b4.
Please just take it, that is a free pawn, and in no world do you play d6 now, which also blocks away your bishop's view.
Thank you. Let's continue to keep him busy.
Bishop a3. Of course you will take it, right?
Bishop c5. That blunders a bishop.
But should I even take it, though? Because if I take his bishop, he may decide to play d6 to attack my bishop, which ends the video.
Therefore, I guess I should play d4.
If his bishop is attacked, he cannot move his pawns.
Bishop e7. Ah ha! I think I can take it now. And in no world do you move your pawns now.
He takes d4. And he proves to me that he can still move his pawns. But anyway.
Bishop takes d8. Now just calm down, take my bishop, and everything is fine.
And do not move your c-pawn, just because my bishop is attacking it.
King takes d8.
And he resigned.
Mission accomplished.
[Music]