If a piece, not a pawn, lands on the G file,
S1mple goes clean the garbage,
playing 3 minute splits on a 100 rated account,
and apparently, this guy is a Dragon Ball fan,
remember this guys, remember, this.
Alright, let's find an opponent.
We get a 1-16 from Australia.
Ah ha! White pieces.
The most obvious threat is definitely G6 and BG7.
Therefore, B3.
If I can control the G7 square first, there's no more threat.
G6.
G6. Thank god I prepared for that.
Bb2.
Well of course he can still play Bb7,
but there's no way he cannot see that it's a huge blunder, right?
Nh6.
That blunders a rook.
But should I even take it though?
Because not only Bg7 is a threat,
but also Ng4.
Nah, it's fine.
Bxh8.
I mean no one plays such an absurd move like Ng4, right?
F6.
Yeah, that move makes sense.
But of course, I still need to prevent Ng4.
Therefore, H3.
Nf5.
Ah ha! He obviously want Bg7,
defended by the f5 horsey.
Therefore, E4.
Of course there's no such thing like Ng2-G3, right?
Nd6.
Perfect!
No more threats now.
Nc3.
Maybe it's finally time, for me to have, an absolutely normal chess game.
Nf7.
Ah ha! Now I understand what he wanted.
The knight started on H6,
to f5, to d6, and then to f7,
so that he can capture my bishop, which is trapped on H8.
And by the way, let's just totally ignore the fact that he can just go there,
in one f***ing move.
But anyway, let's just continue the game.
Bc4.
He took my bishop.
Alright.
Now Bg7 is unavoidable.
So I guess,
E5.
That was a pawn, but I need to distract him from playing that move.
f5.
Well, at least he got distracted.
But again, that move is still a threat.
G4.
Please take it.
Well at least just please push it like you did the last time.
Fxg4.
Qxg4.
That blunders a pawn.
Is he going to c?
d5, bishop b5 check, c6, queen d4, cxb5, e6, b4,
knight back to e2, queen b6, queen takes H8,
and finally, queen takes e6 winning a pawn.
(I'm not sure what I was doing here)
Okay, I'll clean up the garbage.