If Stockfish thinks that the game is balanced, the video ends.
First three moves don't count.
Disclaimer.
I only use Stockfish's evaluation after the game is already done,
which means I didn't use it during the game.
And with that out of the way, let's start the game.
We get a 100 rated from Mexico.
E4.
Sicilian.
Wow. I would love to have a Sicilian game with a 100 rated opponent,
but sadly, I'm actually making a video, so it's pretty much not possible.
Queen H5. Don't panic guys, I have a plan.
G5. That blunders a pawn, and as you can see, the evaluation went to 1.1 for me,
which is more than enough to continue playing normally.
But sadly, I didn't know that during the game.
Therefore, I went for the safe route.
Queen takes F7. Check.
King takes F7. My plan was to give him a free queen,
so that he's up a ton of material, and then I'll find a way
to shift the game from his advantage, straight towards a forced checkmate.
Bishop C4 check.
King back to E8. Oh wait. I have an idea.
Bishop back to E2. Can you see my idea guys?
Knight H6. And since my 100 rated opponent saw my idea,
I will assume that all of you guys did too.
D4. Since I already lost a queen, who cares about another pawn anyway?
Knight F5. And look at that E-val bar. But it's only been move 7 into the video,
which means the video is so short. Well who cares, bishop H5, checkmate.
And since the video is so short, I'll answer some of your comments instead.
That's not not even close, it almost ended your video.
Well, not even close. Imagine living in Asia and not knowing
what croissants and mukbangs are shake my head my head.
Well, I'm very sorry for that. What's an M? So in case you don't know
about it, I would prefer you totally not knowing
about it, and it's purely for your own goo- Oh wait he knew about it. Yikes.
[Music]