If the opponent rejects on croissant, simp does croissant mukbang.
I actually don't even know what a mukbang is, because apparently that is not English, so I think he just wants me to eat a croissant, but in fact, I have never seen a croissant in real life.
I actually didn't even know what a croissant is, until I see this challenge, and then I did some google search, which shows this, and it looks like some kind of food, but no offense, that looks absolutely boring, and bland.
A.F.
Therefore, let's rewrite this challenge so that it is a bit more seriously.
If my opponent rejects a non croissant, the video ends. Of course, I have to always give him a non croissant chance, if it's possible.
Let's go. We get a 2 1 5 from Russia. Hell yeah, this has to be my first ever Russian opponent.
E4.
So I can just play E5 and block his pawn from moving forward, which will just prevent on croissant from ever happening, but that seems like a dirty trick, so let's just make another rule, that I must not block his pawn's way.
Therefore, knight C6. A Russian will never play E5 in this situation.
Of course. Now C5 is the threat, since it forces me to play either D4 or B4, because the challenge requires so, and then he may going to decline the French move. Therefore, E6.
B3. Ah ha, he obviously wants to play bishop A3, which will help him play C5, and then potentially end my video. Therefore, B6.
Still bishop A3 anyway. Alright, I'll take it. I think I missed something about queen F3 back there. But who cares anyway.
Knight takes. Knight F6. I'm not gonna lie, this mission is actually going way better than what I imagined. What the hell was that?
That blunders a pawn. But I can't take it, because I have to give on passant chance. But of course he'll not take on passant, since my knight is much juicier.
Are you serious?
I can't trust the Russians anymore.
(music)