If my opponent moves his queen on an even-numbered move,
the video ends.
Playing 3-minute splits on a 100-rated account.
Okay. Even numbers suck.
Let's find an opponent.
We get a 1 0 8 from the U.S.
E4
E5
Still theory.
For those of you who don't know how the moves are numbered,
they are written right here.
Also, in this game, my opponent is playing black,
so his moves will be noted on the right-hand side.
And with that out of the way, let's continue the game.
The next move is an even-numbered move,
therefore, queen E7, queen F6, queen G5, and queen H4
are all threats to the video.
But sadly, there's no way I can prevent all of them from happening.
So I guess, knight F3.
At least I can stop two of them, right?
Bishop C5.
Thank you.
Even though the next move is not even-numbered,
I still think I need to work my way up to control more dangerous squares.
Therefore, D4.
E takes D4.
E5.
Now my E-pawn takes away the F6 square from his queen too,
and since queen E7 is such an absurd move to play,
I can say that this video is going to last really long.
D3.
That blunders a pawn.
H5.
Very aggressive.
But actually, I think that's pretty good for me.
Castle.
Since I have castled king side,
he now has even more reasons to push his pawn towards my king,
instead of moving his queen.
Right?
What the f-
[outro music]