If my opponent types in chat,
the video ends.
Well, normally, no one chats during a game of Blitz Chess.
But if we do this,
every time one of my pieces,
or pawns,
is taken,
I press F to pay respects.
If we combine these two rules,
the challenge is legit.
Playing 3 minute splits on a 100 rated account.
I have nothing else to say.
Let's find an opponent.
We get a 300 rated from the US.
E4.
E5.
Still theory.
Knight F3.
Knight F6.
The Russian opening.
So normally, I would take on E5,
but after D6,
Knight F3,
Knight takes E4 will force me to send an F in the chat,
which may cause my opponent to reply.
Therefore,
Knight C3.
Knight C6.
Bishop C4.
Bishop C5.
Such a peaceful game for a 100 rated match.
I'll castle.
Castle.
D3.
Knight G4.
Aha!
Here we go.
The first strange move of the game.
Bishop G5.
Bishop takes F2.
That's a big blunder.
He was probably thinking about danger levels.
If you attack my queen,
I attack your king.
But sadly,
things don't work like that.
After rook takes F2,
Knight takes F2 counterattacking my queen,
King takes F2.
If queen E8,
I will have Knight D5,
with an unstoppable family fork.
Or if after king takes F2,
Knight E7,
Knight D5,
F6,
there is knight takes F6 double check,
King H8 is forced,
knight back to D5,
and then he will still at least lose a rook to a bishop.
But of course,
before all of that going to happen,
F.
Rest in peace,
my F-pawn.
And let's just hope that my opponent won't reply to just a random F.
Rook takes F2.
Knight takes F2.
Of course I will take that horsey.
But once again,
I will take that horsey.
F.
I haven't even sent my second F yet.
What the f-
[outro music]