If your opponent can't check your king,
Not porn.
Oh, wait.
My bad.
If your opponent can't check your king,
The video ends.
Playing 3 minute splits on a 100 rated account.
Sounds easy.
All I have to do, is to always allow a check, but not really allow a check.
And with that out of the way, let's find an opponent.
We get a 135 from the US.
So it's kinda obvious that my opponent can never check me at move 1.
Therefore, let's say, the challenge only starts at move, 3.
E4.
Once again, this still doesn't count yet, because there is no other way.
And I'm not a coward.
E5.
Ah ha. Perfect.
F4.
There you go.
Even though I said the challenge starts at move 3,
I already gave him a check at move 2.
I'm such a generous man.
Nc6.
Nf3.
Even though I gave him a check, I still don't really like to be checked,
and since the challenge only requires that my king is always checkable,
I think this is the safest way to continue the game.
Nf6.
Ah ha. He's trying to block his queen's check, which is a big threat to my video.
Therefore, king e2.
Now there's another check right here.
The video, is safe.
He takes f4.
Nc3.
Nothing too crazy so far, except for the fact that I'm playing Bonk loud.
d6.
Ah ha.
He's trying to go Bg4, which looks like it pins my knight real hard to my king and queen.
But guess what? That's actually good for me, since he'll have another potential check.
So I guess, let's just ignore that.
d4.
Bg4.
I'll take a pawn.
Qe7.
Very aggressive.
But again, that's actually good for me, since he now has one more potential check.
Bg5.
d5.
Again, very, aggressive.
e5.
I want to close down the center, which may sound stupid because I need him to attack my king,
but since this guy is playing really aggressively, I don't think we have to worry about that.
Nxd4.
That blunders.
Wait.
If I take his knight, there will be one less piece attacking my king, which leaves more room for the video to end.
Nah.
I'm worrying too much.
That blunders a horsey.
h6.
I'll take.
gxh6.
Alright.
Now I think we need to think again about taking this bishop.
Well, who cares.
Qxg4.
As long as his queen is still alive, I think it's still fine.
fxe5.
Aha!
Once again, he's trying to block his queen's check.
Therefore,
king back to e1.
Now Qh4 is available, the video is once again safe.
e4.
That blunders a pawn.
Now even if he goes exf3, I will still take his queen, because even though his queen is dead,
his pawn on f3 will be the new check holder, not to mention about Bxc7.
Opening Bh4+ and Bb4+.
Qd6.
Ah!
So he didn't blunder his queen, which should be even better for me.
Qxc4+ check.
Oh, wait!
He can't check me in this position.
I'm so f***ing stupid!
Thanks for watching!