If my opponent plays a very aggressive move,
the video ends aggressively,
playing 3 minute splits on a 100 rated account.
Well, maybe you are wondering,
when do we consider a move as an aggressive one?
No worries, because I will be the judge of that.
If I think a move is very aggressive,
then it is very aggressive,
and if I don't, then it's not.
Very simple.
And with that out of the way,
let's find an opponent.
We get a 174 from Australia.
Ok, first move.
I think in order to prevent my opponent from playing aggressively,
I need to play even more aggressively.
E4.
E5.
Nothing special so far.
Knight f3.
Bishop c5.
That is a gambit.
And gambits can be considered as aggressive openings.
But still, I don't think this is too aggressive.
You know, like, it's kinda aggressive,
but not too aggressive, that makes me end my video.
Therefore, knight takes e5.
Accepting a gambit is an aggressive play,
but of course, this challenge only affects my opponent,
so it doesn't matter how crazy my play is.
Queen f6.
Very aggressive.
No.
I mean it looks kinda aggressive,
but it's not too aggressive.
I mean if he really wants to play aggressively,
he can just play queen h4,
forking my e-pawn and my f-pawn.
But instead, he chose queen f6,
which allows knight f3,
going back to safety.
And also keeps his queen from getting into too much trouble in the future.
So in conclusion,
I think that,
he played aggressively,
but he also didn't want to play too aggressively.
Which means,
the video,
survived.
d4.
This move is really aggressive,
but again,
who cares how I play anyway.
And the best thing is,
in this position,
he doesn't have any aggressive moves at all.
Well,
I mean he does have things like bishop takes d4,
or even queen takes f2 going absolutely crazy.
What the f