If Stockfish sees a 1.0 material advantage...
or more...
Simp goes fishing.
Yeah, Stockfish ends my video, but another fish has to die.
Disclaimer.
I only use Stockfish to analyze my game after it is already done, which means I didn't cheat during the game.
I know most people know about this, but I still want to say it out loud,
since there are always some haters who just want to ruin my video coming in and say,
"Oh you trash YouTuber you cheat during the game disliked unsubbed."
And with that out of the way, let's start the game.
We get a 219 from the US.
Man, that is like my 69th American opponent in a row, and chess.com has been invaded by the US.
But anyway, since I have to keep the game as balanced as possible, I think I have to go with a less aggressive opening.
d4.
Yeah, you see? White starts at +0.5 advantage, but after d4, it's just a dead... draw.
d5.
Still theory.
Bg4 is really scary, since it allows me to kick his bishop around, which may cause Stockfish to dislike it,
but a preventing move like f3 or h3 is even riskier, since I may end up ending my own video.
Therefore, let's just follow my own plan.
Bf4.
Wow.
0.00000000.
This video is definitely going to be long.
Nc6.
Aha, I was worrying that he might have played Bg4, but this is actually perfect.
e3.
Now Bg4 is no longer available.
At least I think so.
My god that was scary.
Nf3.
Now that you have developed your bishop, please don't move it again to pin my knight, since I'm pretty positive that it ends the video.
Well, I actually don't think we even need to check Stockfish about that move.
And since I'm being quarantined due to covid-19, let's just end the video instead.
Thanks for watching.