If a piece attacks 3 pieces, or pawns, at the same time, the video ends.
This is going to be short.
We get a 1 0 3 from the US.
So in order to prevent a real fork from happening, I strongly believe that I need to take, as
much center space, as possible.
E4.
E5.
Still theory.
Now queen H4 ends my video, since it attacks my E-pawn, my F-pawn, and my H-pawn.
Therefore, knight F3.
Knights are good, because even though they attack a lot of squares, their attack range
is very limited to their positions.
F6.
That blunders a pawn, but if I take it, there is a chance that he takes back with his pawn,
which blunders a rook to queen H5, but that move actually ends my video, so I cannot play
it, which means I'll be losing a knight, instead of him losing a rook.
Therefore, D4.
Knight C6.
Yes.
Another knight move, which is definitely good for the video.
And if you take a look at the board, there is absolutely no way for him to end my video
right now.
And he resigned.
Mission accomplished, but since the video is so short, I think I'll take this chance
to answer some of your comments in my videos.
I am so used to brilliant moves, I find them easily now.
Yeah you wish.
Nice chopsticks man.
Nice avatar man.
Hey, maybe if you ply your challenges against 1000s, you get better results.
That is absolutely correct, therefore I decided that I should play against the 100s, so that
they become unpredictably hard.
[Outro]