If your piece, not pawn, is a knight's distance away from your opponent's same piece, the video ends.
For example, if this position happens, the video ends.
Okay, so I guess, he means that, if two mentioned pieces are a square root of 5 distance from each other, the video ends.
You know, the Pythagorean theorem. Like, this is 1, this is 2, and this is square root of 1 squared plus 2 squared.
No? Oh well. Anyway. Playing 3 minute splits on a 100 rated account.
Alright. This shouldn't be too hard. But only if I can remain my focus on the game. And with that out of the way, let's find an opponent.
We get a 2 0 8 from the US.
E4.
E5. Still theory.
I really want to play knight F3, but after knight C6, there's a threat of knight D4, creating an L-shaped knight's distance, aka, a square root of 5 distance, with my knight.
So I will have to move my knight again to avoid that, which is obviously not good.
Therefore, knight C3.
Knight F6.
F4.
Vienna gambit.
There's no way he's taking my E-pawn. Right?
E takes F4.
E5.
There's no way he's playing knight E4 or knight D5. Right?
I mean there's obviously a safe square right here. Dude.
Why is he thinking for so long?
Queen E7.
Thank you.
Queen E2.
Since he saw those two squares are not available last time, there's no way he's playing these moves now. Right?
D6.
Yes.
That blunders a horsey.
G takes.
Oh, so he wants to keep his woman above him, instead of putting her above me.
That actually makes sense.
Knight F3.
Knight C6.
Ah ha! He's obviously trying to go knight D5, creating a square root of 5 distance with my knight.
Therefore, D4.
What the f-
[outro music]