100 rated chess, but you are playing Clash Royale. Every piece costs its value in elixir to move,
and you generate 2 elixir per turn. You start with 1 elixir. In case you don't know,
I don't even know what Clash Royale is. We get a 1 23 from the Philippines.
Knight f3. Well, since I only have 1 elixir. d5. d4. Ha, plus 2 baby.
But of course 2 points are still not enough to move a piece. c5. The game will become very
difficult if he gets to develop normally and I have to continuously push these pawns, so if he
can just advance his knight forward to create a tempo for me to push my pawn, that will be extremely
convenient. Well, extremely convenient. f6. Well I mean if he can also just leave his knight right
there and let me make another pawn move. Free horsey. f takes c5. I'll take this pawn. On
second thought, maybe that wasn't a great idea as now he'll have a reason to get his queen out,
which may end up really bad for me as I haven't stacked a lot of elixirs yet.
My bad. But anyway. Knight c6. I mean who knows, maybe he'll blunder that woman immediately after
getting her out. Even a paid actor wouldn't be playing like this. I'll take that woman.
Bishop e3. And in this very position, something unexpected happened. Unlike you guys, I didn't
have an elixir counter during the game, so I had to calculate everything inside my head while
playing the game at the same time, and in this very position, I lost my counting.
Ha. Nevermind. Mission accomplished, and two days ago, I posted a video with a small game inside of
it. For those of you who haven't watched this video, I would suggest you pause this video right
now and go to the link in the description to watch it yourself, and then come back to this video
later for the real answer. This is the polls result as of the moment of making this video,
and the real answer is, I was playing white,
and there is this one guy who absolutely scared me to death with his detailed explanation.
[Music]