I'm better than my viewers but it's this monstrosity.
Ha! Like I'm gonna be scared. Ladies and gentlemen and everyone else,
welcome to another episode of I'm better than my viewers, the series that I play against my viewers
and absolutely destroy them, and the victim this time is a guy called, RiaSaeBoy1. And don't judge
my pronunciation. Bishop takes rook takes bishop takes rook takes bishop takes, king a7 is laundering
bishop b6 rook b6 bishop b6 king b8 bishop a7 rook a7 bishop a7 checkmate in four. Therefore, king b8.
Bishop takes f4. That still blunders the queen. Rook g8. Bishop c8 rook g3 bishop 4g3 knight c8.
The grandmasters always say, knight on the rim is dim, but I didn't really have any choices.
Bishop a7 check. Knight takes. Bishop checks again. King c8. Rook h8 check. Blocking with the
knight should be better here, but things like bishop e6 totally lock down my king is actually
pretty concerning. So I guess, I'll block with my bishop. To be clear, I'm not a coward, I'm just
trying to play as humanly as possible. Rook f8. He wants to double up his rook, which is really
dangerous, therefore, rook a2. If I can't defend, I'll attack. Bishop e3. Okay. Here we go. d5.
I'm sorry Edward, but you need to die so that I can create some counterplay. Edward is dead. Rook
g6 check. I mean he can literally pull his bishop back and my attack will be stalled for at least a
few moves, but who knows, maybe he'll play king h3 and totally block down all of his rooks.
Well, very convenient. Knight e6. Bishop takes d5. That blunders a rook. Alright,
now let's try our best to get a draw. That escalated really quickly. Bishop d7 king h4
rook g4 king h3 rook f4 bishop e6 bishop e6. Checkmate. I'm better than my viewers.
[Music]