If your opponent moves a piece or pawn twice in a row, the video ends.
And you cannot make any sacrifices. This is going to be short. We get a 127 from Australia.
d4. d5 ends the video, therefore, d5 is kinda forced.
e4. Very aggressive. Now e5 or e takes d5 ends the video. So of course, d takes e4 is kinda forced.
Queen f3. Again, very aggressive. That blunders a woman. And I solemnly swear,
that this guy is not a paid actor. Or at least, I didn't pay him.
g takes f3. Aha! Here comes the hard part. Now f4 ends the video, but unlike the last few times
where I can absolutely prevent the move from happening, I cannot 100% prevent f4 in this
position. So I guess. Queen takes d4. He should be able to see, that f4 is just blundering queen
e4 check knight e2 queen takes h1 winning a rook. Right? Yeah, I think he saw it. There are too many
squares for this bishop to move to. Therefore, queen takes b2. I cannot prevent him from moving
his bishop, so I'm trying to focus his eyes into this corner of the board, and then forget about
his bishop. What the f*** was that? No. Now what am I supposed to do? Somehow I have a feeling that
he's already pre-moved king e3 or something. Well, I mean if the video has to end right now,
I guess there's nothing else I can do. e4. Oh wait. Ha! So he didn't pre-move like I was worrying.
What the f***?