100 rated chess, but every time your opponent blunders... a piece, not pawn.
You counter blunder back with the same valued piece.
This is going to be annoying. We get a 181 from Catalonia.
I actually have seen this idea multiple times, but even though it sounds really fun,
I just can't find a way to make it works.
E4. Well, if he doesn't blunder anything in the first place, I won't have to blunder back. Right?
Knight c6. Very solid.
D4.
E5.
D5.
Oh, wait. Maybe I shouldn't have attacked his knight.
Yeah I totally shouldn't have attacked his knight.
That blunders a horsey. But you know, since I can't really take his knight yet,
I don't have to blunder back. Right?
C3.
Knight b5.
Okay, now I can finally take his knight, so I have to blunder something back.
Bishop f4.
Now I guess after he takes my bishop, I can take his knight, and it's just a trade.
Or not.
Wow. Now what do I do?
You see, this is the problem of the challenge. Is that a blunder or not?
You know what? I will consider it as a blunder, because since he didn't retreat his knight,
he is still blundering his knight, which means I have to, still blundering my bishop.
Therefore, bishop take c5, just taking a free pawn, and by the way, that was actually a
brilliant move, so it's technically not a blunder. But you know, as long as I don't
play the line after that, it's not a brilliant move anymore.
F take c5.
Ah ha, now queen h5 check is obviously the best move, but since g6 blocking is blundering a rook,
and I cannot blunder my rook back, that move makes me a fool, for ending my own video.
Therefore, I'll take this knight instead.
Knight f6. Knight f3. Knight take c4, knight take c5.
A6. Ah ha. That once again, blunders a rook to queen h5 check g6 knight takes g6 h takes g6
queen takes h8. But again, I cannot blunder my rook back, so that move is not possible.
So I guess, queen f3.
H takes b5. That blunders a king, but I mean, I cannot blunder my king back.
Oh well.
[outro music]