It's December 10th, and according to Google, it's the...
No.
Aha! According to some other websites, it's the Human Rights Day.
And now I know that people support alcohol more than human rights.
But anyway, with that said, today's challenge is, if a porn dies, the video ends.
Because you know, nothing is cheaper than a porn, and Netflix actually even made a movie called,
"The Queen's Gambit", which is literally letting a porn die.
Writers move number 2.
Therefore today, I will fight for porn rights.
We get a 274 from India.
Since no porn is allowed to die, pushing porns is definitely not the smartest idea.
Night F3.
E5.
Ha! Just as I'm doing a challenge about saving the porns, he decided to sacrifice a porn, on his first move.
Gross Gambit.
B3.
Night F6.
That blunders this porn again.
But anyway,
Bishop B2.
Bishop C5.
That is still blundering that very porn, but this time, it's in two different ways.
This video is going very wrong very quickly.
H3.
Fun fact, when I analyze the game with Stockfish, it thinks that my last 3 moves are all mistakes,
due to the fact that I didn't take the free porn.
F*** you Stockfish.
Night E4.
Okay now things get serious.
He's obviously targeting my F porn, which is also a checkmate in 1.
And even though I really don't want to play it,
I guess I don't have any other choices.
E3.
Okay so I've seen a lot of people don't realize that this porn blocks away the Bishop's view,
but let's just hope, that this guy does.
What the f***?
[Outro]