100 rated chess, but you hate sharp objects, if any of your pieces, not pawns, are forked,
pinned, or skewered. The video ends. Ha, like I'm gonna let the 100 rated people do that to me.
We get a 194 from the United Kingdom. E4. E5. Still theory. D4. G6. Not very aggressive.
I'll take this pawn. C6. I want to develop this knight, but then he can go Bb4 pinning my knight
to my king, which ends the video, so I guess, Bc4. B6. This guy is just moving random pawns.
Knight F3. Bb4 check. Very aggressive. Blocking with a piece will make his bishop pinning my
piece into my king. Therefore, I have to block with a pawn. I mean technically speaking, he is
pinning my pawn into my king, but if you look at the challenge again, it only applies to pieces,
not pawns, so pinning a pawn is definitely not breaking the rules of the challenge.
Bc5. Bg5. I mean if he goes Qf6 right now, he'll be pinning my knight into my F pawn,
which ends the video because a knight is a piece, but since that move is obviously
blundering a woman, there's no way he's playing like that. Right? Of course. I'll take that pawn.
Still, in no world do you take with your queen here. Of course. But that blunders a horsey.
E5. Rf8. Ah ha, he moved his rook to avoid me taking his knight with my bishop which forks his
queen and his rook, which is to say, that at least he can see one move ahead of the current position.
I'll take this knight, since he can see ahead of the position,
I guess we can safely say that he won't just take this pawn carelessly.
[Music]