I'm better than my viewers, is this fair? Yeah, it's fair for white. Welcome to another episode
of I'm better than my viewers, and today's challenger is a guy called Shadownights297.
Bishop takes c5. Man, it's only been one move into the game, and I already don't know what to do.
Let's take it this way. Just like the grandmasters say, always capture toward the center. Bishop
takes c5. Again, capture toward the center. Bishop takes. It seems like he really hates the dark
square bishops. D takes. Huh. Guess what, now taking this pawn is not sacrificing the last
dark square bishop. Rook takes g5. G takes. Alright, inviting the first woman to come in.
Queen takes g5. F6. I think his best choice should be to take this pawn,
but does he have the guts to take it though?
Ha! Coward. c4. And I've just realized, that I've blundered g6.
Yeah. This game is so dead. Taking that bishop is just blundering queen g6 queen h5 checkmate in 2.
So I guess. F7. Bishop h5. G6. Alright, at least this will help for a while.
Nevermind. F takes g6. Bishop takes e6. Wow. He actually saw that by moving his bishop,
he opened up the way for his rook to pin this pawn to my king, so if I take his bishop now,
he can go queen g6 queen g1 queen g8 and there is no way I can stop it. So I guess, king g7.
Rook h7. I'll take that. Not sure about that one man. Queen g1. Ah ha, now I can take this bishop.
Bishop g5. Alright, so in this very position, I realized that there is no way I can win anymore,
so I offered a draw, and of course, he accepted it. So I guess. I'm better than my viewers.
[Music]