100 rated chess, but your king is paranoid, he needs Edward, Frank and the queen as his bodyguards,
they all must always be within one square from the king. I normally don't take on super easy
challenges like this one, but since anime profile pictures are good for thumbnail clickbaits,
this one gets a priority. D4, for those of you guys who don't know, this is Edward, this is Frank,
and you probably already knew about the queen, and these 3 pieces need to always be next to the king.
D5, bishop F4, nothing suits D4 openings more than the London system, and don't you mention
any movies here. Knight C6, aha, against knight C6, I usually like to go, C4. D takes C4. D5, oh,
wait. I think this entire idea of C4 D C4 D5 is actually a mistake, because now he has knight B4,
which threatens knight C2 check, and if I take his knight, my queen violates the rules,
or if I move my king, Frank will no longer be touching the king, which also ends the video.
Yeah, this is really bad. I mean he should be able to see that knight C2 is blundering a horsey,
but of course I won't take any risks this time. Knight A3. Alright, now queen takes D5 is also a
big problem because she'll be starting a fight against my woman, but he should be able to see
that it will blunder a horsey to queen A4 check with a fork. Right? Actually, I just realized
that after queen A4 bishop D7 queen takes B4, he also has E5 double attacks on my queen and my
bishop, and maybe this guy actually did all the calculations even faster than me before taking
my D pawn. But anyway, I need to stop the women's war. In no world do you go queen takes G2 here
because my bishop cannot take your queen. Of course, that blunders a pawn. Ha, now everything
is fine, he cannot take my G pawn when his knight is being attacked, and since knight D3 is obviously
a huge blunder.
F*CK!