100 rated chess, but you move your king until you're put in check.
Ha! Another easy challenge. We get a 100 rated from Argentina, and even though he actually has
a proper profile picture, I have to hide it away due to various reasons. E4. Well, even though I
have to move my king right now, that is obviously against the game's laws, therefore, E5. I mean he
still has queen H5 king E7 queen takes E5 checkmate, so if he really plays queen H5 right now, I think
I will have to flex and delay moving my king for another move. Ha! Here we go. King E7 is forced.
Testosterone. Queen H5. Very aggressive. King back to E8 is blundering checkmate in 1, king F6 is
also blundering queen F5 check king back to E7 queen takes E5 checkmate. Therefore, king D6 is
kinda forced. I mean if he can just blunder his queen with a check like this, it would be very
convenient. Of course it doesn't happen. Okay. Now what am I supposed to do? King C5 is blundering
checkmate in 2, and king C6 is actually also blundering the same checkmate in 2.
I mean king C6 is allowing a bishop check instead of queen check, which will be really good for me.
Nevermind. Wow. King B6 is forced. It's fine, as long as he doesn't see queen B5.
Well since the video is still so short, I will answer some of your comments instead.
Why don't we see the actual resignation? The game was played on a different platform from what we
usually use for a normal chess game, so I allowed my opponents to resign through a chat message.
What food do you like? I like peanuts, and hate carrots. I'm surprised trying to control the
center wasn't one of them, if it was this would have become a lot harder. Actually it was, but I
really did not see it that day, so let's just pretend that I did not break the rules.
[Music]