100 rated chess, but your opponent's pawns caught covid. If a piece, or pawn, is next to a pawn,
it can't move anymore. Very challenging. We get a 1 17 from India. With diamond membership.
Pushing center pawns only provokes him to push his pawns back, which freezes my pawns. Therefore,
knight f3. At least I can prevent e5. Maybe not. That blunders a pawn, but do I even take it,
though? If I take his pawn, d6 will attack my knight, and since my knight is next to his d-pawn,
I cannot move it away, which means I'll lose a horsey. So I guess, I'm not gonna be greedy.
E4. On second thought, maybe it doesn't matter whether my pawns are frozen or not,
it's just about the pieces. Queen e7. Very aggressive. d4. Let's be hyper-aggressive and
win this game fast, because my king is obviously useless in the endgame, where he cannot capture
any pawns due to the rules. d5. Again, very aggressive. d takes e4 will freeze my knight,
and thus winning it in the next move. Therefore, knight d2. d takes d4. Ah ha, I want to take this
pawn back, but that may provoke c5, which freezes my knight and win it. So I guess, c4. I mean d
takes e4 wins this knight, but there's nothing I can do about it anymore. And in fact, losing a
knight like that is not too bad, when I can get rid of his center pawn. Queen c5. Knight b3. Now
don't tell me that he's gonna take right here to freeze my knight instead of moving his queen.
Of course. That blunders a woman. Ha! Now the mission is much easier. d takes c4. Knight takes
d4. In this position, my knight on d4 is frozen, but after he takes my knight, I can move this
knight again, and then he doesn't have any center pawns anymore. Or he can just resign. Mission
accomplished.
[Music]