[Music]
You're a stupid child
You chased your dreams and got hurt
You're bad at lying
But you showed me a smile that couldn't be laughed at
You're bad at saying "I love you"
You're really clumsy
But, but why
Did you say "goodbye"?
You're no good, no good, no good
I love you, I love you too much
No matter how much I drink
My memories don't change
You're a stupid child
You're a stupid child, really stupid
You only believe
You pretend to be a strong woman
You bathe in the night wind of sadness
Three years have passed since you became alone
You even changed the cityscape
You left behind the city of tears
You're a really bad man
I'll take off your ring
I'll make you pay for it
I'm waiting for you
You're a stupid child
(epic fanfare music)