100 rated chess, but your pawns refuse to move unless when their lives are at risk.
This sounds very cowardly, but since it is not about me, I'll do it for the video.
We get a 198 from Brazil.
And as you can see, none of the pawns are at risk right now, therefore, I have to move
a horsey.
D5.
Again, still no pawns being threatened.
Knight c3.
I mean if he pushes d4 to attack my knight, I would gladly let him take it just to open
up the way for the other pieces to move out.
c6.
Not very aggressive.
Knight b1.
Well I mean at least after he develops his bishop, my c-pawn will be at risk of losing
his life, which then allows me to play like a normal person.
Or he can just absolutely block away his bishop's way.
Knight c3.
Well, at least I know this video is going to be very long.
E5.
Very aggressive.
Knight g1.
I mean moving the queen out will definitely help me a lot.
And again, he decided to block away his queen instead.
Knight b1.
My position is absolutely wonderful.
D4.
Ah ha, even though I said that I would sacrifice a knight just to open up my position, now
when I rethink about that idea, it sounds like what a coward would do to avoid the challenge's
difficulty.
Therefore, knight f3.
No need for any sacrifices, I will win this game fair and square.
c5.
Knight a3.
Man, I've just realized that I should've played knight a3 sooner so that he can take my knight
which attacks my pawn and allows me to open up my position.
E4.
Knight g1.
That's fine, knight h3 next, and there's no way he's not taking it.
Knight e5.
Here we go.
Knight h3.
Alright, take this horsey, and we'll officially start the game.
Knight f3 check.
Wait.
I didn't even see that.
That blunders a horsey, but since none of these pawns are being threatened, I cannot
move them according to the rules.
And my king is stuck.
So basically this is a checkmate.
What the f-
*outro music*