100 rated chess, but the royal couple and the peasants must stay together, the king and queen
always have to be touching, and all the pawns also always have to be touching. I personally don't
think this is very interesting, but since a lot of people reacted to this one, maybe there is
something that I'm missing. We get a 168 from Spain. E4. Since the pawns have to stick together,
I think I will delay pushing center pawns for now. B6. D4. Bishop B7, expecting knight F3 and I win
a free pawn. Well, that works too, expecting queen D3 blundering a queen. Of course that doesn't
happen. G6, I mean a move like bishop takes C7 will end my video because it disconnects my remaining
pawns, but I mean who plays like that anyway. Right? Of course. I'll go back. Queen D3. Aha!
As soon as my bishop doesn't control the D3 square anymore, he moves his queen to D3 immediately.
Which is to say, very aggressive. Bishop G7. Queen E4. That blunders a woman. Wow,
this challenge is going way better that what I imagined. Knight takes E4. D6. Knight 2 C3. Knight
D7. Oh wait I missed a free pawn. Nevermind. I'll take that pawn now, and he should be able to see
that knight takes C7 is just blundering a horsey. Right? Yes. These 3 pieces are scaring me to
death right now, therefore, let's try to trade some of them down. Please just don't go crazy
and take any of these pawns, because if there is just 1 pawn being taken away, the rest of the
pawns will be disconnected, except if that pawn was Hikaru, or Anish. Bishop trade. E takes is
just ending my own video, therefore, knight takes is kinda forced. And even better, now it's very
clear that my queen is defending both of these pawns. What the f-
[Music]