100 rated chess, but you must promote 7 pawns into queens.
Well, I'm pretty sure some of them won't want to change their gender,
but of course, I make the decision here. We get a 183 from India. So the best plan is obviously to
not push any pawns forward to avoid them dead, but sadly, I'm not a coward. If I lose, I lose.
D6. Not very aggressive. D4. Alright, these are the only 2 pawns that I'm gonna push.
If these guys die, I won't have enough 7 pawns to promote, which means the video ends.
Queen D7. Dude, I can't believe he actually pushed his pawn just to create a square for
his queen to move forward. Bishop C4. Knight F6. Dude. Somehow this guy decided to lift his queen
up, and then just leave her there blocking his bishop. Knight C3. In no world do you take Edward
right now. Of course. Knight F3. Bishop E7. D5. I mean C6 will create a lot of trouble,
but it's not like he's gonna play it anytime soon. Nevermind. Alright. I have to take it.
It's fine, I still have enough pawns for this game. David is dead. Man. Maybe the entire idea
of pushing pawns forward was a massive disaster. Queen E2. Alright, change of plan. All, eyes,
on, Edward, and at least with this plan, I can keep him alive for a couple more moves.
Well. Even though I have to end the video right now, since it is still so short, I'll answer some
of your comments instead. Never overestimate 200 elo. But if I underestimate them, the people in
the comments are gonna go like, "How dare you disrespect your opponent?" "Everyone deserves
to be respected, disliked and subbed reported to YouTube." "Sir, you just have no idea how tough it
is to be a YouTuber." "Bad video, you should've reverted to the original challenge if you failed
because you increased the difficulty yourself." "Aha, you must be new to the channel, let's just
say. I'm not a coward." "Why do you still not know how to checkmate with bishop and knight?
Surely it can't be that hard." Well.
[Music]