It is the United States National Guy Day, and as a real man that is arguably a lot more manly than my viewers.
100 rated chess, but the women don't move.
You may want to ask why am I taking on such an impossible challenge like this, and the answer is obviously...
Testosterone. We get a 133 from France.
E4. Queen h5 is very likely happening next, so at least I'll try to prevent it.
I mean he still has queen f3, but a lot of people don't tend to do that very often.
Bishop c4.
Ah ha. Now the queen f3 threat is even more obvious than before, therefore I have no other choice, but to sacrifice this pawn.
Why is he thinking for so long?
Ha! Doubters.
Bishop b7. I mean queen f3 is also an option to defend his e-pawn, but who puts their queen straight into enemy bishop's attack anyway.
Right?
This guy is very strong.
Knight f6. Some people may say that this is a bad move as it provokes queen e2, but I do have faith that he's not gonna make such an unhuman move.
Right?
Of course. But that blunders a pawn.
Knight takes e4. Bishop takes e4.
Ha! Now I have completely stopped the queen f3 threat, and even better, he actually cannot make a queen move in this position without blundering his rook,
and after knight f3 or pawn f3, his queen will be boxed inside his territory, and the video shall continue for a very long time.
What the f-
[Music]