100 rated chess, but you have high ping, your pieces and pawns must see a capture 1 move
before they can deliver it. I have ping, but my pieces suffer. We get a 100 rated guy from India.
E4. E5. This challenge will become absolutely impossible in the late game,
therefore, I'll try to end it quickly. Knight F6. Aha, my queen saw the pawn last move already,
so I can take it now. Bishop E7. D4. Knight takes D4. That blunders a horsey, but my queen didn't
see that capture before, and that also blunders this pawn, but my queen also did not see that
before. So I guess, bishop D3. Knight C5. That blunders this knight again, and again I cannot
take it. But I can take this pawn. Knight takes D3. I still cannot take that knight according to
the rules, king D2. Let's hope that he'll move his knight and blunder his rook. Of course that
doesn't happen. Queen G3. Knight takes E1. Again, my king didn't see this capture before. Knight C3.
Quite frankly, f*** this horsey. Knight E2. Still cannot capture, but this time, queen E3 check.
King F8. Ha, after all that time. Dead. Knight C6. Knight F3. Queen E8. I cannot take his queen
due to the rules, and if I keep my queen here, he'll capture and I actually cannot take back
also due to the rules. So I'm. D5. That blunders a pawn, but the rules. Bishop E7. Now I can
take it. Rook G8. I don't care about that pawn. Rook E1. H6. Knight E4. Bishop G4. That blunders
a triple fork. Knight F6. Unless he decides to take my knight which turns out that I blundered
my knight because my rook cannot take his queen due to the rules. H3. Well at least after he moves
his queen, I can take his bishop. That is even better. Rook takes king takes queen takes. Bishop
takes D4. Rook E1 check. King D8. My king feels a bit uneasy. I'll hide him away. And I'm not a
coward. Knight E5. That blunders a bishop. Queen D5 knight D7 queen D4. King C8. Rook E7. Rook takes
G2. That blunders a king. Queen down king over rook down. Checkmate. Mission accomplished.
[Music]