100 rated chess, but you reveal the challenge after 6 moves. I don't know why he picked the
number 6 instead of 5 or 7, but I'll respect his personal hobby. E4. I have no idea what the
challenge is, so as usual, we'll just play the game normally until move 6 and then see what
will happen. E5. D4. Knight F6. D5 knight E4 queen E2 is definitely the best continuation,
but since I only have 6 moves to play the game freely, I don't want to spend the majority of
them on pawns and queen, so I guess, bishop G5. H6. Bishop H4. On second thought, maybe I should
have taken his knight instead of wasting a move on retreating my bishop. G5. Very aggressive.
I'll take this pawn. Knight takes E4. Ah ha, now I believe we need to counter-attacking the knight
has to be the best move, but doing that will create too many tactics on the board, which is
probably not a very good idea when I'm about to unveil the challenge. So I guess, bishop G3.
D6. Alright, let's see what's under this black thingy.
If X pawns were captured, including enemy ones, every X move must be king. And since there are
2 pawns die before the challenge begins, therefore, X equals 2. Bishop C4. I mean it will be very
problematic if he takes my bishop right now because I cannot take his knight back due to the rules,
but since he didn't take it last time, there is no reason to do that right now especially
after he's just created a war between the pawns here. Right? Well, at least now no one will call
this guy a paid actor. King D2 is f***ing forced. Knight takes H1. You know what, this game is going
very wrong very quickly, so why not try a chance. Knight takes F2. Ah ha, that blunders a king,
but since the challenge forces me to move my king right now, king back to E1. I mean since
he's blundered his king once, he'll definitely blunder his king twice. Right? Absolutely.
Queen takes F7. Checkmate. Mission accomplished.
[Music]