100 rated chess, but you reveal the challenge after one move.
That move will be very important. We get a 145 from Ukraine,
and even though I'm very sorry about your situation over there and I hope you're safe with all my
heart, I still have to beat you up in this game for the video's sake.
D4. The first move will decide my fate for this entire video,
but since I have absolutely no idea what the challenge is, I guess let's just try to open up
the center. E5. Alright, let's see what kind of disaster is going to happen.
Whichever piece or pawn you moved has to be alive for the entire game,
you can't let it die at all costs.
Wow.
Oh my f***ing god that was so f***ing scary holy f*** I can't believe I f***ing survived that f***.
E4. I mean the situation is still pretty much a massive disaster as my e-pawn has now arrived in
his half the board, but this is obviously still better than ending the video on move 2.
Knight D2. D5. Since he didn't take it last time when it was free,
there's no way he's taking it right now when it is defended. Right?
No doubt. E3 is kinda forced, in no world do you play knight E4 here just to prevent my queen from
defending my pawn and after I take your knight you decide to immediately take my pawn just before I
can move my queen to defend it. No doubt. Qg5. H4 blundering Qg3 checkmate in 1 will be very
convenient. Sadly he's not a paid actor. That blunders a horsey because she takes H3 is
blundering Qh4 checkmate in 1, but since it's only been 6 moves into the game, I don't want
to end this video too early. So I guess, Qh6, just because I've moved my queen, doesn't mean I'm not
defending my pawn anymore. Knight back to G1. Knight D2 knight B1, knight H3 knight G1. Maybe
this guy is Magnus Carlsen. Bd6. C4. Ah ha, that once again blunders Qh4 G3 Qg3 brilliant move Hg3
bishop G3 checkmate in 3, but again, I don't want this video to end too early. Bishop G3 check.
H takes G3 is forced. Queen takes H1. And I've just realized, that bishop takes E3 is defending
this knight that I'm attacking. Now I feel like a paid actor. Ha! Nevermind. I'll take it this time.
G takes. Queen G1. My god that looks like a mouse slip. Queen F2. Checkmate. Mission accomplished.
[Music]