100 rated chess, but every 5 turns you offer a draw. If the opponent accepts, you lose.
Too easy. We get a 2 0 7 from Naru.
E4. So to make him not accepting my draw offer, I obviously need to give him some advantages.
B5. Ha, now after he takes my pawn, he'll have 1 point of material advantage,
which will massively decrease the chance that he'll accept the draw offer.
E5. Alright, I'm literally blundering 2 pawns at the same time,
so if he doesn't take one of them, I'm down to just never play chess again.
Of course. Knight F6. Take this one too please. Maybe later.
Knight C6. Alright, I'll have to offer a draw next move. So please, just don't make a blunder
right now. Are you serious? Alright. I have an idea. Draw offer. I want to take that knight,
but if I do that right now, he will definitely accept the draw offer, which ends the video.
Therefore, I'll sit here and wait for him to decline the offer first, and then I'll take that knight.
Aha! He declined it. Now that blunders a horsey. I mean if he can just resign right now feeling
bad about blundering a piece and declining a draw offer. That will be very convenient.
Of course that doesn't happen. I'll take this pawn. Alright, I'm giving you back the horsey,
just take it and don't accept the next draw. Or not. Knight D3. Okay now please take it.
If he doesn't take it this time, I have no idea what to do after this.
Thank you. Knight F6. Since he was the one who makes the last capture, his fighting spirit must
be very high right now, so I'll say that we don't have to blunder anything more until move number
10. Queen E3 check. Bishop blocks. Alright, once again, please don't blunder right before the draw
offer. Good. Draw offer. And to make him not accept this draw. Rook B8. He should be able to see,
that now he actually has bishop takes E7 brilliant move knight D5 bishop D8 knight E3 bishop E7
knight C2 knight C3 knight E1 rook E1 winning two pieces for a rook. Right?
What the f-
[Music]