[Music]
You're a stupid child
You chase your dreams and get hurt
You're bad at lying
But you show me a smile that doesn't make me laugh
You're bad at saying "I love you"
You're really clumsy
But why did you say "goodbye"?
You're no good, no good, no good
You're too dark and too innocent
No matter how strong the alcohol
Memories that don't waver
You're a stupid child
You're a stupid child, really stupid
You just believe
You pretend to be a strong woman
And bathe in the night wind of sadness
Three years have passed since you became alone
Even the cityscape has changed
You left only regrets in the window
You're a really bad man
I'll take off your ring
I'll make a fuss
I'm waiting for you
You're a stupid child
[Music]
You're no good, no good, no good
You're too dark and too innocent
No matter how strong the alcohol