You are white? And I'll be honest, that doesn't look good for me. Welcome to episode 6 of I'm
Better Than My Viewers, and the challenger this time is a guy called Le... Totoro. Man,
I have absolutely no idea how to make the text-to-speech engine to read that name correctly.
And in fact, even I don't know how to read that name correctly. But anyway, the most obvious
threat now is like knight f3 king moves bishop c6 checkmate, or knight f3 knight f6 checkmate,
or bishop f6 bishop c6 checkmate, or knight c6 knight f6 checkmate, or so any other combinations.
But the entire point is that it is very easy to take over all of these 4 squares around my king,
which will result in a checkmate. Therefore, E takes f7 is kinda forced. That is the only
move that gives my king a free square to move, and even though I'm sure that was the best move,
there is still a checkmate in 5 for black in this position, so if you are interested,
feel free to pause the video and find it, but the point is that my opponent is currently 1470 rapid,
and his peak was 1600, which is to say he is not like any other people I have faced before,
and starting a game at checkmate in 5 for him is probably not the way I want to do this.
Knight g7. Ah ha, that move blocked away the only getaway square that my king has,
therefore, I have to create another one. C pawn changed gender. Ah ha, the evaluation bar moved
from mate in 5 to there is no checkmates anymore. I'll take his queen, and never mind,
that was a bad move, there is another checkmate on the board. And then there is no checkmate again.
Taking this bishop is just asking to be royal fought, and even though I have a rook that kill
the guy, I don't want to live so passive like that, therefore, c8 changes gender. Dude, it's
like every move I make is just blundering a checkmate of some sort, so I'm not gonna care
about it anymore. Knight c6 check. Rook takes. Bishop takes. F pawn changes gender, and I've
blundered checkmate again, and he's missed checkmate again. Rook takes king takes queen
takes -26, that is actually the best case scenario I have ever been in this entire game,
that means I'm making progress, and I'm only down 7 points of materials right now.
Knight check. D takes, okay now it's 5, and only -20, so I have faith that I can turn this around,
unless he pushes one of these pawns to make another queen. This is really bad. I only had 4
rooks at the beginning, but he has 4 pawns that is very close to changing gender. Queen h1 check.
I have to trade down a queen, can't let him have 2 queens when my king is so strong in the middle
of the board like this. King f2, queen takes c1. B pawn changes gender. Taking this knight is
blundering a queen, therefore, I can only take this bishop, and then from this point, the game
continues for a few more moves, and in this position, something unexpected happened. I found
out that taking this knight is blundering my queen just like before, so I see that there is nothing
else I can do, and he can still make another queen very very soon, therefore, I did the thing that
everyone would do at this point, which is, offering a draw. And funny enough, he accepted it, game
drawn by agreement, not paid actor, and I'm still better than my viewers.
[Music]