100 rated chess, but your pieces can only move one square when they are attacked.
This obviously sounds too easy, so let's just say, that my opponent's pieces can see through
everything. Now it's a bit more challenging. We get a 163 from the US. E4. My e-pawn is not being
attacked by anything, therefore, E5. Alright, now queen h5 will be very dangerous because she's
gonna see a ton of my pieces. But who develops their queen first anyway? Right?
Knight c6. It's fine, it's not like a lonely queen is gonna destroy my video or anything.
Bishop c4. G6. Queen g5. Aha, that blunders a queen, but since his queen is also attacking my
queen, my queen can only move one square due to the rules, so I actually cannot take it. Bishop g7
then. Knight f3. I really want to develop this knight, but since his bishop is attacking it,
the knight can only move one square, which is not possible, so I guess, d6. Knight takes e5.
That blunders the woman again, but sadly, I have to take the knight instead. Bishop d5.
That once again blunders the same woman, and to be honest, since I cannot take it anyway,
I'd rather kick it away. Alright, now queen takes e5 will be very problematic because since his
queen will be attacking my bishop, I cannot move it 2 squares, his bishop is attacking my knight,
so my knight also cannot capture, which means I'll have to move my king, but who plays like
that anyway? Right? Right? Ha. Of course, but since the video is still so short, once again,
I'll answer some of your comments. This is like anti-chess, it's unfun, and you almost never get
to make any interesting decisions. Well, I'm sorry you're disappointed. Despite check to end the
video, simp has more evidence that his opponents aren't paid actors now. Finally. Someone has
finally stood by my side, if you were a girl, I would have asked you out for a date. Don't tell
my girlfriend.