100 rated chess, but it's rushy. You may only play moves to and from the E-file.
Very difficult, but nothing is impossible. We get a 100 rated Brazilian.
E4. A move that is from the E-file and also to the E-file, is definitely following the rules.
E5. I mean he doesn't have to follow the rules, but I respect it.
Bishop E2. I actually wanted bishop C4, but as bishop from F1 to C4 is not connecting with the
E-file, I need to move him to E2 first, and then continue from E2 to C4. Knight C6. Bishop C4.
D6. Since I obviously cannot move any pawns, now I can only choose to move something between my
queen and my knight. And I'll choose my queen. Queen E7. I wanted to go queen F3 aiming for a
scholar checkmate, but since his queen is already defending his F-pawn. Queen E3 instead. Since I
can only use my light bishop, my queen will help with controlling the dark squares. Bishop E6.
Ah ha. I can take his bishop as it is standing on the E-file, but as I only have so many pieces
to play with. Trading is definitely not a good idea. King D8. Ha. I bet that was a failed attempt
to castle his king, so even though I really want to castle right now to flex that I can play the
move. Bishop F3 first. I need to move my knight first, and then when I can finally show him the
proper way to castle, he'll probably cry while realizing that I'm actually much better than him,
and then decide to run away with a resignation. Or I don't even have to do that.
This guy was so mad at the fact that he cannot perform the move, so he resigned.
But anyway, mission accomplished.
[Music]