100 rated chess, but your queen is cheating, she must always be closer to the enemy king than your own.
Net or air is never my favorite choice of anime, but chess is a different story.
We get an exact 100 rated guy from America.
D4. There is no way I can move my queen away from my king at the moment,
so let's just say, that the challenge starts at move 2.
E5. Opening up the way for the queen to leave her husband, and please don't play G3 here.
Thank you.
Qh4. Alright, now the challenge truly begins.
My queen is now 5 squares away from my king, but only a square root of 18 away from the enemy king,
which means she is obviously cheating.
Qd5. Very aggressive.
Ne7. I mean he should be able to see, that my knight is attacking his queen in an extremely obvious way,
so a move like Kd1 making the distances between my queen to both kings equal which ends the video can not be played at the moment.
Right?
Wow.
Even I didn't see that coming.
If I take his queen, that will reduce the distance from my queen to my king down to only square root of 13,
which is shorter than square root of 18, which makes me a fool for ending my own video.
Therefore, Kd8 is kinda forced.
Square root of 32, square root of 18, but I can already see, that this video is going to be short.
Qe8 check.
Ha! Guess what, even if I take that queen, that won't end the video.
And still, in no world do you go Kd1 here.
No world, including this one.
No doubt.
But you know what, just to be safe, Kd8.
This way, I will never have to worry about Kd1 again.
And no, I'm not a coward.
Bd3.
D6.
Let's just open up the center and checkmate him real fast before something crazy happens.
Like that one.
That blunders a bishop.
C4.
Centralizing my queen will only make her a bigger target to be attacked,
which may reduce the number of safe squares far away from my king,
so I guess, I'll take this pawn instead.
Nc3.
Nbc6.
Game abandoned.
Mission accomplished.
[outro music]