100 rated chess, but the opponent's king is in love with their queen very much,
their queen must never leave their king's side. It's been a long time since I last
take on a luck-based challenge, so why not try our luck today.
E4. Ah ha, that opens up the queen's way, which is very dangerous for the video, therefore,
B5. I'm sacrificing this pawn to make him move his bishop instead of his queen,
which is by the way, the distraction strategy. Or he can also not move the queen and not take
the pawn at the same time. That horsey already blocks the queen's way to end the video,
therefore, I guess I'll keep this pawn. Knight C3, bishop B7. D4. Ah ha, that opens up queen D3
ending the video, so I guess, B4. I mean if I attack his knight, he won't have time to move
his queen. Right? Of course. E6. Again, I'm attacking his knight, no worries about the video.
Knight takes B4. That blunders a horsey, but do I even take it though, because if I take it,
he'll most likely place E3 to block the check, which opens up this very dangerous diagonal for
his queen to end the video. Well, as always, I'm not a coward. I mean who knows, maybe he'll block
with his bishop instead and his queen can never even go to D3 to end the video. Nevermind. Pulling
this way is only provoking queen A4, so I have to go this way. Bishop G5. That blunders a horsey.
Bishop takes knight takes queen takes. Please resign. F3. You know what? I have an idea.
Queen E3 check. Alright, please block with your woman. Perfect. Of course I cannot trade queens
because his queen in heaven cannot be considered as by his king's side. Queen back to G5. My plan
is very simple, I made him move his queen once, so it will reduce the chance that he'll move his
queen again to end the video, because as the grandmasters always say, don't move a piece too
many times in a row. What the f-
[Music]