100 rated chess, but you actually play against someone your level.
Very clear and simple. I normally play E4 against people at the 100 rated era,
but in a more serious game, I tend to play D4. Knight C6. Meichner's defense,
I'll take the full center. E5. D takes knight takes F4. Knight G6. Aha,
he's provoking F5 which blunders a pawn to queen H4 G3 queen E4 queen E2 queen E2 bishop E2 knight
6 E7 therefore. Knight F3. The situation is actually very good for me as his knight is
very limited in places that it can land, nevermind. That blunders a horsey. Well you know,
even though this is my real level chess, people still blunder their horses every now and then.
Bishop check. C3. Very good move as it stops my knight from being developed normally.
Bishop D6. Aha. He's probably thinking that my bishop is too strong, so he decided to sacrifice
a pawn to trade off my strong bishop, bishop takes pawn takes queen takes. Knight F6. He's
provoking a pawn push, and since I don't know what plan he's having in his mind,
let's just avoid it for now. Queen E7. Aha. He wants to trade queens so that we'll head into
an endgame with his king on a very strong dark square and I only have a light square bishop that
cannot attack his king. So I guess, E5 instead. At least this will force him to make a queen trade
himself. Well you know, even at my real level, people still blunder their queen every now and
then. Resignation. The challenge didn't require me to reveal my rating, so I'll answer some
comments instead. Please put a stop to these easy challenges. But I lost. You know what?
I changed my mind.
So,
you.