If a piece, not a pawn, lands on the F file,
Simp says what the F*CK, playing 3 minute splits on a 100 rated account.
Also, the starting position, doesn't count.
Right.
I believe this video is going to be unbelievably short.
But still, I kinda ran out of ideas.
Therefore, let's find an opponent.
We get a 1 56 from India.
Great.
An impossible challenge.
And an impossible opponent.
This should have been a chess impossible episode.
But anyway.
First move, it's kinda obvious that knight F3 is the biggest threat.
But of course, there's nothing I can do about it.
You know, since he moves first.
Therefore, let's just sit here and wait for my destiny.
E3.
Not very aggressive.
And of course, knight F3 is still the biggest threat.
I mean queen F3 is also a threat.
But you know, who the hell moves their queen first anyway.
So I guess, D4.
I'm planning to go bishop H3.
Sacrificing my bishop to deflect his knight away from the F file.
Knight C3.
Thank you.
Bishop H3.
Of course he'll take this way right?
Man.
The video hasn't even reached 2 minutes yet.
And since this video is so short.
I think maybe I should reveal my real voice, saying what the F*CK.
Okay, on second thought.
Maybe it's not the time yet.
So I guess.
What the F*CK.
[outro music]