100 rated chess, but your viewers think you use paid actors. To prove them wrong, you must finish
the game before the opponent blunders a total of 10 points of materials. Finally, after all that
time, someone finally allows me to play the game, like a normal person. We get a 168 from Poland.
E4. E5. Queen H5. The plan is very simple. Since I cannot let my opponent blunders 10 points of
materials, the best plan is obviously to quickly checkmate his king before he can end my video.
Knight F6. Ah ha, that blunders a pawn, so it is now 1 point out of 10. Queen takes E5. It's fine,
we still have 9 more points to spend, and if he can just block with the queen right now to allow
a queen trade, that will definitely prevent a queen blunder from happening in the future.
And then he decided to block with a bishop. Bishop C4. It's fine, at least with my queen
in the middle of the board, he'll get scared and not play risky to blunder too many things.
D6. Queen G3. Alright, now knight E4 queen G7 is absolutely amazing because that is just a
pawn trade, which does not add a number to our counting. Or he can just only blunder his pawn
and doesn't take my pawn. I'll take it. Well, it's still fine, now if he can just go bishop F8
to blunder his king, and even though it also blunders the rook and the F pawn, we'll only
be at 8 out of 10, but I get a checkmate to win the challenge. Of course that doesn't happen.
That blunders another pawn. 3 out of 10, this is getting a bit serious.
King D7. Alright, so in this position, there should be a forced checkmate at his king.
I found nothing. Queen E6 check. King E8. Alright, change of plan. Queen F7 king D7 queen E6 king E8
queen F7 king D7 draw by repetition. The challenge only said that I have to finish the game,
not winning it, therefore, mission, accomplished.
[Music]