100 rated chess, but you had way too much caffeine, every 5 moves you go afk to have
explosive diarrhea.
Let's say, 2 minutes.
You may be wondering why it takes me so fast to carry out such thing, let's just say I
have some secret skills.
We get a 1 0 5 from the Philippines.
E4.
The plan is very simple.
If I have to afk 2 minutes every 5 moves, I technically only have 10 moves to finish
this game.
Therefore, let's try to do it in 5.
E5.
Bishop C4.
A light square bishop is definitely one of the strongest weapons against a black king.
G6.
Ah ha.
What a coward.
He's obviously trying to prevent queen H5, so if I play queen F3 right now, he will most
likely be able to see the threat immediately and prevent it from happening.
So I guess, D4.
He takes D4.
I'll develop my queen this way.
It's gonna be hard to think about a quick checkmate, but there is no problem to think
about a quick free rook.
Or bishop.
Queen takes G7.
Knight E7.
Ah ha.
That blunder's a king, but according to the mission, I have to go afk after 5 moves, and
now since 5 moves have passed, I'll answer some of your comments during the free time.
I obviously definitely really don't like ads, but I love your videos, heart heart heart.
But I like ads, so I don't like you.
Can't comprehend the incomprehensible.
I'm not a chat.
Coward.
You would want to be white to actually win this challenge.
This challenge said that I needed to impress my Asian parents, and if you think I can do
that just by switching sides, I can easily tell that you're not an Asian and don't have
any Asian friends.
Resignation.
Mission.
Accomplished.
[Outro Music]