It's the 14th of July, aka the United States National N*** Day.
And yes I also cannot believe YouTube demonetizes a word that is used for a national holiday.
But anyway.
100 rated chess, but opponent's queen doesn't have clothes on,
my pieces and pawns must not look at her.
Sounds easy enough.
We get a 1-0-3 from Greece.
E4.
For those of you who are wondering why my queen isn't included in the challenge.
I also don't know.
E5.
D4.
Queen g5 immediately makes my bishop gone blind and ends the video.
But who plays like that anyway?
Right?
No doubt.
Capturing this way is obviously dumb.
I'll capture this way instead.
He mimicked the capture.
Queen takes.
And in no world do you copy my move.
You know what?
I changed my mind.
Only my queen sees his queen, and as you might have thought,
it is absolutely okay for a woman to see another woman n***.
So the video continues.
Queen a4 check.
And I'm not cheating.
Knight c6.
There is no such thing as attacking the queen for a tempo.
Knight f3 instead.
b5.
That blunders a pawn, but it is too risky to create such a tactical position with his queen included.
Avoiding is best.
f5.
Ah ha.
He's probably planning to go queen e4 which forces a queen trade,
and since the challenge needs his queen to operate,
I cannot allow that to happen.
I mean as long as he doesn't blunder his queen anymore,
this video will be totally under my control.
What the f-
[outro music]