New Year Chess, you give away 2 pawns, 0 rooks, 2 bishops and 2 knights, but if your opponent
refuses, the video ends. Nice. I don't think I will have any problems playing with only a queen
and 2 rooks. We get a 3-0-2 from France. E4. C5. So I guess we can start with the pawns. D4.
C takes D4. Yes. Taking back the pawn will make it a trade, and not a giveaway anymore. Therefore,
C3. D takes. Perfect. I think today's video is gonna go really well guys. But anyway, now I'm
being down 2 pawns, but if I take his pawn back, it will turn out that I only gave away 1 pawn
instead of 2. Therefore, Bc4. Of course you will continue to take. Right? No. It doesn't count,
because I still haven't taken that pawn back yet, so it's still a full giveaway of 2 pawns.
Bf7 check. K takes is forced. Nf3. It's getting kinda annoying that I can't sacrifice my other
bishop, due to his pawn can just go all the way down. Qb6. Very aggressive. Qc2. Just please take
this pawn and let me develop my bishop. G6. Fine. Ng5 check. Perfect. And you know what,
since he keeps refusing to take, I think I have an idea. Nd2. I'm planning that after he takes
my knight, I'll go Kf1, D takes c8 changing gender, and I'll take his new woman, which still
keeps the 2 pawns count, which means I'll be fulfilling all of the mission's goals.
Unless he refuses to take my knight and end my video.
Well, happy new year.
[music]