100 rated chess, but you don't reveal the challenge.
And somehow this idea got 18 brilliant votes.
But anyway, we get a 118 from Italy.
And you know what, if I take on this post normally,
the game will be too easy and it also won't make any sense because I always
need some sort of challenge in order to make a video.
Therefore, let's say that I will uncover this very suspicious black section
after I've captured my opponent's queen.
d4. According to the challenge, I can actually play this game like a
normal person. Therefore, let's try to win this game
real fast with the England gambit. Gambit declined. Well if he doesn't take
mine, I'll take his. Now he takes.
c5. In case you don't know, developing a deep pawn as the first move makes the
position become very positional and very hard to attack his king,
so if he can at least blunder a piece right now, that will make things a lot
easier for me.
Well, very convenient. I'll take it. b4. That blunders a pawn.
c3. I'll go back this way. queen a4. Very aggressive. Queen c7.
Man since I'm playing this game in an absolutely normal way,
there are not many things happening for me to talk about.
e4. That blunders a rook. Bishop takes c3 check. Knight takes c3.
Queen takes c3 check. King e2. Very aggressive. Queen takes a1.
Let's just hope that he won't resign the game before I capture his queen.
Queen b5. Knight c6. Threatening knight d4 forking his king and his queen.
Well maybe I don't have to. But now the question is,
do I take his queen? If I take his queen right now,
I will have to uncover the suspicious black part in the challenge,
and since it got 18 brilliant votes, we can be sure that it is something either
very nasty, or very stupid.
Well as always, I'm not a coward. Alright, let's see what is going on right here.
The video ends you f***ing idiots.
[Music]