100 rated chess, but it's April Fools, you have 5 turns to lose.
A short video confirmed, but since I'm actually a bit busy these days, I'll take on this one.
We get a 148 from the Philippines.
I have no idea what is the connection between losing in 5 moves and April Fools, but E4.
E5.
Alright, so in order to lose this game as fast as possible, Queen H5, some people may
wonder why I'm playing the literally strongest move against the new players when I'm trying
to lose.
Well, trust me, I have a plan.
Knight F6.
Ah ha, that blunders a pawn with a check, and of course since I want to lose this game
instead of winning it, I'll take that pawn.
Again, trust me, I have a plan.
Bishop E7.
There is no need to move any other pieces because this game will only last until move
5.
Queen G5.
I know you guys are getting very panicky as I keep unnecessarily attacking him which requires
him to defend his position which prevents him from attacking me, but once again, I have
a plan.
H6.
Ah ha, that blunders a pawn and allows my queen to infiltrate into his position, but
since I need to lose instead of win, I'll take it.
Rook G8.
My secret weapon?
Resignation.
Ha, gotcha bitches, and since the video is so short, I'll answer some of my comments
instead.
Chess, but stockfish ends my video.
In case you don't know, stockfish is not that powerful.
LOL you are funny, subbed.
Plus one baby.
You only use condoms once question mark exclamation mark question mark exclamation mark.
That is why I always suggest a man to have at least 10 pieces in his wallet.
The outro was nowhere near giga chad as the rest of the video.
Or permaband.
(crowd cheering)