100 rated chess, but your pawns are not allowed to touch any of your opponent's pawns.
Well, knight f3, of course I'm not gonna push pawns too early, and if he can just blunder a
pawn right now, that will be very convenient. f5. Very aggressive. Knight c3. e6. I want to
push this pawn to open up my queen and bishop, but if he goes f4 next, that will make his f-pawn
touches my e-pawn, which ends the video. Therefore, d3. Bishop c5. Bishop g5. Bishop e7. Bishop f4.
I mean as long as he doesn't play something like c5 and c4, the video will be absolutely fine.
Alright, knight e5. Okay now it is very clear that the c4 square is heavily controlled, so in no
world do you push that pawn. Thank you. e3. I'm threatening queen h5 g6 knight g6 hg6 queen h8 to
finish this game real fast before he can end my video. And he saw it. Bishop e2. d6. Bishop h5
check. I mean g6 will make the game really complicated, but I'm sure he's just gonna take it.
Perfect. Queen takes h5 check. g6. Knight takes g6. I mean my knight is no longer controlling the
c4 square, but he should be able to see, that c4 is just blundering a full rook and probably the
king as well. Right? There we go. Queen takes h8 check. I mean if he can just pull his bishop
down to block the check, that will help me. A lot. Of course it doesn't happen. Queen g7. Knight c6.
Long castle. Alright, now he should be able to see, that c4 is just opening up my rook straight
towards his king, so in no world that move should be played. Right? b6. I'll take this pawn. Bishop a6.
Ah ha, that move is obviously telling me that he wants to go c4. But again, my rook will be opened,
and maybe his target is actually to trade pawns and then target my a-pawn, therefore, a3. Now there
is no reason to play c4 anymore. It's like every single time, when my opponent ends my video,
Stockfish gives them a compliment.
[Music]