If a piece, not pawn, doesn't protect anything, the video is unprotected.
Playing 3 minute splits on a 100 rated account. Let's go, we get a 1 17 from Canada.
So now the most obvious threats are pushing the center pawns, because a move like e4 will
make his g1 knight not protect anything, which means it ends the video. No, that is not fair,
so let's just say, that the knights in starting position, doesn't count. And with that said,
the video continues. Bishop b5 is obviously the next threat. So I guess, a6. Well, actually,
a move like g3 also make his bishop not protecting anything, which is also unfair,
since I cannot do anything about it, so let's change it to, the entire starting position,
doesn't count. And I'm not a coward, it's just to make the rules a bit fairer.
Knight c3. e5. Again, the starting position, doesn't count. Bishop c4. For those of you
who can't see, this bishop is still guarding this pawn. Knight c6. Queen h5. Very aggressive. g6.
Queen f5. That blunders a queen. e takes f5. d5. Oh wait I blundered a pawn. I mean taking his
queen made my adrenaline rise so high that I couldn't properly control myself. Bishop takes.
It's fine, it's just a small pawn anyway. Knight ce7. Bishop takes f7 check. Man,
look at this bishop. It went from f1, to c4, to d5, to f7. And then to hell.
Knight e2. Not very aggressive. I'll take this pawn. d3. Bishop g7. Oh, wait. My bad.
Ha! Not even close. h6. And the best thing is, there is no way he can end my video anymore.
What the f-
[Music]