100 rated chess, but your king is h***. He needs to capture the opponent's queen himself before the
game ends. Pretty complicated, but I have a plan. We get a 1 61 from Tunisia. D4. E5. In order to
take his queen, I need to open the way for his queen. It's lit. Knight c6. A casual England
gambit to bring my queen out, and if he sees me bring my queen out, he'll also bring his queen out.
Knight f3. Queen e7. Bishop g5. Queen b4 check. There usually is a bishop on f4,
but since his bishop is not attacked right now, big chance he'll make a mistake.
There we go. That blunders a pawn. Knight d2. Another free pawn. I've been taking a lot of
pawns, it is time that he wants to trigger a queen trade, which I definitely won't agree to,
but I will manage to bring his queen out of her bedroom. Or not. Queen a5 then. I guess I'll have
to take a few more things before that woman wants to leave her husband. E3. Knight takes knight takes
queen takes. Knight c4. That blunders a bishop. I mean who resigns just because of a bishop anyway.
Right? That is correct. Another pawn dead. The only way to stop a queen is to use your own queen.
Well? I mean offering a draw is also an option, but that usually won't work.
Maybe I was going a bit too far with my captures, but since the video is still so short,
I'll answer some comments instead. How can you be this much better than somebody who is as good as
you, smiley face? I mean I'm better than my viewers, but some viewers are equal to me,
so that happens everywhere. Send this to Gotham Chess for a guess the elo episode.
No he probably won't do that. The paid actor getting a paid actor to make himself look like
a paid actor. Welcome to my channel.
(Music)