100 rated chess, but you have a rook lift every 3 moves.
Very salty.
We get a 198 from Russia.
E4.
Since I'll have to lift a rook on move 3.
H5 is kinda forced.
Bishop E2.
Very aggressive.
Just as I pushed my pawn, he immediately attacked it.
Therefore.
H4.
You know what people say, if you can't protect your girl, just put her in more danger.
H3.
Not very aggressive.
The time has come.
Rook H7 is kinda forced.
G3.
I'll take it.
Opening up more room for my rook to move is always good.
F takes.
This rook doesn't have many squares left to move, and I don't really want to pull it back
to just push it again in the future.
Therefore, A5.
Man, this challenge is getting a little bit annoying.
A4.
Very aggressive.
Rook A7 is kinda forced.
Knight C3.
Ha!
Finally!
After all of those moves, now I finally have some time to develop the other pieces.
E5.
Taking the center baby.
Bishop H5.
Well.
That is very aggressive, but I really don't understand the purpose of that move.
Bishop C5.
Queen F3.
Oh wow!
So Bishop H5 is to attack the F7 pawn with the future queen on F3.
Dude, the creativity is absolutely remarkable.
But anyway.
I have to lift a rook now, but a normal rook lift is just hanging my king.
Therefore, rook takes H5 is forced.
Man, this guy has to be the creativest guy I have ever seen.
Queen takes H5.
It's fine, I still have another rook here.
Queen F6.
I mean since he tried to checkmate me, how about we try to checkmate him back.
Ha!
Noob!
That blunders a king.
Queen F2 check.
King D1 is forced.
Oh, wait.
Even though queen F1 is checkmate in 1, it's actually a third move.
Therefore, rook K6 is forced.
This challenge is going very wrong very quickly.
He takes my knight.
King E7.
Ok dude, now just take my bishop and we can continue to checkmate your king.
Well.
That also works.
Queen to F1.
Checkmate.
Mission accomplished.
[Music]