100 rated chess, but you reveal the challenge after your opponent's third move.
This is the first time that I've had to reveal a challenge after my opponent does something.
So maybe it's actually easy. We get a 157 from India.
E4. E5. Since the challenge is connected to my opponent's moves and not mine,
the best plan is definitely to delay his development, and the most optimal way to do it,
is a gambit.
Qh4 check. G3. This is also very good, because I can force him to retreat his queen right before
the challenge begins, which means his development is absolute zero at the moment I opens that
covered section. Qh6. Alright. Here we go.
What file did that piece come from? You must make only knight moves for the matching number of files,
a is 1, b is 2, and so on. And h is 8.
Worst possible situation, but that's life. E takes f4. Knight c3.
D6. This pawn cannot go down any further. Knight e2. Bishop h3. That attacks my bishop,
but knight move is forced. I mean who knows, if he can just blunder his bishop right now,
that will be very convenient. Well, not a paid actor.
Long castle. Knight hg5. Triple fork looks absolutely amazing. Rook e8. Aha!
Now he's threatening rook takes e4 check, and there's nothing I can do about it.
Well you know what they say, if you cannot defend, you don't defend. Knight takes f7.
Rook takes e4 makes me a fool for ending the video, but you better move your queen here.
Still thinking.
Mission accomplished.
[MUSIC]