100 rated chess, but you do my shopping for me. Materials value is converted to USD.
King's worth 10, I'll cover the cost later. So I understand this as for every point of
material I capture. I'll get $1 in return. We get a 140 from India.
E4. E5. Among all of the challenges I've been through before,
maybe this is the one that I don't want my opponent to resign the most.
Qh5. A very familiar opening, and unlike usual, I can play the optimal moves this game.
Nc6 Bc4 g6 Qf3 Nf6. Nothing wrong so far, and the plan is to avoid taking his queen too early.
Well, I have no other choices. But this is also a big chance for me, because if this guy doesn't
resign after losing his woman, he won't be resigning after losing every other thing.
Ha! This guy. Is so dead. Bc5 d3. We'll start the attack. Nd4.
C3. That blunders a fork with a rook, but that scenario is only good in a normal game,
where I won't be losing my knight after the capture. In this game, this capture is better.
Pawn takes queen takes. Now my queen can infiltrate and deal more damage than if I had taken the fork.
D4. That blunders 5 dollars. King up. 3 more dollars.
C takes d5. He didn't say anything like losing pieces is losing money,
so I don't really care about that useless bishop. Check knight blocks +5. Knight develop. Queen c3
knight e5 queen e5. Alright, here's the situation. His king worth 10 dollars, and the rest of his
army is only 8. Therefore, change of plan, we're not capturing anymore. Next target. Nevermind.
31 dollars in total, but since there is no way I can fail this challenge,
there is no mission accomplished today.
[Music]