100 rated chess, but if your pawn can move, it has to. Very challenging. We get a1 o3 from the US.
a4, my plan is to let him push a center pawn first, and then I'll push back,
which makes my pawn cannot move forward anymore. d5. Yes. d4. Ha, 1 down, 7 to go.
Bishop f5, it's gonna be a big problem if he goes knight c6 knight before attacking my c2 pawn.
So I guess, b4, he should be able to see, that knight c6 will be attacked immediately by b5.
Right? Well, pushing b5 now will allow knight b4, and since I cannot stop knight c2,
c3, let's just hope that he doesn't take my knight with his bishop.
Thank you. b5. Ha, free tempo. Or not. That blunders a horsey. But should I even take it,
though, because if I take his knight, b takes c6 opens up the b file for his rook to attack my
knight along with his bishop. Well who cares, b takes c6. I mean the mission is already very hard,
so losing a few pieces in the process is pretty much unavoidable. b takes c6. 2 down, 6 more to go.
g3. Ha, free tempo again. Queen f6. f3. Rook b8. Oh no here he comes. h4. Rook takes b1. Well,
I was expecting bishop takes b1 winning a knight, but that is actually just a trade after rook takes
bishop takes queen b3 and he'll have to give back a bishop or lose a queen, but sadly, I cannot do
any of those things, due to the rules. Therefore, g4, at least that is kind of a tempo. Bishop g6.
That missed a free rook. But anyway. h5. Bishop c2. Wow, somehow he really did find out the only
safe square. g5. Ok, it's very close to the point that I can move a piece now. Queen f5. e4. That is
a very risky move, but after d takes e4 f takes e4 queen takes e4 check, I can go queen e2 because
I cannot move a pawn during a check, and you know, there is a chance that he will trade queens
instead of taking my rook in the corner, which makes it a really worthy risk. Nevermind. That
blunders a woman. But anyway. g6. Queen takes e4 check. Ok here we go. Queen e2. Please trade
queens. Well that actually helps stop my h-pawn, so it's also kinda good for the video. G takes f7
check. King takes. c4. Somehow I have a feeling that I've just blundered my king. Bishop b4 check.
King f2 is forced. Knight g4 check. King g3. Rook b3 check. Aha! Finally. Knight f3. I bet you have
never seen anyone who develops their first minor piece at move 20 like I do. g6. c takes d5,
let's just move fast to flag him down. g takes h5. That blunders a queen again, but d takes e6
check. King takes e6. That blunders the queen one more time, but sadly. d5 check. King takes again.
a5. One more move, and we go all out. Rook d3. That move shows that he's panicking from time
shortage. a6. And he ran out of time. Mission accomplished.
*outro music*