100 rated chess, but pawns cannot capture. So the useless guys are getting even more useless.
For both sides. Let's go. We get a 2-0-1 from India. E4. Aha! Scandinavian is just asking him
to end my video, E5 may invite him to play D4, which is also not good for the video, and knight
C6 is just inviting bishop B5, which forces my knight to move again, since I cannot take back
if he takes my knight. Therefore, B6. Let's get things slow and steady. Knight F3. Bishop B7.
Knight C3. G6. Nothing crazy so far. Bishop C4. Bishop G7. Castle. Aha! He's obviously baiting
me to go bishop takes C3, thinking that after D takes C3, there is bishop takes E4 winning a pawn,
but he actually has knight G5 D5 F3 bishop takes C2 queen takes D5 queen takes D5 bishop takes D5
C6 bishop takes F7 king F8. And it's just an equal trade, but my king cannot castle anymore,
not to mention that it ends the video from the very beginning. Knight H6. D4. I'll castle.
Knight G5. Very aggressive. Now E6 should be really good, but pushing my center pawns doesn't
seem to be a good idea for the video, not to mention that he can also play D5, which is an
absolute disaster. Therefore, knight A6. Let's just go slowly and wait for him to make mistakes first.
Queen F3. Aha! He's obviously baiting me to go bishop takes D4, which allows him to go queen D3,
forking my bishop and my knight, and since I cannot take his knight due to the video's sake,
I'll have to lose a piece. So I guess, knight F5. Of course he cannot take my knight due to the pin,
but actually, I think I still have blundered a piece.
Oh well who cares anyway. As long as my video doesn't end,
it doesn't really matter how much material I have.
I can already see that a lot of people are gonna say, "You did that on purpose." But anyway, what the f-
[music]