100 rated chess, but a peasant uprising is brewing. If there are any pawns alive at the
end of the game, both players lose. Okay so technically I don't give a shit if my opponent
loses or not, so this actually means, I lose. Great Worm Gold. I mean having a great worm is
cool and all, but golding it, is not very suggested. E4. In order to let my pawns die,
I need to push them. E5. Still theory. D4. Alright, the first conflict of the game,
and if he can just capture all the way down to the B pawn, that will be very convenient.
Sadly he's not a paid actor. Knight F3. I'm sorry Edward, but you'll have to die sooner or later
anyway. Edward is dead. Bishop E2. Take this pawn too please. Or not. C3. On second thought,
maybe I should have blot with my knight to provoke him to take my pawn to attack my knight.
There were three twos in that sentence. Bishop A5. Since he didn't want to take my pawn,
I'll take his pawn instead. Both sides need to lose pawns, not just me.
D6. I'll take that as well. Bishop B6. That sacrifices another pawn. Queen D8 checkmate in
one by the way. Ah ha. Instead of taking my pawn back, he went for knight D7 blocking the queen's
weight of the checkmating square, obviously to flex that he can see the checkmate threat.
B4. Back to the pushing pawns plan. Bishop takes F2. That blunders a bishop, but the question is,
do I even take it though? If I take it, I will have a 3 points material advantage, which may
cause him to resign, but if I don't take it, that may mess up some special plans he has inside his
mind when decided to sacrifice his bishop. And then also resign from the game, not to mention
that my viewers are gonna call me a coward. So I guess, I have to take it. I mean it's fine,
like who resigns just because they lose a bishop anyway. Right?
[Bloopers]
Well I actually saw that was coming, so there's no what the f*** today.
[Outro]