100 rated chess, but pawn lives are sacred. No pawn can be harmed during the filming of this video.
An extremely difficult to the point of impossible challenge, but since this specific guy has
donated me a lot of money, I'll do it this time. We get a 100 rated guy from France.
Fun fact, I played a lot of chess in July, but don't remember seeing any French opponents,
so this guy is probably the first one after a month. G3. Of course in no world I'm pushing
my center pawns, but he will. Bishop G2. Another pawn push will give me a bunch of headache,
but he should be able to see, that my bishop is aiming at his weak B7 pawn,
so it would be better to keep his D pawn defending his rook. Right?
Ha! He's even more careful than I thought. B3. Queen C7. I don't know what that move does,
but no threat anyway. Queen E5 bishop E5 expected. Didn't happen. That blunders a pawn,
but the rule is against me, knight F3. C4 will be a bit problematic, but as it hasn't happened yet,
it'd be better to just ignore it for now. D4. Knight A3. More control over C4 to prevent it
from happening, and furthermore, I actually have a secret plan with this sneaky horsey.
Queen C6. He's pinning my knight into my bishop, which is very dangerous,
so I'll unpin myself first. Knight F6. Knight E5. Since I cannot take his pawns,
the plan is very simple. I win his woman, he resigns, game over.
Exactly as planned. You see, when I played knight A3 a couple of moves ago,
I have already calculated that his queen will move from C7 to C6 to B5 and die to my horsey,
knight takes B5. Restoration. Mission accomplished.
[Music]