100 rated chess, but if you can blunder a pawn, you have to.
Very challenging. We get a 100 rated from Mexico.
Ha, 100 versus 100, this is going to be fun.
E4. It's actually pretty bad that I got the black pieces in such a difficult challenge.
But anyway. B5 is kinda forced. As the rule mentioned, I have to blunder a pawn, if I can do
so. Bxb5. F5 is forced. This is going very wrong very quickly. Exf5. Qh5 check is obviously the
biggest threat. Therefore, Nf6. C4. Aha! Finally, there is no more pawn that I can blunder.
A6, somehow I have a feeling that he's gonna blunder his bishop right now. And it really
happened. Bxd7. I solemnly swear, that this guy is not a paid actor. Or at least, I didn't pay him.
B4. Very aggressive. C5 is forced. It's fine though, because I think that I will have to
lose all of my pawns before I can play the game normally. Bxc5. Aha! Once again, no blunders
available. Bxf5. Qa4 check. Bb7. Bb2. Aha! That blunders a queen, but sadly, I have to blunder
a pawn. Okay man, take my pawn. Oh please just take it. Aha! That is even better. Even though
I can play g5 to blunder my g-pawn, I'm already having my e-pawn being free, and since he can
only take one pawn at a time, I think we can all agree, that I don't need to blunder many pawns at
once. Therefore, Bxa4. I mean there is some chances that he's just gonna resign right now.
Maybe not. Bxc5. Nxe5. No pawns to blunder, so I guess, I'll take a pawn. Nxe2. Castle.
H4. Very aggressive. G5 is forced. Wow! Now after Hxg5, H6 is forced, which blunders my knight,
and my queen cannot even take back, because I need to leave my h-pawn free for his rook to take.
This guy is totally destroying me right now. Nevermind. Nxe4. Hxg5. H6 is forced.
Ba5. That blunders a bishop. Gxh6. That blunders a king, and even though there is a checkmate in 2,
as a grandmaster once said, if you have a checkmate, look for a better one.
Or something like that. Qxd2 check. Kf1 is forced. Rxf2 check. Kg1 is forced. Rxg5.
Rxg2 check. Kxg2. Qxe2. Checkmate.
Mission accomplished.
[Music]