100 rated chess. But it's Pride Month, all of your pieces, not pawns, must not move straight.
It's very weird that the only individuals on the board that can change gender are the only things
that don't take part in the challenge. But who cares anyway. We get a 132 from Cambodia.
E4. Again, pawns are not included. D5. I'll take it. Queen takes. Knight C3. A knight definitely
doesn't move straight. Queen E5. Bishop E2. I mean even though diagonals are actually straight lines,
we all know very clear that the challenge giver did not include them.
H5. Very aggressive. Knight F3. Queen E6. D4. Bishop D7. Bishop F4. At this point,
I dare to say that I'm 100% going to win this super easy challenge. B5. D5. Queen A6. A4.
I mean this move is actually not that good because my rook is totally exempted from this
game due to the rules, but maybe this guy is an unpaid actor. Thank you. That blunders a woman.
Knight takes A6. I actually cannot castle. So queen E2. This queen is just a bishop in disguise.
Rook B8. Very aggressive. But that blunders a horsey. Rook takes B2. Ah ha. Knight takes A4.
Please take this knight and blunder your king. Or not. Knight E5. I know you want it.
Dude. I actually believe that this guy sees the checkmate threat.
Knight C5. Before you jump down to the comment section and type "Trash YouTuber you blundered
your horsey disliked unsubbed", I just want to say that Stockfish thinks this move is excellent.
And yes I did blunder my horsey that does happen sometimes.
E6. Ha. That blocks the bishop. Queen C8 check. King E7 is forced. Now there is queen C7 king E8
queen D7 checkmate in two. But my queen is just a bishop. So bishop G5 check. No disrespect,
but I don't think he has the gut to go king D6. Yeah. No disrespect. Queen D7. Checkmate.
Mission. Accomplished.
[Music]