100 rated chess, but you resign when you have mate in 1. A loss, is a win. We get a 1 53 from India.
e4, f5, the renowned Duras gambit. Which is a bad opening.
He takes f5. Queen h5 is very dangerous. Knight f6. Queen e2. d5. Knight c3. I'll take this pawn
back. The only way I can win this challenge is to create a very difficult to see checkmate in
1 that my opponent fails to see and I also need to keep my opponent from resigning the game.
That blunders a horsey. It's fine, I mean who resigns just because of a horsey. Right?
Of course. Queen a5. Knight f3 knight c6. Enough material developed, now I only need to find a way
to set up a tricky checkmate. Knight h4. My bishop should be used to control his king, bishop c2.
Queen d3. That blunders a queen, but I definitely don't want to take it because
it only provokes a resignation. And my bishop is trapped.
What kind of situation that a queen gets to trap a bishop by staying on a same color square.
And on the same f***ing diagonal. And he offered a draw. The challenge requires me to resign,
so of course I cannot accept this. Knight b5.
What the f***
is