100 rated chess, but your king is riding your opponent's horses. If they go up,
your king will go up. If they go down, your king will go down. This may go very wrong very quickly.
We get a 6d9, I mean 690 from the US. Ha, this guy is pretty high rated,
so hopefully he won't make weird moves that can end my video quickly.
E4, I'm opening up some space to move my king up, but of course,
the best case scenario, is still not moving the king up at all.
C5. Sicilian. Knight F3. That is actually really bad though, because I've seen a lot
of low rated players who play knight C6 here, which is not good for my king.
Wow, this has to be the first time I've ever seen a low rated player plays the correct second move
of Sicilian theories. D4, and since he's been playing all the correct moves, he'll definitely
take this pawn, right? Knight C6. Fine. King E2. Man, now there's knight takes D4 check,
king E3, knight takes F3, and I'll have to continue advancing my king instead of recapturing.
This video is going very wrong very quickly. Ha, not even close. Pushing the pawn to attack
his knight is obviously a bad idea. Therefore, C3. E5, aha, that pawn now took away the E5 square
from his knight. Therefore, D5. Now after he pull his knight back, I can finally pull my king back.
Or he can just play knight A5 and absolutely ruin my plan. Thank you. King E1. Ha, easiest mission
of my entire channel. Now knight C8 ends the video, because my king doesn't have any squares
to go down. But of course, no one plays like that anyway. Right? What the f-
[Music]