I'm better than my viewers. Master vs Rookie. This looks absolutely horrible for white,
but I'm not a coward. Males females and gmales, welcome to another I'm better than my viewers
video, and the viewer who's gonna lose to me today is a guy called grill master Cullen Rules.
Now I have 2 choices, retreat a queen and lose the other queen for free, or trade 2 queens for 2
rooks. Losing a queen means losing 9 points of materials, trading 2 queens for 2 rooks means
losing 8 points of materials. So I guess, I'll choose the latter. Rook takes E6. Let's give a
check first. I mean who knows, maybe he'll think that this is checkmate because his king cannot
move so I can get a free win and I can tell my viewers that he actually resigned. But of course
that doesn't happen. I can retreat my queen now, but that will give him a free turn to take my F
pawn. So I think I'll sacrifice her. Rookie takes F6. Knight F3. Defending my F pawn, and on second
thought, maybe I should've taken this rook instead so I can defend my C pawn first as he wouldn't
have the materials to attack my F pawn. Yeah. My bad. Knight C3. At least I'll try to cut off the
rook's connection. Nevermind. Have to take that. Rook takes. It's actually pretty amazing that a
900 rated guy can see that my pawn is pinned to my queen and rook D1 is also a checkmate in 1.
Bishop A3. I don't know, just a random move to delay rook C1. Rook A4. Bishop takes rook takes.
E3. Making room for my king to escape, but to be honest I don't think he can survive.
Rook down rook takes rook takes. Bishop B5. I mean who knows, maybe he'll give me enough
time to castle and move my queen out of danger. Sadly he's not a paid actor. And after a few
moves more, I lost, but as usual, since I started from a worse position,
I'm better than my viewers, but this guy, and only this guy, is equal to me.
[Music]