100 rated chess, but you're a terrorist, sacrifice a piece at opponent's king every 4 moves.
Disclaimer. I'm not a terrorist. We get a 1 0 7 American.
E4. E5. Still theory.
Knight's E3. Vienna game, and I prefer, the Andersen defense. I actually don't know anything
about this opening, but the guy's name sounds cool. Knight A4. Ah ha. I'll have to sacrifice
a piece at his king on move 4, and at the moment only my bishop can do that. So even if I retreat
it, his knight can still take and the video will have to end, not to mention that he can also play
D4 blocking my bishop's view, therefore, bishop D4 is kinda forced. This is also really good as
I can provoke C3 blocking his knight's way of going back. Exactly as planned. Here we go. Bishop
takes F2 is forced. King takes F2. I have 3 free moves before something else has to die. Knight F6.
H3. I don't know what that move is for. Knight takes E4 check.
King E1. Ah ha. Now queen H4 is best, but then I'll have to make a sacrifice on move 8,
so if he respawned queen H4 with G3, my queen will be put in danger, and even queen takes G3
is not possible as that is not a sacrifice. So even though it is really difficult, I think we'll
have to skip this amazing chance.
Well, mission accomplished.
[Music]