100 rated chess, but you've got a cold, every second move you sneeze and have to move a piece.
Not porn, at least 4 squares. 4 squares obviously sounds way too difficult, so let's change it to
3. Not gonna lie, it still sounds pretty impossible. We get a 1 1 4 from the US.
D4. So in order to have a lot of squares to move my pieces around, we need to open the board.
A counter gambit. I really want to take his pawn, but since it is my second move.
A2, knight c6. Let's count. 1, 2, 3. Which is to say, that every knight move is absolutely
following the rules. F3. I'll take this pawn. C3. A2, 3 square move, knight f6. I mean he can go cd4
and these center pawns are gonna cause a ton of trouble for me, but I didn't really have any
choices. Thank you. Now I can take this pawn. B takes. A2, bishop c5. 1, 2, 3. Knight e2.
D5 should be the best move here, but since I don't want to take too many risks,
d6. To be clear, I'm not a coward, I'm just trying to be careful. G4. A2, 3 square move again.
Knight e5. I'm threatening knight d3 checkmate in 1, but since it is so obvious,
I don't think there's much hope in achieving it. Wow! Knight d3, checkmate.
And here I thought it was absolutely impossible. Mission accomplished, but since the video is
still so short, I'll answer some of your comments instead. Get rid of the cringed outro. Dude,
this entire channel is cringe. I bet you all my friends that in the first 3 moves, you must have
played a few games to find someone able to defend the queen and bishop mate at the start. Smiley
face. No, you lost the bet, I only played once, and in fact, the 100 rated people are actually
good enough to defend the scholar's mate. Now even though you've lost the bet, taking all of
your friends obviously sounds way too cruel, so let's just say that I'll only take the girls,
you can keep the dudes. Quack. Video spoilers, your permabanned.
*outro*