100 rated chess. But simp is a pacifist, which means no checks, no captures, no attacks.
No. I'll just allow myself to attack, because just moving the pieces around is pretty much
already attacking something. And with that out of the way, let's start the game.
We get a 100 rated from the US. E4. Since I cannot capture anything,
taking center space is obviously not necessary. B6. Bishop C4. Bishop B7. Even though I'm attacking
his E pawn, once again, we already removed the attacks part from the challenge.
Queen H5. Very aggressive. G6. That's actually nice though, since I'll probably fianchetto my bishop
anyway. Queen F3. Ah ha, he's probably thinking that after knight F6, he can go E5, which wins
a horsey, since his queen pins my knight to my F7 pawn. Therefore, E6. Everything is still going
according to plan. That blunders a queen. But I cannot take it, due to the rules.
But I also cannot move my king away, due to some bigger rules.
What the f- Wait what?
Ha. Mission, accomplish. But since the video is so short, I'll answer some of your comments instead.
Do not get checkmated one more time. Man, this guy sounds so angry. Please just look at the
thumbnail, the challenge literally required me to do so, which means I didn't really have any
other choices. Simpy yells at this guy for sandbagging, even though he is a sandbag. Oh wait.
I didn't see anything.
[Music]