I'm better than my viewers, Fortress. Looks fun. Welcome to episode 13 of I'm better than my
viewers, and the challenger this time is a guy called Star on Da Great, exclamation mark.
I will be playing black this game, and even though Stockfish is saying that black has the advantage,
we all know that it is not true, because all these queens are going to die. So black actually
only has some same color bishops and a few knights, which is pretty impossible to deliver a checkmate.
B takes a3 discovered check. Queen blocks is forced, well I mean if he can just play c3 to
block his own bishop, that will be very convenient. Of course it doesn't happen. Queen takes is forced,
c3 best move by the way. Or not. Ah ha, now I can go king takes to save my queen,
but then there is still knight a4 check king a2 knight c3 royal fork anyway, and I believe
that situation is actually even worse for my king, therefore, queen takes b2. Bishop fe5.
Of course there's no reason to take his bishop, so I'll take this knight instead. As long as this
thing is still on the board, there is always a chance that he'll mess up. Nevermind. King takes.
Stockfish obviously doesn't know how to evaluate this position, because now I have to somehow keep
all of my horses alive, and just for context, there is already one about to die. Bishop f6 check.
King takes c2. Ah ha, now please go knight d4 check and then take my bishop so that I can move
my knight out of danger. This guy is totally destroying me right now. I'll take this horsey,
oh, wait. Maybe I should have taken this pawn first. Yeah, that was unfortunate. I have to
take that. It's fine, my knight didn't really have any moves anyway. Another horse dies. Knight takes
g2. Alright, at least these 2 guys are safe, let's just hope that they can make it all the way to
the white king. B4. Bishop c4. Need to stop those pawns first. King h6. Ah ha, that king obviously
wants to run out of the fortress, therefore, knight takes d2. Alright, now just go king g5
and give me a free tempo to go knight f3. And he saw it. Knight f3 anyway. King g7. Ha, after an
unsuccessful attempt to break out, he has become really sad and decided to go back inside the
prison. But anyway, it was in this position, I decided that there is no way I can checkmate him
with this limited amount of materials, so I offered a draw, and surprisingly, he actually declined the
offer. Yeah, even this 900 rated guy knows that he is the one having the advantage here, not me.
Bishop g6, just a random move, I needed time to think. Bishop ef6. Knight e1, that is one of the
3 safe dark squares left on the entire board. Knight takes e4. Ah ha, that move is threatening
to win my knight, and even though there is knight d3, my knight won't be able to go anywhere after
that, therefore, let's take a risk. Bishop takes e4, I'm removing my bishop from controlling the
b5 square, so let's just hope that he'll push these pawns to give me some free moves to develop my
knight. Maybe not. And now since I only have one knight left, there is absolutely no way I can
checkmate him, so after just 2 more moves, we agree to a draw. Which is to say, that, I'm better than
my viewers, and if you don't agree that I'm better because Stockfish said that I have the advantage
from the start, well, who cares.
[Music]