100 rated chess, but you must deliver a super checkmate, opponent's king should not be able
to escape from checkmate even if his pieces could move twice in a row. So to make it easier for you
guys to understand, in this position, queen takes f7 is a super checkmate, because even if his king
can take my queen, the dude will still be in check by my light square bishop and there is no way to
get out of it, which is to say that his king was actually checkmated twice. Maybe some people still
haven't understood, but I don't give a shit. We get a 1 47 from India. e4. e5. Still theory. d4.
Since I want to super checkmate him, pawns won't have many useful effects, so I would rather let
them die. Unless he doesn't want to take. Bishop g5. Knight c6. f4. Let's try to be really aggressive.
Knight b4. What is better than having 2 center pawns? Having 3 center pawns. Knight takes e4.
Ah ha. That blunders a woman, and even though I really don't want to take it because it may cause
my opponent to resign, logically speaking, I of course need to remove his queen so my pieces can
have a lot of safe space to move around, so I guess, bishop takes d8. Bishop e7. He wants to
castle, and I cannot let that happen, so I also have to take this bishop. King takes is kinda
predictable. Bishop c4. Alright, let's try to super checkmate real fast before he decides to resign.
Knight c3. I'll take that too. And that wasn't such a good idea.
You know what? This challenge is absolutely impossible, it is already difficult enough
just finding a normal checkmate, not to mention about resignation, abandonment,
or running out of time, there is obviously no way I can do this. Have a great day.
[Music]