100 rated chess, but if your opponent blunders a piece, not pawn, you have to undo your last move.
Well, I guess we also have to say, not king. Very challenging. We get a 132 from Belgium.
E4. Knight c6. Not very aggressive. D4, now if he plays knight e5 blundering his knight,
I will have to undo my last move, but since my last move is pushing d4, I cannot move my pawn
back, so knight e5 is actually ending the video. But I mean, who plays like that anyway. Right?
Of course. He takes d5, once again, since my last move was also a pawn move.
It cannot be undone. So in no world do you blunder your knight like this.
Yes. Knight f3. A knight move is better than a pawn move, because I can always move it back.
Well unless he takes my knight with his queen.
Thank you. Man, it feels like this guy can always end my video at any times he want.
Knight c3. Of course I cannot take his queen due to the absurdity of the rules.
But you know, he doesn't know about that. Or maybe he does. That blunders a woman,
but sadly, knight b1 is forced. What kind of challenge is this?
F6. Alright, now c4 attacking his queen should be better than knight c3 again,
but I mean if he still leaves his queen there, the video ends since I cannot move my pawn backwards.
Therefore, as much as I hate it, knight c3. Well I mean this is already the second time
I attack his queen like this, there is no way he doesn't see it this time. Right?
Queen e4 check. Well he did see it this time, but still blundered his woman in a different way,
and since it is a check, I cannot undo my previous move.
What the f-
[Music]