I'm not worse than my viewers.
Well technically that is correct, but the name was I'm better than my viewers.
Porn Mountain.
Let's go.
Ladies and gentlemen and gays, welcome to another episode of I'm better than my viewers.
The series that I made so that my viewers will stop bats eating me, but apparently it didn't work.
And the viewer this time is a guy called...
Ember.
I'll give a check first.
King takes.
I'll take this porn.
Queen takes.
That blunders a queen.
E6 double attack on the royal couple.
On second thought, maybe queen takes was actually a good move because queen e8 will just be
blocking his king's way back to safety.
King e8.
I'll take that woman.
Alright, now both of us are maidenless, the game truly begins.
D takes e6.
I'll give another check.
Who knows, maybe he'll decide to go king f7 blundering knight e5 check king f6's forced
g5 checkmate in two with a pawn.
Right?
Of course it doesn't happen.
I have to take that.
King takes.
C takes b6, solidifying this side of the board.
E takes d5.
Knight e5 check.
King e8.
I'll take this rook.
I mean since he already had a queen in this game, if he can just let me also have a queen
for myself, that will be the nicest thing ever happen to me.
This horsey still dies.
Rook a8 again.
B5.
Rook b6.
There's not much I can do on that side anymore.
I'll switch to this side.
Rook takes b8.
I'll take this rook.
Rook takes.
G5.
Rook h7.
A4.
Rook back to h6.
Wow.
I have no idea why that was even an option, but I'm not gonna refuse it.
Rook takes.
And then we just shuffled our pieces around for the next 20 moves.
F4.
I know a lot of you guys hate it when I skip moves, but for real guys, there was absolutely
nothing to see, except the fact that I managed to push a lot of pawns forward.
Knight takes e4.
F5.
Double attacking his knight and his rook.
Rook g5.
I'll take this horsey.
Rook takes f5.
D6.
Rook d7 cd7 king d7.
And then we shuffled pieces again, we traded rooks, I made a queen, I took his rook, I
made another queen, I checkmated him.
I'm better than my viewers.
.