100 rated chess, but if the bishop sees a pawn, the video ends.
Another impossible challenge, but the truth is I'm really lacking ideas these days,
so I actually don't even have a choice. We get a 190 from turkey. I mean in the very
starting position, the bishops are already looking at a lot of pawns. Therefore,
let's change the challenge to, sees a different colored pawn. The video ends.
D4. Aha, now bishop F4 seeing my C pawn, or bishop G5 seeing my E pawn is ending the video.
Therefore, E5, I mean he can still play bishop F4 to end the video, but who plays like that anyway?
Right? Of course, but now bishop E3 is also ending my video, and since there is actually no way to
defend it, knight C6. If I attack his pawn, he has to defend his pawn, which means he can't end my
video. There we go, and that move was also really good for me, because now I can go, bishop C5.
My bishop now doesn't have to see his F pawn, and even though E3 ends the video now,
who plays like that anyway? Right? That makes sense. F6. I'm provoking him to take my pawn,
so that he won't play E3 or A3 to end the video. Perfect. Knight takes, since he saw I moved my
knight, now he'll move his knight too. Man, I'm so good at reading these guys. Knight G4. Alright,
now comes the problem. Now E3 should be the best move with the idea of sacrificing a pawn to save
the king, but since sacrificing is not very natural, let's just hope that he'll play knight
E4 defending the F2 square instead of E3 ending my video. Yeah, or not playing any of those moves.
Bishop F2 check. King D2 is forced, queen E7. Oh no my horsey, and he should be able to see,
that now E3 is blundering a king. Right? Of course. Another impossible challenge done.
Queen to E3. Checkmate. Mission accomplished.
(upbeat music)