100 rated chess, but you blunder your queen, every time your opponent blunders a piece.
Not pawn. This is going to be short. We get a 1-16 from Argentina. As usual, E4.
C5. Sicilian. Knight F3. E5. Aha, the very famous, ja-la-la bad variation.
But anyway. I'll take the free pawn. I remember that I once learned about the ja-la-la bad
variation, but it's been a long time since then, so it's actually pretty scary that I may get caught
in his opening preparation. Nevermind. That blunders a rook to queen H5 check G6 knight
takes G6 H takes G6 queen takes H8, and even though I have to blunder my queen according to the rules,
I haven't gone for that line yet, so to make things fair, knight back to F3. I didn't play
queen H4, so he didn't blunder his rook, which means I don't have to blunder my queen. Everyone
is happy. C4. That blunders a pawn, but do I even take it though, because that pawn opens up the way
for his bishop to go to A3, which blunders a bishop, which means I'll have to blunder my queen,
and since there is no way for me to do so, I'll have to end the video instead.
Well, no one plays like that anyway. Bishop takes C4. Once again, this is not a thing.
Thank you. D4. I know that allows bishop C5 ends the video, but I have faith that he's not going
to play it. Knight G4. I really want to play H3 knight back bishop takes, but somehow I have a
feeling that he's just gonna take my F2 pawn and blunder his knight, which forces me to blunder
my queen. So I guess, E5. D takes E5. D takes E5. I'm actually amazed that he hasn't taken my F2
pawn yet, since most 100 rated opponents I've met always play like that. Nevermind. That blunders a
horsey, and as the rule mentioned, blundering a woman is forced. I mean keeping the queen on D1
for him to take is also fine, but I have a feeling that he's just gonna take my rook, which allows me
to retreat my queen. Well. That's sad. I'll take the knight. Alright, now just calm down, and move
your bishop away from my pawn, because you know, if he blunders another piece, I'll have to end my
video, since I have no queen left to sacrifice. Yes. Bishop E3. Alright. Take it. And my king
will join the battle. Or not. Knight C3. H5. Very aggressive. Rook D1. A6. This guy really doesn't
want my king to be in danger. Knight E4. H4. That blunders a pawn. Knight takes C5. B takes C5.
Bishop takes C5. H3. Ah ha! I think I have an idea. Knight D4. I'm calculating, H takes G2,
knight F5, G pawn changes gender, knight takes G7, checkmate. Ha! Perfect plan,
except if he blunders a piece to end my video before that.
What the f-
[Outro]