100 rated chess, but you are playing as Spain vs Costa Rica, you must capture 7 of your
opponent's pieces or pawns, without losing any of your pieces or pawns. Well, I guess I'm losing
subs from Costa Rica. We get a 268 from the US. Knight f3. Pushing center pawns is obviously too
risky. So I guess, knight f6. Taking 7 different pieces or pawns is a very difficult task,
so if he can just play e4 or g4 blundering a pawn right now. That will be very convenient.
I solemnly swear, that this guy is not a paid actor. Knight takes g4. Alright, 1 down, 6 to go.
Bishop h3. Aha, so normally I would play h5 here so that if he takes my knight I can open up my
rook. But just for this game, I have to retreat it. Knight c3 b6 b3 not very aggressive bishop
e7 bishop a3 g6 d4 bishop g7. Nothing wrong so far. Knight e4. Aha, that blunders a horsey.
But do I want to take it though, because if I take his horsey, he may feel bad about losing
an entire piece, which may lead to an instant resignation. You know what? I'm not a coward.
At the end of the day, I mean who resigns from the game just because of a single horsey anyway.
Right? No doubt. Castle. Queen d3. Aha, that queen technically cannot take my knight because
my bishop is defending it, but based on my experience, you can never trust the 100 rated
guys to notice that. Therefore, I'll move my knight back. No need to rush, I only need to
sit here and wait for my opponent to make mistakes. Knight e5. That blunders a rook,
and even though taking it is very risky because it can lead to a resignation, I need to make
progress. Beginners don't tend to use their rooks very often, so I don't think that he'll resign
just because of a rook, and as long as he doesn't take anything too crazy, this challenge is still
very doable. What the f-
[Music]