100 rated chess, but you reveal the challenge after your 5th move. I'm pretty concerned that
there is only one type of reaction, and it is even more concerning that the reaction is a laughing one,
Keck W. But let's go anyway. We get a 127 from Egypt. Knight F3. This knight totally
prevented any attempts to scholar checkmate, I guess I'll go for a gun bit. Didn't happen.
Not yet, knight F6. Stafford gambit, also didn't happen. A counter gambit,
and since I'm not a coward like him. I'll take. Knight takes. I can take this pawn,
but as I'll have to uncover the challenge after 2 moves, it would be better if I can
make more development beforehand. Bishop C5. Knight E2. Ah ha. Even though I said I should
be focusing on development, I'll take. Bishop takes F2 is checkmate in 1, and if we're lucky enough,
the challenge should not interfere with this plan. You really need to use the restroom,
you have 5 more moves, before you wet your pants. For your information, I never really have to go to
the toilet, because I actually built a pipe system that connects my desk with my house's toilet.
So I can literally just poop right here and then the shit will find their own way to the toilet.
But you know, a challenge is a challenge, and I guess we only need 1 more move.
Nevermind. This check is best, but that cannot win the king, queen H4 instead.
Queen takes E5. He probably thinks that I will take and blunder my woman.
But no. A resignation should be coming. Right?
Queen B4 check. No more time for development,
I'll have to find a way to checkmate in 2 with 2 pieces.
King D1. Queen B2 is best, but that won't create a checkmate, and since he didn't resign after the
woman loss, I don't think he'll resign because of the rook. Knight E4 instead.
Knight D2. Alright. Here we go. Queen takes D2. Backward bishop moves are very difficult to see,
now he's gonna think that he is actually checkmated and the game is bugged out.
Game is bugged and turn off is fun.
[outro]