100 rated chess, but you reveal the challenge on the 12th move. Not many challenges can get this
many reactions, so I have to say that I'm very eager to uncover it. We get a 128 from Mexico.
Very handsome. E4. Knight c6. d4. Take over the entire center. Knight f6. Tips for the beginners
out there. Don't play like this. E5. In case you are wondering why I suggested you guys avoid this
opening, I'm pretty sure you're going to see the reason. Right. Now. There we go. Queen takes g4.
And guess what, I'm pretty sure the other horsey will also be blundered very soon.
I solemnly swear that this guy is not a paid actor. Queen takes d4. d6. Bishop c4.
F6. I think Stockfish wants me to take on f6 right here. But I actually prefer, e6.
Completely locking down his position, so maybe he's gonna sacrifice a queen to make room for
the other pieces. Of course that doesn't happen. Let's play a little bit tricky. Bishop g5. Oh no
my bishop. F takes g5. That blunders a rook. Resignation. And since I can only uncover the
challenge on the 12th move, I guess we have no challenges today.
Don't worry, I'll be back.