100 rated chess, but it's a build your own challenge.
Create your challenge by clicking any three of the options below.
This guy is secretly saying that I'm a coward.
So first of all, f*** you.
And secondly, a very renowned human being once said,
"Only kids make choices, adults take all."
Let's go. We get a 151 from Vietnam.
E4. The first thing I need to consider is obviously rule number 4
keeping at least one of the four knights dim on the rim at all times.
Knight H6 is kinda forced.
Queen H5. I can only use one bishop according to rule number 3,
and since I'm playing black, my dark bishop should prove more value.
Queen takes H6 ends the video as it breaks rule number 4.
But who plays like that anyway?
Knight F3.
Rule number 7 requires me to move my king exactly one time this entire game,
and as you might have guessed, there is only one choice.
Knight E5.
Castle.
This knight concerns me a lot as knight takes F7, rook takes F7,
he can go queen takes F7 check and I cannot capture that woman.
But to be honest, the chance of that continuation happening is even lower
than the chance of you having a girlfriend in the next 10 years.
Exactly. No harsh feeling by the way.
This bishop is attacking my dimming knight, so I need a backup horsey.
Both bishops capture and there is no way I can save this video,
but no one plays like that in such an open position.
And I did not see that coming.
Bishop A6 ends the video, but since there is no real way to stop it,
and also there is no way I'm turning down this queen,
I'll take.
I mean since he played that move in 0.3 seconds,
there is no way a resignation can happen right now,
but he should be able to see, that he should take this pawn first
to attack my rook instead of taking my knight.
What the f-
[Music]