100 rated chess, but everyone got a chance.
All of your pieces, not pawns, must check your opponent's king before they die.
Not only will they check, checkmate.
We get a 2 26 from somewhere around the world, it seems like chess.com forgot to add the
flag for this guy.
Very racist.
E4.
E5.
Since I'll have to attack his king a lot.
King's gambit.
King's gambit is risky for my king, but it also creates a lot of initiatives for me to
attack his king.
Gambit accepted.
Queen h4 is a threat.
Knight f3 book move.
D6 book move.
D4 book move.
This guy is scaring me by continuously making book moves, I'm down to resign if g5 happens
now.
Of course.
I'll take this pawn.
a5.
That weakens b5 a lot, I'll take this pawn first.
D takes e5.
Bishop b5 check.
In case you haven't noticed, this guy hasn't even developed a single piece yet, so bishop
b5 is forcing him to finally make a first piece move.
Or king.
Queen trade is legal as that is a check.
But I don't like it, knight bd2.
Rook a6.
That blunders a rook and a knight, but my bishop is much stronger than his rook, and
there is also no reason to waste a move on a horsey that will never be developed.
Knight e5 instead.
I'm starting to feel the tension, let's try to end this quickly.
Rook e6.
Queen f3.
You may say he's threatening to take my knight which hasn't given a single check yet, but
since his rook is also as active as my knight, who plays like that anyway.
Right?
Ha!
Doubters.
Long castle.
f5.
Knight takes e4.
Fe4 queen e4.
Alright, now my setup should be strong enough for a checkmate attack.
So as long as he doesn't make a crazy capture.
What the f-
[Outro music]