100 rated chess, but it's bullet hell, whenever any of your pieces or pawns get attacked,
their next move must dodge it, they cannot capture if they are being attacked.
Including pawns into this is making the challenge absolutely impossible. I'll eliminate this part.
And I'm not a coward. We get a 179 from the US.
D4. E5. Nothing better than an England gambit against a 100 rated opponent.
D takes E5. Knight C6. Knight F3. Still theory.
Shout out to the beginners out there, this opening is actually very bad for black,
so in case you want to be safe and play the game in a more serious way,
I would suggest you avoid this opening and learn something a bit more casual.
Queen E7. Well, but if you want to have some fun and destroy your opponent quickly,
feel free to learn this opening and get destroyed in case your opponent also knows the theory.
Bishop G5. Ah ha, that bishop is attacking my queen, and according to the rules, I have to move
her. Check. Knight FD2. That blunders a pawn. Knight F3. You have been disconnected, please
refresh the page to reconnect. No I'm fine thank you. That blunders a rook. I guess we can all
easily agree that this guy is not a paid actor, and he's simply just being destroyed by my England
gambit. And thus he decided to also blunder a horsey. Queen D1. Ah ha. His queen is attacking
my queen, so my woman cannot capture anything, and is also forced to move. C3. That blunders a pawn,
but again, since his pawn is attacking my queen, queen back to B6. I mean a move like queen D7
check will be forcing my king to move, but since I have no choice but to capture his queen,
it will make me look like a fool for ending my own video. But who plays like that anyway? Right?
I'm worrying too much. Bishop C5. I mean what can go wrong anyway?
Queen D5. Wait. That blunders the F pawn with a check, but this queen is attacking two pieces,
so which one do I move?
What the f-
[outro]