100 rated chess, but the number of reactions is how many points of material you have to win.
Open parenthesis, exactly, close parenthesis.
Buy.
And to make it fair, promotions, do not count toward the challenge.
Too easy.
We get a 1 0 5 from America.
With premium membership.
There were 27 plus 11 equals 38 total reactions.
And let us count.
8 pawns are 8, 4 minor pieces are 12.
Rooks are 10, queen is 9, so we have 39 points of total materials able to be captured.
Which means if I lose 2 pawns or more, the video ends.
Too easy.
Since I don't want to lose any material this game.
E3.
Knight F6.
The original plan was to use only my queen to capture his entire board,
but now since he's stopped the threat.
Bishop C4 instead.
D5.
Bishop E3.
Bishop G4.
Blocking with a knight is obviously stupid because if he takes the video immediately ends.
F3 is kinda forced.
Bishop H5.
If I cannot attack his king side, I'll attack his queen side instead.
E6.
Queen B5 check.
Knight C6.
I'll take my first pawn.
1 down, 37 more to go.
And disclaimer, this playstyle of only moving a woman is not recommended at any rating levels,
don't try this at home.
On second thought, maybe do try this at home.
Queen takes A8.
D4.
That provokes a trade, which is not good for this video as I can only lose a pawn this
entire game.
So I'll give a check first.
C6.
Now I'll take this pawn.
I mean he should be able to see, that taking this pawn is blundering everything left on
his queen side.
Right?
Frick.
Queen B8.
I guess it's fine, I'm allowed to lose a pawn anyway, so all I have to do is to not losing
anything else.
Queen D8.
Bishop check.
Knight blocks.
Queen takes A7.
And in no world do you take this pawn.
No world.
Well even though I haven't managed to reach 38 points yet which means the challenge is
not accomplished, the video also didn't end abruptly, so I'll just end it here.
So I'll say this is a draw.
[Music]