100 rated chess, but before starting the game, you must pick a number from 0 to 10, then
reveal the challenge.
Of course I'm not gonna just simply choose a number.
To do this completely fair and square.
We'll make it random.
Very simple.
Our number will be a random integer from 0 to 10, then we print out the result, and since
my computer doesn't know what random is, I'll make him read a book called random.
Here we go.
Result is 1, I'll uncover the challenge.
The number you chose is the number of pieces, and/or pawns, you must capture during the
game, no more no less.
This is not even a covered challenge as you can just write the entire thing down all at
once and I'll still do the randoming part.
But it's fine.
We get a 100 rated American.
C4.
Since I cannot take too many pieces and pawns, the only way to open up the challenge, is
to let him take mine.
Nevermind.
E5.
Let's play as aggressive as possible.
Knight F3.
Bishop C5.
He finally took a pawn.
Queen F6.
Knight takes F7.
Ah ha.
Here comes the problem.
He's blundering a massive check, but if I take the check, that is not a checkmate, so
I'll have to continue playing without capturing anything more while also be losing a rook.
The other option is to take the knight, but there is no initiative after that.
Alright.
I'll take this check.
King D2.
The plan is very simple.
Queen E3 check.
Draw by repetition lets go.
Didn't happen.
We need more materials.
Knight C6.
I mean since his king is heavily attacked, there is no way he's taking my rook.
Right?
Knight B4 check.
King C3.
Another chance for a repetition, but I'm not taking it anymore as I may be called a coward.
D4 check.
King B3.
A5.
Oh no my woman.
Ha!
I bet this guy will never believe in women after this game.
A4 king A3 knight C2.
Double checkmate.
Mission accomplished.
[Music]