100 rated chess, but you don't have a premium subscription. Each piece, or pawn, can only move
5 times throughout the game and then its free trial ends. 5 times obviously sounds way too easy,
so let's change it to 3. Now that is a bit more fair. We get a 100 rated guy from the Philippines.
E4. Since I can only move each thing 3 times, the best way to do it is obviously
to go as far as possible. From now on, my E pawn can only move 2 times more.
Bc4. Moving a queen or a bishop out doesn't sound like a very good idea as their moves
are very flexible and there can be a lot of chances to make good use of a move in the future.
Therefore, I'll move a horsey. Nf3. Nf6. I mean I don't have much faith that a 100 rated guy knows
about the fried liver attack. I'm very sorry I underestimated you. Alright then. D5. Exd5.
Ok so the next book move should be Na5 attacking this bishop, but for this game, I think I'll go
for, the Alvastad variation. The internet usually mentions this as the Levi-Rosman variation,
but no, it's actually the Alvastad variation, and in case you are wondering who Alvastad is,
I have no idea, but trivial matters aside, let's see if he can see the best move of Bf1 Nd4 c3
Nd5 cd4 Qg5 Bb5 Kd8 and the position is still very balanced. No he didn't. Qxd5. Well I mean even
though he didn't see the best continuation, our positions are still absolutely fine.
Well, that resignation is kinda what the f*ck, but since I won the challenge,
mission accomplished instead.
(outro)