100 rated chess, but every time a bishop moves, a piece has to move up.
Well, that sounds too easy, so let's change it to "you move your king up".
And you know what? That is actually still too easy. So furthermore, I cannot take my opponent's
bishops. Yeah, now that is enough challenging for a video. Let's go, we get a 2-1-0 from the US.
With premium membership. E3. A bishop move will force my king to move up, but if I play a move
like d5 trying to stop bishop c4, it will just provoke him to play bishop b5 check, which actually
doesn't even allow my king to move up, which means I'll have to end my video. Therefore, e5,
bishop c4 and king e7, are expected to happen next. Or not. Now knight c6 should be the best move,
but after bishop c4, I'll have to go king e7, which allows queen takes f7, and even though
it's not a checkmate, I don't think I should let that happen. So I guess. D5. Let's just disallow
bishop c4 first, because if he doesn't develop his bishop, I won't have to advance my king.
Well, I guess I still have to advance my king sometimes. King takes f7 is forced.
Man, I totally didn't see this coming. And I also didn't see that coming. King f6.
E4. That blunders this bishop again, but of course, I cannot take it, due to the rules. D takes e4.
D3. Ah ha, now I have a chance of pulling my king back, but you know what, that sounds very coward.
Therefore, E takes d3. I will not pull my king back, he will either stay here, or move forward.
I solemnly swear, that this guy is not a paid actor. Man, it's gonna be a big problem if I
have to disclaim the paid actor stuff like this in every video. King f5 is forced. This is really bad,
if he somehow moves his bishop again, it's king g4 forced, and then my king cannot move forward
anymore. And it really happened. Wow, this guy is absolutely destroying me right now. Wait what?
Ha! Mission accomplished.
[Music]