100 rated chess, but you reveal the challenge after 2 captures.
Too easy. I will win without even a single capture. We get a 1 33 from India.
C3 E5. D4. Ah ha, he's provoking the first capture of the game, and since I only have 2
captures to spare for this entire game, E5 is kinda forced. I mean who plays F3 anyway? Right?
D5. That allows bishop C5. This looks very promising.
D6. For some very unknown reason this guy is trying his best to force a capture,
and since I don't want to play a move like C6, I guess I'll allow it. And you better try to
defend your king, or you can also distant your queen away from your king to put him in greater
danger. First capture of the game, and it is absolutely worth it. For those of you who are
arguing that I said I was gonna win this game without any captures, I'm very disappointed that
you actually believe those words. King D1. This loses a bishop, but that is the second capture,
which will activate the challenge, and even though I'm absolutely not scared of the challenge,
avoiding risks is never to be underestimated. I mean this still loses my E pawn,
but he won't be able to see a short distance backward queen move.
That blunders a woman, but the challenge.
You choose to honor the loss of materials by only being able to move the material
captured before the challenge began, which means I can only move pawns.
And this very undeveloped bishop.
B6. I'm blundering my queen, but she doesn't move, so who cares anyway?
Well it seems like my opponent cares about my queen more than I do.
C5. This is all I can do at the moment.
*Sado music*