100 rated chess, but progress is hard, after every 2 moves forward, you must make 1 move
backwards. Sounds absolutely impossible, but as we all know, I'm not a coward. We get a
164 American. E4, that is 1 move forward. E5. Ah ha, so my favorite move right now against
the 100 rated players is D4, but after D4, I'll have to make a backward move, and apparently
since my pawns cannot do that, I'll have to end the video instead. Therefore, knight C3.
Queen H4 will be very dangerous, but since I'm already defending my E pawn, there's absolutely
no reason to play such a move. Right? Nevermind. Alright, knight B1 is kinda forced. This game
is going very wrong very quickly. Thank you. He is obviously asking for G3 E queen E4 queen
H1, but sadly, I'm not that stupid. G5. Very aggressive. G3. In no world do you take this
pawn and force queen E2 because I have to make a backward move which blunders a rook.
Of course. Backward move. Queen G2. Bianchetto. Queen my queen. Queen F6. Knight C3. Knight
C6. Knight D5. Queen E7. That blunders a woman, but sadly, I have to make a backward move.
Queen back to F6. Ah ha, he's obviously provoking me to go back to D5, and you know what, there's
no way I'm refusing that. Queen E7 again please. Queen E6. Ha, that still blunders the queen
regardless. Knight C7 triple fork. King E7. Testosterone. Now I have to make a backward
move, and it just happens, that there is knight takes E6. I bet he doesn't have enough testosterone
to take with the king. Man. I really underestimated him. Bishop C4 check. King D6. D3. B5. That
blunders a pawn, but again, backward move. Bishop A6. F4. Let's see if he knows about
the famous French move. Ha. No. F takes E5 check. No way he's taking with king here.
Queen F1 is forced. Knight takes C2. That blunders a horsey. Knight F6. Bishop G5. Alright, now
please just make a random move and blunder queen F6 checkmate in 1. Sadly he's not a
paid actor. And in this very position, there is a very easy to see checkmate in 10 for
white, so if you're interested, please feel free to pause the video right now to find
the checkmate, while I don't give you any seconds to do so, because I already saw that
checkmate from 10 moves earlier. I'll take that horsey. Spoiler alert, that move wasn't
the correct move for the checkmate in 10, I wanted to keep the puzzle for you guys to
solve on your own. F6. Ah ha, that blunders a king to queen F6. King D5. Bishop B3 checkmate
in 2, but sadly, I have to go backward. F5. Bishop B3. Rook HF8. Queen F4. Checkmate.
Mission accomplished.
[Music]