[Music]
You're a stupid child, chasing your dreams and getting hurt
You're a bad liar, but you showed me a smile that couldn't be laughed at
You don't even say "I love you" well, you're really clumsy
But, but why did you say "goodbye"?
You're no good, no good, no good
I love you, I love you too much
No matter how strong the alcohol is
Memories that don't waver, like a fool
[Music]
You're a fool, really a fool
You only believe
Pretending to be a strong woman, you bathe in the night wind of sadness
Three years have passed since I became alone
The town has changed
I left only regrets that I had forgotten
You're a really bad man
I'll take off your ring of love
I'll punish you
You're a fool, waiting for an excuse
You're no good, no good, no good
I love you, I love you too much
No matter how strong the alcohol is