100 rated chess, but if your opponent's move lands on an even-numbered rank,
you move a piece. And if it's an odd-numbered rank, you move a pawn. Very challenging,
we get a 298 from turkey. e4. Aha, even-numbered rank, therefore, I move a piece. g4. Very
aggressive. Knight f6, I mean now the situation is gonna be very disgusting if he keeps on moving to
even-numbered ranks like this, but since I'm obviously attacking his e-pawn, d3 or knight c3
is definitely expected to happen. Right? Well, I guess that works too. Knight back to g8. It's
fine, it's not like he can keep on playing with even ranks like this forever. Ha! e5. This guy is
so dead. f4. Another even rank, but this time, I have my bishop. Alright, now just play something
like a4 and allow queen h4 check destroying your king. d4. Well I mean even though that blocks the
view of my bishop, it is still an even-numbered rank move. Therefore, queen h4 check. King f1.
Odd rank move. e takes d4. I mean now knight f3 is very dangerous as it not only attacks my queen,
but the fact that it is an odd rank move also forces me to make a pawn move,
which then cost me my woman. c3. Another pawn move. b takes c3. Ah ha, that blunders a king,
but since that move lands on an odd-numbered rank, I have to move a pawn. Well, I mean at least since
I'm threatening checkmate in one, knight f3 winning the queen is definitely not going to happen.
Wow. That blunders a king, but just like last time, I have to move a pawn. Okay, now there are
two situations. He takes my pawn, I checkmate him, or he takes my queen. I'm f4. But in this very
position, something unexpected happened. I got a power outage. I know this may sound very weird
to some people, but getting an unexpected power outage is actually a normal thing where I'm living
in, which is to say, that I have no other choices, than to end this video right here.
[Music]