100 rated chess, but enemy king is hungry, your opponent's king must consume 3 pieces before you
can checkmate. I don't know why I have to care about whether my opponent is dying from hunger
or not, but let's go anyway. We get a 1 21 from the Philippines. E4. E5. I mean I just have to
play normally, while also being a little bit careful when deciding to trade pieces to avoid
not having enough materials for a checkmate. Bc4. Bc5. Qf3. Nf6. And I mean if he can just
take my knight right now and lose his queen and resign the game, that will be very convenient.
Too convenient to be true. d6. Ng5. Castle. No blunder from my opponent in the first
5 moves, so it should be coming. Right. Now. I should be a prophet. That blunders a woman.
F4. Even though he's lost his queen, he still decided to push a pawn to attack my king side,
which is to say, very aggressive. But that blunders a pawn.
D4. Ah ha. That blunders a rook, but if I take that rook, I'll be losing my bishop,
and since the plan is to let his king take 3 pieces, I actually don't want to make unnecessary
trades. So I'll take this pawn instead. I mean who knows, maybe he'll continue to blunder his rook.
I solemnly swear, that this guy is not a paid actor. Bxh1.
Kf1. Alright, now the challenge begins. Bg2 check. We still have all of our pieces,
so let's sacrifice 3 of them to complete the ritual. 1 down, 2 to go. Ng4. H4. Nh2.
This is actually much easier than I expected. Nevermind. Nc6. Well it's fine, now he'll take
it for sure. I have a very bad feeling about this. G takes, bishop takes, rook takes, knight takes,
king takes. And my knight is still alive. Again, still alive. You know what? Nf1. Maybe g2 was in
his blind spot, so I decided to change square so that he can see my knight a bit easier. Nevermind.
Qxbx. Rx is not in my plan, change of square. Still in his blind spot.
Fxb. As long as he refuses to take my knight, everything I do is totally meaningless.
e5. That blunders a very easy to see checkmate in 7, but who cares anyway.
Ha! Finally. Check check. My knight is unnecessarily defending my bishop.
Nb8. Please take it.
This guy. Is so dead.
I mean that checkmate was a bit clumsy, but I managed.
[Music]