I'm better than my viewers, well at least I'm pretty sure I'm better than the Jerome Gambit players.
Gentlemen and ladies and pride people, welcome to another I'm better than my viewers video,
and today's challenger is one of my strongest viewers, Antti.
Bishop e4 check is too dangerous, I'll eliminate that first.
Queen takes d5. Free woman.
Another woman jumps in. Rook blocks.
Queen d3. Aha! Chess guide, if your opponent has an exposed king, check him until he pins his own piece.
Therefore, check check check check check check.
Bishop c5. Check.
e4. I'll simplify a little bit.
Rook f5.
Queen a6. That forces me to simplify more, and of course, I'm not a coward.
Rook f4. And Stockfish didn't like that move very much.
Queen a takes c6. That knight is pretty much unsavable at this point.
Knight b6 check. I'm spending one move just to distract his queen away from the center.
Horse E is dead. I have 3 rooks afk in the back, let's get them in.
Queen check. King over.
Queen takes rook takes queen takes rook takes queen takes rook takes queen takes.
Rook takes.
King b3. Rook e7 is blundering queen d6 forking my king and my rook.
Therefore, rook f4. Queen h5 check.
Bishop blocks.
Queen e2 check. King h3. No more checks.
c4. Aha! He's baiting me to take his pawn aiming for a trade,
but then he will actually take my pawn and go for a repetitional check or trade his queen for
2 rooks and go for a draw of bishop vs pawn endgame. Therefore, I'll take this pawn instead.
At this point even Magnus Carlsen cannot win this game as black against me,
but we still shuffled our pieces around for the next 20 moves,
which are a lot of moves to edit so I skipped it instead.
Rook check. King over. Rook check. Ladder check mate.
I'm better than my viewers.
[Music]