I'm better than my viewers? Waterloo. Too many pieces, but it's fine. Morning everyone,
welcome to another episode of I'm better than my viewers, and the viewer this time is a guy called
Wanch SB. I'll take this horsey. I mean taking a free piece with the tempo on attacking his rook
can never be a bad decision. Rook h6. Ah ha, he saw that I was having a double attack on his rook
and his knight, so he decided to counterattack on my bishop. So I guess, bishop takes f7 check.
King takes, now I can take this knight. Rook takes a4. Man. I thought we were having fun on this
side, somehow he decided to transfer over to that side. Knight g4. No, I want to play on this side.
Okay it's that side then. Rook takes. Rook h5. I'll take this pawn, it's funny that the
plank pawns are not protected in this position even though both sides have a lot of rooks.
Rook a6. Rook a3. The rooks protect each other through their x-ray vision. Rook takes a3.
Rook takes a3. I mean if he can also let me infiltrate his backline right now,
that will be very convenient.
Well, I guess we can all agree, that a viewer obviously cannot be a paid actor. Rook takes a8.
Knight a6. That knight is actually trapped in the very first place. b5. Knight takes g4.
I'll take that knight first. Rook a6. Ah ha. I'll take this pawn. And then he said,
man I don't know whether I should accept the sack or not. Brah. Queen takes. That blunders a queen.
Knight e5 royal fork. In case some of you guys didn't see it, bishop takes d7 was not a sacrifice
because his bishop was pinned by my rook and his d-pawn was also indirectly attacked by my knight
on d3 through a potential future check. And if you still don't understand anything, well, it's fine.
King d6. Swoosh and sook. f5 check. I mean who knows, maybe he'll decide to go king d6 which
blunders knight f7 checkmate in one with the king in the middle of the board.
Again, not a paid actor. Knight f7. Checkmate. I'm better than my viewers.
[Music]