100 rated chess, but it's my wedding anniversary.
The king and queen must move together to the other side of the board without being captured.
It's been a week since this guy made this donation to me, but as they always say, better
be late than never.
A very difficult challenge, but I'll try my best to make this anniversary go really well.
E4.
E5.
I mean I'll try my best, but whether my opponent will cooperate with me or not, that I cannot
control.
And it seems he won't be cooperating.
I was about to go king E7, but as that is blundering mate in one now.
Knight C6 instead.
Bishop C4.
G6.
Nothing wrong so far, nevermind.
That blunders a woman, but if I take that woman, there is a very big chance that he'll
resign, so I guess.
King E7.
We are making progress here.
Queen H4 check.
Aha.
If I move my king, he may decide to make a queen trade, which ends the video.
Therefore, knight blocks.
I mean if he takes my knight, king takes also ends the video as my king and queen are not
together anymore.
Who plays like that anyway?
Right?
No doubt.
But that blunders a bishop, D5.
I mean I don't want to take a woman, but I'm not saying no to a free bishop.
Nevermind.
That blunders the woman again, but I'll take the pawn.
As long as there is no crazy queen blunder that force my king to leave his wife, nothing
can go wrong here.
Dude.
I didn't even know this move exists.
Well, I have no other choices.
I mean since he literally forced me to take his woman, of course he won't be resigning.
Right?
Ha.
Doubters.
Pawn takes.
We win this game for sure.
Well even though this video didn't go well, I wish you all the happiness with your partner
as you continue your life journey together.
I'll do better next year.
And what the fu-
*Outro music*