100 rated chess, but you're a wingman for your opponent, you must help your opponent
promote a pawn to a queen before checkmate. Okay so I don't think anyone would want to
help their opponent in an intimate relationship, but for the video's sake, I guess we can make an
exception this time, we get a 145 that needs a new wife from Luxembourg. E4. I mean after all of
those crazy hard challenges, this easy one is definitely going to give me a relaxing game.
D5. Ah ha, normally I would have taken that pawn, but just for this game. C4. Alright,
2 choices, there is no way he's not taking one of them. Very convenient.
B3. I mean since he took it last time, there is no way he's refusing it this time. Right?
Absolutely. Man, this game has been going so well until now, and as far as I can remember,
those games that went smoothly in the beginning, usually don't end up good for me.
Bc4. Alright, now I'm having 2 pieces attacking his pawn, so may as well just take something
before it dies, and this may sound rude but I don't believe that he can see Qd4 Qb3 Qa1 Bf7
Kd8 Bg8 winning in exchange. Or he can just not take the pawn and not make the queen fork at the
same time. Nf3. Nd4. Ah ha, now he finally sees the queen fork and is trying to get Nxd4 Qxd4,
but of course, I cannot allow that. Nxf3 check. Qx, I'm setting things up first for a quick
checkmate right after he can have his new woman. Bxa2. Ah ha, that blunders a king to Qf7 Kd7 Qf5
Kc6 Qb5 Kd6 e5 a very well-known checkmate in 4 with a pawn, but sadly, I cannot do that before
he has a new queen. e5, no way he's not taking it this time. Random move. d3. It's fine, I mean how
hard can it be for a chess player to make a new queen when their opponent is obviously provoking
it to happen anyway. Why is he thinking for so long? What the f-
[Music]