100 rated chess, but you are trying to lose. The challenging part is that you have to lose all
your pieces and pawns before you lose. Warning, this challenge is obviously even harder than your
weenie every time you see your crush, so if you are expecting a win from this video, chances are,
it's definitely going to happen. We get a 135 from the US. E4, the pawns die first.
C5. Ah ha, it's been a long time since I last saw a 100 rated guy that knows about the Sicilian
defense. Knight F3. Quite frankly, most of my opponents so far just move their queen next.
This is called, the Sicilian defense, Mon Goobse variation. Which I know absolutely nothing about.
Knight C3. Queen C7. D4. I'm sorry David, but you need to die first. Or not. That blunders a queen,
but if I take that queen, there is a big chance that he will resign from the game, therefore,
bishop C4. Queen takes E4. That blunders the queen for the second time, but still. Bishop E3.
Queen retreats. I'll take this pawn. Alright, since I'm not attacking his queen anymore,
he should have more than enough time to move all of the other pieces. Or not. You know what?
Queen E2. Alright, change of plan, it seems like this guy is doing some sort of challenge that
requires him to only move his queen for the entire game, therefore, I'll let his queen
infiltrate my territory and take as many pieces and pawns before it dies. Exactly as planned.
Fun fact, that move actually still blunders the queen to rook G1. Queen H3. Bishop F7. King F7.
Knight G5. Royal fork, or bishop F7. King D8. Knight G5. Queen F5. Long castle knight C6.
Bishop E6. Queen F6. Knight E4. Queen G6. Knight F7. Check with a discovered attack on the queen,
but once again, I cannot take his queen. Queen G5. That blunders the queen for I don't even know
how many times, but sadly. Bishop D2. It's funny that David was supposed to be the first pawn to
die, yet he still lied until this move. And he will still live. What the fu-
[outro]