100 rated chess, the movie, before you win, you must prove your opponent is a paid actor.
Ha! Too easy, we get a 2 0 7 paid actor from Indonesia.
E4. Since I already paid him and told him to play like a paid actor,
the only plan we have today is to win the game within the first 15 moves.
D5. Ah ha, fun fact, I actually told him to play the Scandinavian defense myself.
I'll take that ball. Queen takes. Knight c3. Most of the normal 100 rated players are just gonna
blunder their queen right now in some way or another, but I actually told my opponent not
to blunder their queen too early into the game, so he'll just gonna pull her back right now.
Just as planned. Bishop c4. F5. Ah ha, I also told him to play really aggressive,
therefore, very aggressive. Knight f3. E6. Not very aggressive. D4. Knight f6. Ah ha,
I also told him to let me pin one of his knights, and since I've just append up my dark square
bishop, he let me pin his knight right away. Knight c6. D5. I also told him that he should
not blunder his pieces in the first 7 moves of the game, now is move 8, so a blunder should happen at
any.. moment.. now.. that blunders a horsey. E takes d5. Bishop takes d5. Knight takes d5. Ah ha,
he chose to blunder his queen because we're almost at move 15, therefore, I'll take it.
A resignation is coming at any moment now. King takes. I'll take this knight as well. Or even
better, instead of resigning, I guess he'll go king e8 allowing queen e5 bishop e7 queen e7 checkmate.
Well, a win is a win, and since all of you have believed that I paid this guy to play against me,
mission accomplished, and even though I should be answering some of your questions now,
none of my viewers are my paid actors, so I actually cannot do that in this video.
[Music]