100 rated chess, but you're a Star Wars fan, you must make the following moves.
C3, Rook 2 D2, Bishop B8. I have never watched Star Wars or read any of their products,
but I'll pretend I'm a fan in this video. We get A1 1 8 from India. C3 is forced. Fun fact,
I actually had to quit a lot of games to finally get to play with the white pieces just for the C3
move. C5. Rook 2 D2 is the most complicated move to execute, so I guess we'll go with Bishop B8
first. D4. C takes D4. Bishop F4. Man. The fact that he pushed his C pawn first to open up this
diagonal makes this guy look like an amazing unpaid actor. Queen A5. Very aggressive. Bishop B8.
Rook takes B8. Alright, in order to perform Rook 2 D2, we're gonna need 1 rook on rank 2,
1 rook on the D-file, and then the rook on rank 2 will move to D2. Therefore,
H4. This rook is going to the D-file, by the fastest way possible.
Queen H5. Rook H3. Knight F6. Rook D3. Apparently this guy is doing some sort of never-pushing
center pawns challenge. Knight E4. A4. 1 rook on the D-file, the other goes to rank 2.
Knight takes F2. Very aggressive. That blunders a horsey. G5. Rook A2. 2 steps done. Now we open
the road. Queen H4 check. G3. In no world do you blunder your queen now to force me capture and
then you resign? Of course. B4. The path is made, nothing can go wrong now. Nothing can go wrong now.
There we go. Mission accomplished, Rook 2 D2. And then somehow chess.com decided to write it as Rook
A D2 instead. Well, if this is the case, then I don't know how to do this challenge anymore.
Apparently chess.com prefers to write down the file instead of the rank,
so if my logic is correct, there is literally no way to make a rook 2 D2. Therefore, mission
Impossible.
*outro*