100 rated chess, but you reveal the challenge whenever you want to.
This is the first time in this entire channel that I get to choose how the challenge is going to happen,
and of course, there is no way this is a loss, we get a 100 rated victim from Australia.
E4. Well, I guess we just play normally until I have a confirmed
checkmate sequence and then I'll uncover the challenge.
E5. Let's try something fun. F4. King's gambit baby.
Queen H4 check. Moving king forward sounds a bit too much fun. G3. And I'm not a coward.
Queen F6. D4. He takes that way. E5. Queen G5. Bishop takes F4. The fact that he refused to
bring his queen back or just simply move her to the other side makes me pretty sure that he's
going to blunder his queen. Right now. There we go. Queen takes H5. And let's just hope that the
challenge doesn't involve my opponent's queen, I mean who the f*** writes a challenge like that anyway.
G6. Queen F3. And also hope that it doesn't ban going backwards, I mean people did gave a
challenge like that before, so no one should be copying that again.
Bishop H6. Bishop C4. Bishop takes queen takes.
D6. Ah ha, that blunders queen F7 king D8 queen F8 king D7 E6 king C6 queen F3 king B6 queen B3
king C6 queen B5 a very textbook and easy to see checkmate in 6 moves. And as promised before,
I will be uncovering the challenge when I have a confirmed checkmate per 10. Therefore,
you must checkmate within the next 2 moves.
How am I supposed to checkmate in 2? When there is a checkmate in 6.
Oh well, I guess I'll play 2 more moves. And now I'll answer some comments instead.
What's a skewer in chess context? It's actually very rare to see a serious question in my comment
section, so I will try to answer this comment in the most optimal way possible. Google it.
Simp should use the YouTube money to get better wifi. Not enough.
I don't believe you, I bet you like to stab people IRL.
Only half true, I only like to stab girls with my meat.
*outro*