100 rated chess, but Edward the E-pawn is the commander. None of your pieces, or pawns,
can move past Edward. And he cannot die. We get a 100 rated guy from Turkey. I cannot move
anything past my E-pawn, therefore, the first move has to be, an E-pawn move. E6. I really
want to push E5 to expand how far my pieces can move around, but D6 and F6 are too much for me to
handle at the moment. D4 instead. E5. That blunders a pawn, but David cannot move past Edward. Knight
F3. E takes D4. I'll gambit. C3. D takes C3. Bishop C4. C6. Ah ha. Now D5 is forking my bishop and my
E-pawn, and even though it normally loses a pawn, the situation is different this time.
C takes B2. Bishop takes B2. It's funny that I have 2 very strong bishops but they actually
don't move very far. C5. Knight B D2. C4. That blunders a pawn, and this time I can take it.
D5. Ah ha. Now I have to make a very important decision. Do I take this pawn? If I take this
pawn, my pieces can advance to the 5th rank, but it also puts Edward in a very dangerous situation
that my opponent can go crazy and decide to take this pawn. But who cares anyway. I mean what are
the chances that he blunders his queen just to end my video right now? Right? No doubt. That blunders
a bishop, but it most likely ends my video, I also don't want knight E3 because I'm pretty sure that
he's gonna blunder his bishop into my Edward. So I guess, I only have one choice. Knight D6 check.
Queen takes D6. Queen E2. This way my queen can pin his bishop into his king and my E pawn is
still being defended by my bishop, and he should be able to see that queen takes D5 very obviously
blundering a woman. Right? Ha. Doubters. But still this is very dangerous, so I guess, I should take
a risk. I'm blundering my horsey, but this is a worthy risk as I'm trying to bait F6 attacking
my knight so that I can finally advance my pawn forward and get everything back under my control.
What the f-
[Music]