We meet again, Black King.
Why do I always have to see you?
Who else do you expect to see here?
I don't know. Candice?
Who's Candice?
Candice NU-
You asked for it. Now I unleash my hidden weapon.
This pawn go. I'll tell you what to do.
Now you should push your center pawn to open up your bishop's way of attacking my newly pushed pawn.
Yeah sure.
Wrong pawn you idiot.
Now move the other one.
Oh how dare you copied my move. I'll copy your move back.
Who's copying who now you moron?
You messed up my entire opening preparation.
D3.
Oh now you dare attacking my pawn.
You know what? How about I let you attack another pawn.
Which pawn are you going to take now you mother-
What an idiot. I'll just take one of those.
If you are given two women to pick, just randomly pick one of them you overthinker.
Oh is that so? How about I give you three choices.
Oh no. What do I do now? No one taught me how to handle this overwhelming situation.
Oh no. Oh no. Oh no. Random capture.
Ha. Wrong move. That let me move my queen.
PFFT. Moving your woman? Now move her again.
You dare challenging me to move my woman again? I will do so.
I push this pawn. Now don't take it and let me fork you.
In your dream. Ha. Watch and learn you noob. This is called a double attack,
which means I'm having two completely separate attacks at your pieces.
And now you can only save one of those two things, which means I'll get something for free.
Ha. Watch and learn you noob. Just move a piece to protect the other one.
Your elementary tactic doesn't work.
Ha. I also calculated that. Your horsey is blocking your woman, so I win this soldier.
So what? I'll let this soldier avenge his dead comrade.
So what? I can move it here. Tick.
Wait what tick? What do you say when you attack your opponent's king?
I check. Then what do you say when you attack your opponent's queen?
We don't have a word for that. And for the gender equality purpose,
I suggest we call that tick from now on.
Okay so you want to tick my queen. I'll move her then.
Some nice battery you have there. Now I want take your bishop.
You want take my bishop, I don't want you take my bishop.
You don't want me take your bishop, I want you take my bishop.
You want me take your bishop, I don't take your bishop.
You can leave your bishop there and I promise to never ever touch it.
You want me leave my bishop, I move my bishop.
That blunders a woman.
I thought we were talking about bishops.
Who cares about dudes.
You want me take your bishop, I don't take your bishop.
You want me take your bishop, I take your pawn.
I want you take my bishop, you take my pawn, my pawn takes your bishop.
I want you take my bishop, your pawn takes my bishop,
my bishop can take your knight, but I'll do it with woman.
Dude I don't have my woman anymore.
That is not my problem.
Oh you dare attack my rook? I will let you do so.
And I will do so.
Ha! It is time for me to deliver my ultimate tactic.
King d7.
I warn you, you better retreat your queen before managing to blunder her in my territory.
Ha! It's like you can touch my woman.
I'll take this pawn.
Maybe I blundered my woman, but I will never blunder my animals.
Check.
So what?
So I move my king.
Since I don't have much time left, I resign.
And technically speaking, you still haven't won the game yet.
[Music]