100 rated chess, but you're fasting, you can't capture until move 10, and after that you can
only capture once every 3 moves. Yesterday was a total disaster, so today we take on an easier
challenge. We get a 100 rated guy from India. E4. Pushing center pawns is definitely not a
good idea as I cannot make any captures in the opening, therefore. B6. Slow and steady,
just like a casual foreplay. Qh5. Bb7. Qxh7 is forcing my king to take his queen which ends
the video. But who plays like that anyway? Right? No worries. Nc6. I mean I cannot take his queen,
but no one said I cannot attack her. And also no one said that he cannot lunder her. Nf6.
I don't really care if he continues to blunder his queen or not, just please don't play this move.
Nb5. Ah ha! He's trying to fork my king and my rook. So I guess. D6. Nc7 can still happen.
Thank you. I cannot let a trade happens right now.
Nbb8. Please stop moving that horsey. You are killing me sir.
That blunders many things in many different ways. But I have to go with. Qc8. This is not a
checkmate by the way. I repeat, not a checkmate. Thank god. G6. The challenge said I cannot capture
until move 10, which means I can start capturing from move 10, and now it is move number 9,
which is the last move according to the challenge, which means if he lets me survive this one move
right here, I will make sure this guy cries all his tear out and never wants to play chess again.
(Music)