I'm better than my viewers. Of course I am, ladies and gentlemen and everyone else,
welcome to another episode of I'm better than my viewers, and the challenger this time is a guy
called, lol3270, with a rating of whopping 1980 points. This is not going to be good. G5. Ha,
what kind of 2000 rated player that blunders a queen fork on the very first move.
Bishop takes H3. I'll take that bishop first, there's no reason to pick a woman when I'm
still having many choices. Queen takes D4. Now I'll take this queen. Queen takes,
trading queens when I'm down in materials is not a very good idea, bishop D2. I'm also baiting him
to take my knight which blunders bishop C3 royal fork, but since he is 2000 rated, I don't think
there's much hope in achieving that. Queen E4 check. Rook E3. Queen F5. I'll give a check.
Since all of his minor pieces are on the other side of the board, if I really start to attack
his king, there is a big chance that I can at least win some queens while he is trying to defend.
King G8. Bishop D3. Queen E6. Ah ha. Very aggressive. He wants me to take his queen,
and then he can recapture with a check, which makes him the attacking side. So I guess,
queen E2. I just want to ask him, do you want to hold on to this strat?
And he does. C5, making room for bishop C4. Knight takes B4. Bishop C4 triple skewer.
Knight D5. Bishop D5 queen D5 rook E8 check. King H7. Ah ha, that blunders a very easy to
see checkmate in 25. Rook H8 check. I can't believe he still hasn't resigned, because even
the worst chess player on this entire planet can still see this very simple checkmate in 25,
there's no way a 2000 rated player cannot see it. King G6 is forced. Queen G4 check.
Queen blocks. Ah ha, that blunders a different kind of checkmate. H5, checkmate with a pawn.
That escalated really quickly. But anyway. I'm better than my viewers.
[Music]