100 rated chess, but it's International Women's Day, your queen is MVP of the game,
making the most captures, the most moves, and delivering checkmate. The last part obviously
sounds way too luck-based, because my opponent will most likely resign the game as my queen
is causing chaos in his territory, so I guess, I'll completely delete that part.
That sounds much better, but before the video begins, have you ever been in a situation that
you are about to checkmate your opponent and then they said, resign right now or I'll expose your IP
address to everyone on the internet? Well, with NordVPN, you don't have to worry about those guys.
Anymore. Is your computer full of malware because you didn't know anything about computer so you
accidentally downloaded them and then don't know how to get rid of them? Well, then I would suggest
you clean your SSD first, and then go for, NordVPN. Are you tired of seeing unnecessary too many ads
on every single website that you visit? NordVPN can remove those ads for you. Are you living in
a country that bans YouTube but somehow still able to find my videos? I bet you are using,
NordVPN. If you are interested, check out NordVPN at their website through the link in the description
below, or if you have too much time to spare, just pause the video and type this link with your own
hands in a new browser tab. Back to the game, we get a 1 1 7 from Italy. E4. E5. This makes my
Epawn is the MVP of the game since he's made the most amount of moves, but in order to move my
queen out, I of course need to make way for her first. Knight F3. Here we go. Queen F6. The massacre
starts here. Knight takes E5. That blunders a horsey, and unlike all of those videos where
there is always a random reason preventing me from taking that horsey, this time, I'll take
it without a doubt. Now my queen is officially the MVP of the game, let's just not let any pieces take
their position away from her. Queen F3. It's going to be hard to play with only a queen. Bishop C5.
Please don't offer a queen trade. Of course I cannot let my woman die on women's day. Queen E7.
Also need to be careful though, I cannot let his queen be the MVP instead of my queen.
My woman is better than yours. Bishop C4. Ah ha. He's trying to attack my Epawn, and even though
my queen is obviously already defending it, there is always a chance that he cannot see it and
proceed to take the pawn which forces a queen trade. So I guess. Knight F6. Completely preventing
the threat is definitely the better idea. And no, I'm not a coward. E5. Very aggressive. Knight C6.
To those of you who are about to comment that I'm blundering a horsey, you suck. Bishop E6.
What kind of move is that? He is sacrificing his bishop just to unpin his pawn, but I cannot take
his bishop with my queen because of a possible queen trade. I cannot take his bishop with my
pawn because that will force him to move his queen more times than I move my queen. I also
cannot retreat my knight because of the F7 pawn. So in conclusion, what the f*** am I supposed to do?
Ha. My queen moved 3 times, which is the most in this game, but she has only captured once,
which equals to his dead horsey. So I guess. Mission. Kinda accomplished.
[outro music]