If a kind of piece goes extinct, for one side, the video ends.
Playing 3 minute splits on a 100 rated account.
Let's go.
We get a 175 from Germany.
E4.
E5.
So the most dangerous things are obviously the queens, because if only one queen dies,
the video will immediately end.
And then he decided to develop his queen first.
This video is going very wrong very quickly.
Knight c6.
Well, technically if he really takes my pawn now, I won't be able to take back due to the
rules, but there's no way he's gonna play like that.
Right?
Thank god.
G6.
Queen g4.
That blunders a bishop.
D5.
Bishop b3.
That blunders a queen, but of course, I cannot take it, due to the rules.
Knight f6.
Now there's no way he doesn't see such an obvious threat.
Are you serious?
D4.
Ha!
Finally.
D takes c3.
Now I have to be careful, because his other knight is invincible.
Ah ha!
Taking his queen is obviously the best move, but actually, it makes me a fool, for ending
my own video.
Therefore, bishop d7.
Queen e2.
Bishop g7.
Knight f3.
Castle.
And in this position, something unexpected happened.
As you can see right here, I was playing the game with a very poor internet connection,
and at this very moment, the white bar turned red.
And it said...
"Reconnecting".
That red thing lasted for about 2 minutes, and at the moment I was finally back to the
game, I saw my opponent had castled.
And my time...
0.
F*** my ISP.
[Outro]