100 rated chess, but Andy and Edward are in love, connect these pawns before you win,
if one of them dies, the video ends. And then the guy below that said. Okay, this is good.
I absolutely don't know where the good part is because this is obviously very impossible.
But of course, let's try it out anyway, we get a 237 from Ireland.
E4. For those of you guys who don't know, Edward is actually the E pawn, and Andy is actually the
A pawn, which is to say, that I need to connect these two pawns together. And as you can see,
they are not very close to each other. E6. The idea is D5, E takes D5, E takes D5,
and then Edward will be a little bit closer to Andy. H4. Very aggressive. D5, of course takes
stakes. Right? Maybe not. Bc5. It's fine, I also need to win this game after the pawns are connected,
so there's nothing wrong to prepare everything beforehand. D4. Oh, wait. I think I have a great
idea. Ne7. The plan is very simple. D takes C5, B6, C takes B6, A takes B6, and then Andy is a
little bit closer to Edward. Yes, I mean people usually don't like to capture away from the center,
but they really cannot say no to a free piece. B6. I mean of course he'll take right,
there's literally nothing else to think about here. Well I mean he can also give an empty check
first, C6. This move also removes a defender of my B pawn, which further provokes him to capture.
Ba4. Nd7. Ha, I'm attacking your pawn, you better capture my pawn when you're still having a chance
to do so. Perfect. And E to B6, and after 8 moves into the game, I finally made some progress.
Bb3. Nc5. Aha, now I'm attacking your E pawn too, so once again, you better take something while
you still can. Very convenient. Edward to D5. Man I'm so proud of myself to be able to get this far
into the mission, now I just need something to capture my knight, and then the mission is completed.
What the f-
[Music]